[
    {
        "question_id": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg_70_shower_tub_101500",
        "episode_history": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located inside the glass enclosure in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A shower tub.",
        "object_id": 70,
        "class": "shower tub",
        "position": [
            2.006499767303467,
            0.08375927805900574,
            6.382257461547852
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6687833601887193,
            0.0,
            0.7434573404941844
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg_74_bath_sink_458208",
        "episode_history": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color pattern of the bath sink that is located below the mirror in the bathroom with striped tiles?",
        "answer": "The bath sink is white with horizontal black stripes.",
        "object_id": 74,
        "class": "bath sink",
        "position": [
            1.7635033130645752,
            0.08375927805900574,
            7.915600776672363
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.18683127338896902,
            0.0,
            0.9823920171112224
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg_199_armchair_322059",
        "episode_history": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there a cushion on the armchair in front of the window in the living room?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 199,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            -2.7757680416107178,
            0.08375927805900574,
            7.7180352210998535
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9998811763949904,
            0.0,
            0.01541535244476366
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg_222_microwave_846005",
        "episode_history": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to quickly heat up my food?",
        "answer": "The microwave on the shelf above the counter.",
        "object_id": 222,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -4.564622402191162,
            0.08375927805900574,
            6.314593315124512
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.415137331250239,
            0.0,
            0.9097587571452277
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg_225_refrigerator_695510",
        "episode_history": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the refrigerator in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A stove with an oven.",
        "object_id": 225,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -1.1395845413208008,
            0.08375927805900574,
            7.847172737121582
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4016512291839534,
            0.0,
            0.9157927113135479
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg_230_dishwasher_595667",
        "episode_history": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the dishwasher located in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The dishwasher is located in the kitchen, next to the sink and below the countertop, near the window with a view of the city.",
        "object_id": 230,
        "class": "dishwasher",
        "position": [
            -4.482060432434082,
            0.08375927805900574,
            9.339299201965332
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.30296557756031045,
            0.0,
            0.9530014999009957
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg_231_oven_and_stove_434043",
        "episode_history": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located between the countertop and the range hood in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "An oven and stove.",
        "object_id": 231,
        "class": "oven and stove",
        "position": [
            -6.422368049621582,
            0.08375927805900574,
            7.955533027648926
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3049363739960867,
            0.0,
            0.9523727252573536
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg_240_cutting_board_878397",
        "episode_history": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the cutting board that is placed next to the knife block on the kitchen counter near the stove?",
        "answer": "Beige.",
        "object_id": 240,
        "class": "cutting board",
        "position": [
            -4.795924186706543,
            0.08375927805900574,
            6.408726692199707
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.38538817024868816,
            0.0,
            0.922754549288362
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00669-DNWbUAJYsPy_183_sofa_seat_47842",
        "episode_history": "00669-DNWbUAJYsPy",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object to the right of the bed and next to the lamp in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A sofa seat.",
        "object_id": 183,
        "class": "sofa seat",
        "position": [
            12.217523574829102,
            0.07263270020484924,
            2.519836664199829
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.200062554594127,
            0.0,
            0.9797831261301003
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00669-DNWbUAJYsPy_190_telephone_392128",
        "episode_history": "00669-DNWbUAJYsPy",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to make a phone call from the bedroom?",
        "answer": "The telephone on the bedside table.",
        "object_id": 190,
        "class": "telephone",
        "position": [
            10.321558952331543,
            0.07263270020484924,
            1.0967018604278564
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7405680506788154,
            0.0,
            0.6719813705109536
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00669-DNWbUAJYsPy_245_laundry_basket_180086",
        "episode_history": "00669-DNWbUAJYsPy",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the laundry basket next to the TV stand in the bedroom empty?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 245,
        "class": "laundry basket",
        "position": [
            8.134953498840332,
            0.07263270020484924,
            2.3806042671203613
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5999594713505498,
            0.0,
            0.8000303948830749
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV_319_bidet_401827",
        "episode_history": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bidet located in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The bidet is in the bathroom, positioned between the toilet and the wooden shelf with plants, near the bathtub with the blue shower curtain.",
        "object_id": 319,
        "class": "bidet",
        "position": [
            -0.4361187219619751,
            3.706296682357788,
            -7.061110973358154
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5599793922082664,
            0.0,
            0.82850653606478
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV_322_bathtub_925177",
        "episode_history": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bathtub with the blue shower curtain?",
        "answer": "The bathtub with the blue shower curtain is in the bathroom, next to the toilet and under the window.",
        "object_id": 322,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            0.2953738570213318,
            3.706296682357788,
            -7.870737075805664
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.479542396133832,
            0.0,
            0.8775187122279633
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV_395_chest_of_drawers_864674",
        "episode_history": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the tall dark brown furniture piece with multiple drawers located near the mirror in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A chest of drawers.",
        "object_id": 395,
        "class": "chest of drawers",
        "position": [
            -4.50847053527832,
            0.10629653930664062,
            -1.6661359071731567
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.985884521729329,
            0.0,
            0.16742672968952904
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV_424_chess_3677",
        "episode_history": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object with a checkered pattern on the bottom shelf of the wooden bookcase?",
        "answer": "A chess set.",
        "object_id": 424,
        "class": "chess",
        "position": [
            0.37994110584259033,
            0.10629653930664062,
            -3.8742687702178955
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6227382827760626,
            0.0,
            0.782430208494739
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV_468_hanging_clothes_970655",
        "episode_history": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color are the hanging clothes that are near the bookshelf filled with various items?",
        "answer": "Blue.",
        "object_id": 468,
        "class": "hanging clothes",
        "position": [
            0.6873124241828918,
            0.10629653930664062,
            -4.569540023803711
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9670699366958151,
            0.0,
            0.25451078079160494
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV_505_newspaper_733906",
        "episode_history": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to catch up on the latest news?",
        "answer": "The newspaper on the bed.",
        "object_id": 505,
        "class": "newspaper",
        "position": [
            4.948899745941162,
            0.10629653930664062,
            -7.62910270690918
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3576345596606436,
            0.0,
            0.9338616180871434
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV_637_radio_971779",
        "episode_history": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there a cat figurine placed on top of the radio on the small table in the hallway?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 637,
        "class": "radio",
        "position": [
            0.8196297287940979,
            0.10629653930664062,
            -3.8391222953796387
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9916031112015754,
            0.0,
            0.12931848226511744
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV_704_microwave_267688",
        "episode_history": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the microwave that is placed on the countertop next to the sink and below the window with decorative items?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 704,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            5.443291664123535,
            0.10629653930664062,
            -0.8209623098373413
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2983677256768608,
            0.0,
            0.9544509941712134
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV_707_kitchen_counter_407069",
        "episode_history": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the microwave on the kitchen counter next to the sink clean?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 707,
        "class": "kitchen counter",
        "position": [
            5.013580322265625,
            0.10629653930664062,
            -1.0854434967041016
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4660324397254085,
            0.0,
            0.8847676334064123
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV_708_dishwasher_72797",
        "episode_history": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to clean the dirty dishes after a meal?",
        "answer": "The dishwasher under the counter.",
        "object_id": 708,
        "class": "dishwasher",
        "position": [
            3.6056289672851562,
            0.10629653930664062,
            -1.1741989850997925
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5354444907491045,
            0.0,
            0.8445704217686244
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV_713_oven_250585",
        "episode_history": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located below the stovetop in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "An oven.",
        "object_id": 713,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            3.5026772022247314,
            0.10629653930664062,
            -1.5204248428344727
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8709705199940503,
            0.0,
            0.49133527585681636
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV_723_fridge_73930",
        "episode_history": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to store my groceries and keep them fresh?",
        "answer": "The fridge in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 723,
        "class": "fridge",
        "position": [
            1.327559471130371,
            0.10629653930664062,
            -1.4571387767791748
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8821995431434655,
            0.0,
            0.47087574377691277
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV_792_toaster_549199",
        "episode_history": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there bread inside the toaster on the wooden counter in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 792,
        "class": "toaster",
        "position": [
            3.3514270782470703,
            0.10629653930664062,
            -1.3059313297271729
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9729288888143859,
            0.0,
            0.23110468907056894
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV_831_spice_rack_222905",
        "episode_history": "00657-TSJmdttd2GV",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to add some seasoning to my food?",
        "answer": "The spice rack on the kitchen counter.",
        "object_id": 831,
        "class": "spice rack",
        "position": [
            5.147034645080566,
            0.10629653930664062,
            -1.3823496103286743
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9302910599666507,
            0.0,
            0.3668222236262762
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm_13_desk_chair_179443",
        "episode_history": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the desk chair that is positioned behind the black desk and near the large abstract painting?",
        "answer": "Beige.",
        "object_id": 13,
        "class": "desk chair",
        "position": [
            1.5083811283111572,
            -3.1826224327087402,
            -0.4878557026386261
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7250295504465237,
            0.0,
            0.688717758576989
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm_16_printer_390403",
        "episode_history": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the printer located?",
        "answer": "The printer is on top of a white two-drawer cabinet in the corner of the room, next to a wall and near a carpet.",
        "object_id": 16,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            3.4253337383270264,
            -3.1826224327087402,
            -1.6619375944137573
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6671497111657531,
            0.0,
            0.744923662459082
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm_86_sink_158998",
        "episode_history": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the pedestal sink located?",
        "answer": "The pedestal sink is located at the end of a narrow hallway, directly under an oval mirror and a wall-mounted light fixture.",
        "object_id": 86,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            0.5295349955558777,
            -3.1826224327087402,
            2.125030517578125
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7006271417511714,
            0.0,
            0.7135275805752599
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm_195_ventilation_hood_574025",
        "episode_history": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the ventilation hood that is above the stove and between the white cabinets in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Stainless steel.",
        "object_id": 195,
        "class": "ventilation hood",
        "position": [
            3.576775312423706,
            -3.1826224327087402,
            7.726710796356201
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3957183276029272,
            0.0,
            0.9183719318441426
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm_196_stove_36153",
        "episode_history": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located on the countertop in the kitchen, directly beneath the range hood?",
        "answer": "A stove.",
        "object_id": 196,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            4.035342693328857,
            -3.1826224327087402,
            4.773653984069824
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9776638906860197,
            0.0,
            0.21017449143194178
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm_197_refrigerator_876144",
        "episode_history": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the refrigerator in the kitchen closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 197,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            0.11780816316604614,
            -3.1826224327087402,
            6.5897064208984375
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.38179256287362423,
            0.0,
            0.9242480397243965
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm_198_microwave_505256",
        "episode_history": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located above the oven in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A microwave.",
        "object_id": 198,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            0.6576387882232666,
            -3.1826224327087402,
            7.219764709472656
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.10502283045805183,
            0.0,
            0.9944698110463581
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm_199_oven_973624",
        "episode_history": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the built-in oven in the kitchen closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 199,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            -0.7469370365142822,
            -3.1826224327087402,
            6.549074649810791
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3788763710741259,
            0.0,
            0.925447294794091
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm_206_dishwasher_369482",
        "episode_history": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the metallic appliance located under the kitchen island counter?",
        "answer": "A dishwasher.",
        "object_id": 206,
        "class": "dishwasher",
        "position": [
            4.054927349090576,
            -3.1826224327087402,
            10.153656005859375
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.19025679908605345,
            0.0,
            0.9817343583686624
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm_317_trashcan_981946",
        "episode_history": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the small trashcan in the room?",
        "answer": "The small trashcan is located under the white desk, next to the chair and near the door.",
        "object_id": 317,
        "class": "trashcan",
        "position": [
            -4.075131416320801,
            0.017377853393554688,
            6.785952091217041
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.16852606880466883,
            0.0,
            0.9856971969795004
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm_403_shower_soap_shelf_126",
        "episode_history": "00366-fxbzYAGkrtm",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I place my soap while taking a shower?",
        "answer": "The shower soap shelf in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 403,
        "class": "shower soap shelf",
        "position": [
            2.929563283920288,
            0.05362018942832947,
            10.939682006835938
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4796761425925025,
            0.0,
            0.8774456098400499
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t_31_washing_machine_572214",
        "episode_history": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash my clothes?",
        "answer": "The washing machine in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 31,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -8.048184394836426,
            0.09944963455200195,
            -5.494609832763672
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9376735623212895,
            0.0,
            0.3475173240627051
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t_49_bathtub_341602",
        "episode_history": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the bathtub that is near the window in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 49,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            -4.49077033996582,
            0.09944963455200195,
            -3.472623586654663
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.43319954663044136,
            0.0,
            0.9012980377206976
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t_71_exercise_bike_501579",
        "episode_history": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the primary color of the exercise bike that is positioned near the window and in front of the wooden dresser?",
        "answer": "The primary color is white.",
        "object_id": 71,
        "class": "exercise bike",
        "position": [
            -5.72144079208374,
            0.09944963455200195,
            1.9611341953277588
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6704196715791162,
            0.0,
            0.741982118355793
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t_86_stuffed_animal_271786",
        "episode_history": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object sitting on the wicker chair next to the wooden nightstand in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A stuffed animal.",
        "object_id": 86,
        "class": "stuffed animal",
        "position": [
            -7.861708641052246,
            0.09944963455200195,
            1.23794686794281
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.1466008870877044,
            0.0,
            0.9891957237600141
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t_97_hanging_clothes_314981",
        "episode_history": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to find something to wear for the day?",
        "answer": "The hanging clothes in the room.",
        "object_id": 97,
        "class": "hanging clothes",
        "position": [
            -7.968873977661133,
            0.09944963455200195,
            1.0555965900421143
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.29070979554700926,
            0.0,
            0.9568112743759952
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t_163_pc_tower_595542",
        "episode_history": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the PC tower on the desk in the home office turned on?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 163,
        "class": "pc tower",
        "position": [
            -1.6002440452575684,
            0.09944963455200195,
            -4.199330806732178
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3983499191493682,
            0.0,
            0.9172335263790198
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t_165_printer_987655",
        "episode_history": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there paper loaded in the printer on the desk next to the computer monitor in the study room?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 165,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            -1.7728281021118164,
            0.09944963455200195,
            -4.165870666503906
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.19623086279224014,
            0.0,
            0.9805577231799325
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t_279_screw_box_361880",
        "episode_history": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to find some screws for my project?",
        "answer": "The screw box on the wooden shelf.",
        "object_id": 279,
        "class": "screw box",
        "position": [
            -6.412153244018555,
            0.09944963455200195,
            -2.2044153213500977
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9955190158281493,
            0.0,
            0.09456156261691354
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t_373_globe_983131",
        "episode_history": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the globe located?",
        "answer": "The globe is on the desk near the window in the study room, next to a red storage box and a bookshelf filled with books.",
        "object_id": 373,
        "class": "globe",
        "position": [
            -0.19709894061088562,
            0.09944963455200195,
            -0.36352384090423584
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9720555435823682,
            0.0,
            0.23475097484523308
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t_515_water_tank_361207",
        "episode_history": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the water tank next to the window in the utility room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 515,
        "class": "water tank",
        "position": [
            -6.193714141845703,
            -2.7005503177642822,
            -5.117247581481934
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6836285717228862,
            0.0,
            0.7298301007249063
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t_533_ladder_911515",
        "episode_history": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the ladder in the utility room?",
        "answer": "The ladder is in the utility room, positioned against the back wall between the shelving unit and the pipes.",
        "object_id": 533,
        "class": "ladder",
        "position": [
            -7.347204208374023,
            -2.7005503177642822,
            -4.959810256958008
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7645680915352138,
            0.0,
            0.6445429647480462
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t_549_ironing_board_763058",
        "episode_history": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the ironing board in the utility room folded?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 549,
        "class": "ironing board",
        "position": [
            -6.220463752746582,
            -2.7005503177642822,
            -5.342201232910156
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8644167035814333,
            0.0,
            0.5027760560820378
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t_580_clothes_dryer_61896",
        "episode_history": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the tall white appliance located to the right of the shoe rack in the utility room?",
        "answer": "A clothes dryer.",
        "object_id": 580,
        "class": "clothes dryer",
        "position": [
            -6.685066223144531,
            -2.7005503177642822,
            -5.189781188964844
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8717594825066596,
            0.0,
            0.4899340819536042
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t_623_oven_604898",
        "episode_history": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the oven that is built into the white cabinets near the kitchen counter?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 623,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            -6.815868377685547,
            -2.7005503177642822,
            1.6141432523727417
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6861459853304176,
            0.0,
            0.727463873202615
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t_625_glasses_610619",
        "episode_history": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the glasses that are inside the wooden cabinet with black drawers?",
        "answer": "Glass.",
        "object_id": 625,
        "class": "glasses",
        "position": [
            -3.3451685905456543,
            -2.6312003135681152,
            0.05057673901319504
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.00314640703659233,
            0.0,
            0.999995050049129
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t_673_beanbag_chair_705208",
        "episode_history": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the beanbag chair located?",
        "answer": "The beanbag chair is in the living room, positioned between the wooden cabinet and the TV stand.",
        "object_id": 673,
        "class": "beanbag chair",
        "position": [
            -3.44295334815979,
            -2.7005503177642822,
            1.489534616470337
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.16979050894515793,
            0.0,
            0.9854801789341804
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t_696_stovetop_432249",
        "episode_history": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the stovetop that is on the kitchen island near the large glass doors?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 696,
        "class": "stovetop",
        "position": [
            -8.742294311523438,
            -2.7005503177642822,
            -0.4650970697402954
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8513209446470796,
            0.0,
            0.5246452603476028
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t_801_air_purifier_591855",
        "episode_history": "00109-GTV2Y73Sn5t",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "Is there enough space next to the air purifier in the bathroom to place a small trash bin?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 801,
        "class": "air purifier",
        "position": [
            -9.296589851379395,
            -2.7005503177642822,
            -2.2250325679779053
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.10986185335628955,
            0.0,
            0.9939468663752209
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_46_desk_chair_742821",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object with a pink backrest and black wheels in front of the desk in the study room?",
        "answer": "A desk chair.",
        "object_id": 46,
        "class": "desk chair",
        "position": [
            -2.404067277908325,
            0.11009860038757324,
            9.88968276977539
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.506426138808562,
            0.0,
            0.8622833443430594
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_68_printer_362593",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the white printer located?",
        "answer": "The white printer is on the desk in the corner of the room, next to a calendar on the wall and a laptop.",
        "object_id": 68,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            -1.7422423362731934,
            0.11009860038757324,
            9.448019981384277
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9111463769997614,
            0.0,
            0.4120828553582503
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_682_printer_211104",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the wooden shelf next to the laptop in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "A printer.",
        "object_id": 682,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            -9.692463874816895,
            0.11009860038757324,
            0.5043601989746094
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9948617919819134,
            0.0,
            0.10124235701791309
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_97_bath_towel_329177",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to dry myself after a shower?",
        "answer": "The bath towel hanging on the wall.",
        "object_id": 97,
        "class": "bath towel",
        "position": [
            -2.483631134033203,
            0.11009860038757324,
            5.6932291984558105
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9270703850017737,
            0.0,
            0.3748873180739285
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_105_bath_towel_667887",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the bath towel that is hanging on the rack near the wall with the painting of a flower?",
        "answer": "Light gray.",
        "object_id": 105,
        "class": "bath towel",
        "position": [
            -2.5045223236083984,
            0.11009860038757324,
            6.728214263916016
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7134567954727281,
            0.0,
            0.700699222915072
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_165_toilet_451043",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located in the center of the bathroom, directly below the shelves?",
        "answer": "A toilet.",
        "object_id": 165,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -2.7817745208740234,
            0.11009860038757324,
            4.479625701904297
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7236147344550605,
            0.0,
            0.6902041118970041
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_193_cart_447038",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the cart near the window in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A bed with stuffed animals and a pink balloon on it.",
        "object_id": 193,
        "class": "cart",
        "position": [
            0.16200104355812073,
            0.11009860038757324,
            5.017323970794678
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7549285501611781,
            0.0,
            0.6558070479581183
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_202_guitar_786808",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to play some music in my room?",
        "answer": "The guitar next to the desk.",
        "object_id": 202,
        "class": "guitar",
        "position": [
            1.1825252771377563,
            0.11009860038757324,
            4.902621746063232
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8334072045296613,
            0.0,
            0.5526594172164766
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_223_plush_toy_535606",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "How many plush toys are on the bed in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "Three plush toys.",
        "object_id": 223,
        "class": "plush toy",
        "position": [
            1.7492291927337646,
            0.11009860038757324,
            5.75091552734375
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.91784886228032,
            0.0,
            0.39693005178585583
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_271_drum_487058",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is the object to the right of the drum near the sofa?",
        "answer": "A black leather sofa.",
        "object_id": 271,
        "class": "drum",
        "position": [
            -0.17626895010471344,
            0.11009860038757324,
            -1.9602006673812866
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6171404794651374,
            0.0,
            0.786852990466161
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_279_wall_clock_212711",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to check the current time?",
        "answer": "The wall clock on the wall.",
        "object_id": 279,
        "class": "wall clock",
        "position": [
            2.8257389068603516,
            0.11009860038757324,
            -0.5005007982254028
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9830219168728633,
            0.0,
            0.18348817658803152
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_292_refrigerator_937543",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to keep my groceries fresh and cold?",
        "answer": "The refrigerator next to the counter.",
        "object_id": 292,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            6.0293288230896,
            0.11009860038757324,
            -1.6358898878097534
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.44455343669622793,
            0.0,
            0.8957523329143904
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_303_washing_machine_213273",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the washing machine located?",
        "answer": "The washing machine is in the kitchen, under the countertop next to the sink and near the door with striped curtains.",
        "object_id": 303,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            4.631935119628906,
            0.11009860038757324,
            -1.5095720291137695
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3262106898415633,
            0.0,
            0.945297088662126
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_307_coffee_machine_873345",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the red and black object on the kitchen counter next to the toaster?",
        "answer": "A coffee machine.",
        "object_id": 307,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            4.797656059265137,
            0.11009860038757324,
            -3.2224526405334473
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6992082642330535,
            0.0,
            0.7149180395179578
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_314_microwave_44508",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the microwave located?",
        "answer": "The microwave is in the kitchen, placed on a small shelf unit next to the stove and under the range hood.",
        "object_id": 314,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            5.859165191650391,
            0.11009860038757324,
            -1.4222139120101929
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9982229777051501,
            0.0,
            0.05958931767909771
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_660_flowerpot_248321",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the flowerpot with the green leaves?",
        "answer": "The flowerpot with the green leaves is in the hallway, near the entrance to a room with patterned flooring.",
        "object_id": 660,
        "class": "flowerpot",
        "position": [
            -10.300386428833008,
            0.11009860038757324,
            1.386165976524353
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.685310737300118,
            0.0,
            0.7282507764095886
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_530_stand_929682",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wooden stand with decorative items?",
        "answer": "The wooden stand with decorative items is in the room near the window, next to the white air conditioner unit and close to the doorway leading to the hallway.",
        "object_id": 530,
        "class": "stand",
        "position": [
            -7.597403526306152,
            0.11009860038757324,
            2.4285192489624023
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7516937662584547,
            0.0,
            0.6595123060020789
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_600_bathroom_towel_520917",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bathroom towel located?",
        "answer": "The bathroom towel is hanging on a rack below the window in the bathroom, next to the white radiator and above a small bench with storage baskets.",
        "object_id": 600,
        "class": "bathroom towel",
        "position": [
            -10.129154205322266,
            0.11009860038757324,
            4.505988597869873
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7553231413029585,
            0.0,
            0.6553525404026682
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_620_bathroom_cabinet_854962",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the bathroom cabinet?",
        "answer": "A wicker laundry basket.",
        "object_id": 620,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            -9.604718208312988,
            0.11009860038757324,
            5.106393814086914
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3536979134668244,
            0.0,
            0.9353597094215759
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_630_bathroom_cabinet_792222",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bathroom cabinet with the wicker baskets?",
        "answer": "The bathroom cabinet with the wicker baskets is located under the window, next to the sink and mirror in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 630,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            -10.351814270019531,
            0.11009860038757324,
            4.980911731719971
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3688358319265872,
            0.0,
            0.9294945557059612
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_687_computer_desk_408732",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the computer desk that is placed next to the large wooden wardrobe?",
        "answer": "The computer desk is made of wood and metal.",
        "object_id": 687,
        "class": "computer desk",
        "position": [
            -9.82638168334961,
            0.11009860038757324,
            -0.04796743392944336
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9968404849984321,
            0.0,
            0.07942951257617992
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_46_desk_chair_47453",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the primary color of the desk chair that is in front of the white desk with shelves and various items on it?",
        "answer": "Pink.",
        "object_id": 46,
        "class": "desk chair",
        "position": [
            -2.404067277908325,
            0.11009860038757324,
            9.88968276977539
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.506426138808562,
            0.0,
            0.8622833443430594
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_68_printer_557251",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the white object on the desk next to the calendar in the home office?",
        "answer": "A printer.",
        "object_id": 68,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            -1.7422423362731934,
            0.11009860038757324,
            9.448019981384277
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9111463769997614,
            0.0,
            0.4120828553582503
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_682_printer_654834",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the desk next to the laptop in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "A printer.",
        "object_id": 682,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            -9.692463874816895,
            0.11009860038757324,
            0.5043601989746094
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9948617919819134,
            0.0,
            0.10124235701791309
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_97_bath_towel_422858",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to dry myself after taking a shower?",
        "answer": "The bath towel hanging on the wall.",
        "object_id": 97,
        "class": "bath towel",
        "position": [
            -2.483631134033203,
            0.11009860038757324,
            5.6932291984558105
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9270703850017737,
            0.0,
            0.3748873180739285
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_105_bath_towel_868524",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the bath towel hanging on the wall?",
        "answer": "A small white cabinet with drawers.",
        "object_id": 105,
        "class": "bath towel",
        "position": [
            -2.5045223236083984,
            0.11009860038757324,
            6.728214263916016
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7134567954727281,
            0.0,
            0.700699222915072
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_165_toilet_331886",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located in the center of the bathroom, below the shelves?",
        "answer": "A toilet.",
        "object_id": 165,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -2.7817745208740234,
            0.11009860038757324,
            4.479625701904297
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7236147344550605,
            0.0,
            0.6902041118970041
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_193_cart_916270",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the primary color of the toy cart that is placed near the pink curtains in the children's room?",
        "answer": "Pink.",
        "object_id": 193,
        "class": "cart",
        "position": [
            0.16200104355812073,
            0.11009860038757324,
            5.017323970794678
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7549285501611781,
            0.0,
            0.6558070479581183
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_202_guitar_141056",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to play some music in this room?",
        "answer": "The guitar next to the desk.",
        "object_id": 202,
        "class": "guitar",
        "position": [
            1.1825252771377563,
            0.11009860038757324,
            4.902621746063232
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8334072045296613,
            0.0,
            0.5526594172164766
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_223_plush_toy_549770",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are the plush toys on the bed in the corner of the room neatly arranged?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 223,
        "class": "plush toy",
        "position": [
            1.7492291927337646,
            0.11009860038757324,
            5.75091552734375
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.91784886228032,
            0.0,
            0.39693005178585583
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_271_drum_387449",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the round object with a beige top and red sides located next to the black sofa and near the glass door?",
        "answer": "A drum.",
        "object_id": 271,
        "class": "drum",
        "position": [
            -0.17626895010471344,
            0.11009860038757324,
            -1.9602006673812866
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6171404794651374,
            0.0,
            0.786852990466161
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_279_wall_clock_779019",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to check the current time?",
        "answer": "The wall clock on the wall.",
        "object_id": 279,
        "class": "wall clock",
        "position": [
            2.8257389068603516,
            0.11009860038757324,
            -0.5005007982254028
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9830219168728633,
            0.0,
            0.18348817658803152
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_292_refrigerator_50760",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the refrigerator in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A countertop with white cabinets underneath.",
        "object_id": 292,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            6.0293288230896,
            0.11009860038757324,
            -1.6358898878097534
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.44455343669622793,
            0.0,
            0.8957523329143904
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_303_washing_machine_645900",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the washing machine located?",
        "answer": "The washing machine is in the kitchen, under the countertop next to the sink and near the door with striped curtains.",
        "object_id": 303,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            4.631935119628906,
            0.11009860038757324,
            -1.5095720291137695
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3262106898415633,
            0.0,
            0.945297088662126
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_307_coffee_machine_853833",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the red and black object on the kitchen counter next to the toaster?",
        "answer": "A coffee machine.",
        "object_id": 307,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            4.797656059265137,
            0.11009860038757324,
            -3.2224526405334473
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6992082642330535,
            0.0,
            0.7149180395179578
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_314_microwave_751828",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the shelf above the kitchen counter and below the range hood?",
        "answer": "A microwave.",
        "object_id": 314,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            5.859165191650391,
            0.11009860038757324,
            -1.4222139120101929
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9982229777051501,
            0.0,
            0.05958931767909771
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_530_stand_312450",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the decorative stand with multiple shelves?",
        "answer": "The decorative stand with multiple shelves is in the hallway, next to the window and the air conditioner unit, near the entrance to the living room.",
        "object_id": 530,
        "class": "stand",
        "position": [
            -7.597403526306152,
            0.11009860038757324,
            2.4285192489624023
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7516937662584547,
            0.0,
            0.6595123060020789
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_620_bathroom_cabinet_617096",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are the drawers of the wooden bathroom cabinet under the sink in the bathroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 620,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            -9.604718208312988,
            0.11009860038757324,
            5.106393814086914
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3536979134668244,
            0.0,
            0.9353597094215759
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_630_bathroom_cabinet_890921",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bathroom cabinet with the wicker baskets?",
        "answer": "The bathroom cabinet with the wicker baskets is located under the window, next to the sink and mirror in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 630,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            -10.351814270019531,
            0.11009860038757324,
            4.980911731719971
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3688358319265872,
            0.0,
            0.9294945557059612
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_622_bin_196905",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the bin that is located next to the wooden cabinet under the sink in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The bin has a woven pattern.",
        "object_id": 622,
        "class": "bin",
        "position": [
            -9.587246894836426,
            0.11009860038757324,
            4.877266883850098
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.18839051560377448,
            0.0,
            0.9820941979415946
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_659_jacket_229438",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the jacket draped over the small wooden chair in the corner of the room neatly folded?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 659,
        "class": "jacket",
        "position": [
            -11.094141960144043,
            0.11009860038757324,
            0.8438244462013245
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9850891047150382,
            0.0,
            0.1720449237022847
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_687_computer_desk_342150",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the computer desk that is placed next to the large wooden wardrobe?",
        "answer": "The computer desk is made of wood and metal.",
        "object_id": 687,
        "class": "computer desk",
        "position": [
            -9.82638168334961,
            0.11009860038757324,
            -0.04796743392944336
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9968404849984321,
            0.0,
            0.07942951257617992
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_715_kitchen_table_403484",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the tablecloth that covers the kitchen table near the plant in a wooden pot?",
        "answer": "The tablecloth has a lace pattern.",
        "object_id": 715,
        "class": "kitchen table",
        "position": [
            -8.081649780273438,
            0.11009860038757324,
            0.26531001925468445
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5620824355653193,
            0.0,
            0.8270812146512329
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_727_range_hood_205092",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the range hood in the kitchen clean?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 727,
        "class": "range hood",
        "position": [
            -10.240279197692871,
            0.11009860038757324,
            -1.9233229160308838
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6742589880964223,
            0.0,
            0.7384949674650388
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_728_oven_567704",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the oven that is built into the wooden cabinets in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 728,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            -13.678818702697754,
            0.11009860038757324,
            -0.011029407382011414
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.32407722796716887,
            0.0,
            0.9460306286337222
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_792_power_breaker_box_117261",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to turn off the electricity in the house for maintenance?",
        "answer": "The power breaker box on the wall.",
        "object_id": 792,
        "class": "power breaker box",
        "position": [
            -13.867467880249023,
            0.11009860038757324,
            1.648673415184021
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8261672864488839,
            0.0,
            0.5634248972149594
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_850_flower_stand_602517",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the flower stand with the black hat?",
        "answer": "The flower stand with the black hat is on top of a small blue dresser next to the window with white curtains.",
        "object_id": 850,
        "class": "flower stand",
        "position": [
            -20.515287399291992,
            0.11009860038757324,
            3.2040634155273438
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3624585594977772,
            0.0,
            0.9319998887590043
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00009-vLpv2VX547B_851_dresser_617601",
        "episode_history": "00009-vLpv2VX547B",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on top of the black dresser near the window in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A vase with flowers and a hat.",
        "object_id": 851,
        "class": "dresser",
        "position": [
            -18.47532081604004,
            0.11009860038757324,
            2.032412052154541
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.701616904337273,
            0.0,
            0.7125543625213321
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_164_coffee_table_905064",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the black object placed on the red rug in front of the sectional sofa in the living room?",
        "answer": "A coffee table.",
        "object_id": 164,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            -3.753359317779541,
            0.08975833654403687,
            -4.35107421875
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9894345638896712,
            0.0,
            0.14498014960833258
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_9_armchair_238901",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the black armchair with the red pillow?",
        "answer": "The black armchair with the red pillow is in the corner of the room, near the two tall windows and adjacent to the entrance with the wooden door.",
        "object_id": 9,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            -0.19811031222343445,
            0.2506200075149536,
            8.169025421142578
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9346001548539111,
            0.0,
            0.35570008510969686
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_65_armchair_836216",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the armchair that is placed near the window with the partially closed blind?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 65,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            -1.6920197010040283,
            0.08975833654403687,
            3.9131453037261963
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5995123410984762,
            0.0,
            0.8003655120447309
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_26_floor_lamp_600746",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is the object to the left of the floor lamp near the window?",
        "answer": "A white sofa with red and white pillows.",
        "object_id": 26,
        "class": "floor lamp",
        "position": [
            -1.1190382242202759,
            0.2455480396747589,
            9.184091567993164
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8485983187776435,
            0.0,
            0.5290377050530111
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_61_footrest_298647",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the small black object in front of the black armchair near the window?",
        "answer": "A footrest.",
        "object_id": 61,
        "class": "footrest",
        "position": [
            0.7886948585510254,
            0.1199546605348587,
            5.60969877243042
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.0890306695370607,
            0.0,
            0.9960288850639738
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_66_led_tv_664553",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the LED TV that is mounted on the wall above the small shelf with a plant and other items?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 66,
        "class": "led tv",
        "position": [
            -1.9915180206298828,
            0.08975833654403687,
            5.176567077636719
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.21794262807774736,
            0.0,
            0.9759615826796486
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_167_led_tv_740376",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to watch my favorite TV shows and movies?",
        "answer": "The LED TV mounted on the wall.",
        "object_id": 167,
        "class": "led tv",
        "position": [
            -3.293100118637085,
            0.08975833654403687,
            -2.7336325645446777
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.27358815745194326,
            0.0,
            0.9618469317422865
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_115_decorative_plant_368267",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the decorative plant in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The decorative plant is on the kitchen island, next to the sink and near the dining area with black chairs.",
        "object_id": 115,
        "class": "decorative plant",
        "position": [
            -0.006419003009796143,
            0.08975833654403687,
            -0.4204939603805542
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.36546964483687877,
            0.0,
            0.9308232585742611
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_78_bed_table_957590",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lamp on the bed table next to the bed in the bedroom turned on?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 78,
        "class": "bed table",
        "position": [
            0.8299570083618164,
            0.08975833654403687,
            4.803403377532959
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9999159794054792,
            0.0,
            0.012962797901681231
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_79_bed_table_751440",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on the bed table next to the bed in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A lamp.",
        "object_id": 79,
        "class": "bed table",
        "position": [
            -2.1369240283966064,
            0.08975833654403687,
            4.385335445404053
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9969304721123928,
            0.0,
            0.07829197771005679
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_475_toilet_paper_91638",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "How many rolls of toilet paper are stacked next to the toilet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "Three rolls.",
        "object_id": 475,
        "class": "toilet paper",
        "position": [
            -8.376843452453613,
            0.08975833654403687,
            -4.727800369262695
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8537636704915288,
            0.0,
            0.5206607292170516
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_474_toilet_254068",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the toilet in the bathroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 474,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -8.072689056396484,
            0.08975833654403687,
            -4.844919681549072
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9338478335736843,
            0.0,
            0.3576705519465316
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_105_bathroom_cabinet_331136",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bathroom cabinet with the sink?",
        "answer": "The bathroom cabinet with the sink is in the bathroom, directly visible through the open door from the adjacent room. It is positioned under a large mirror and above a red bath mat.",
        "object_id": 105,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            -0.10846655815839767,
            0.08975833654403687,
            4.061417579650879
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.1767489261527076,
            0.0,
            0.9842559713325922
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_111_refrigerator_462616",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to store my groceries and keep them fresh?",
        "answer": "The refrigerator in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 111,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -1.7399379014968872,
            0.08975833654403687,
            -2.6802196502685547
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8817639559752218,
            0.0,
            0.4716909220484608
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_113_dishwasher_45176",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the dishwasher next to the sink in the kitchen closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 113,
        "class": "dishwasher",
        "position": [
            -0.010655803605914116,
            0.08975833654403687,
            -0.009359842166304588
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5254067036114914,
            0.0,
            0.8508512183690556
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_245_dishwasher_527624",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the dishwasher that is located next to the sink and under the countertop in the outdoor kitchen area?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 245,
        "class": "dishwasher",
        "position": [
            -0.5888774394989014,
            0.08975833654403687,
            -6.952662944793701
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7642756961459767,
            0.0,
            0.6448896496925524
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_114_microwave_134254",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The microwave is built into the lower cabinets, directly below the countertop and next to the sink in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 114,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -1.847551703453064,
            0.08975833654403687,
            0.15053370594978333
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.47322229127819576,
            0.0,
            0.8809430532318275
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_121_oven_851935",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the oven in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A range hood.",
        "object_id": 121,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            -2.685290813446045,
            0.08975833654403687,
            -0.9707094430923462
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9096586766411126,
            0.0,
            0.4153565841677967
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_122_oven_247036",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the oven in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The oven is built into the lower cabinets, directly beneath the stovetop, with a towel hanging on its handle.",
        "object_id": 122,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            -2.151162624359131,
            0.08975833654403687,
            -0.5262535810470581
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9174284732447295,
            0.0,
            0.39790073696820977
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_187_decorative_bowl_937000",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the decorative bowl with fruits?",
        "answer": "The decorative bowl with fruits is on the dining table in the open-plan kitchen and living area, surrounded by black chairs.",
        "object_id": 187,
        "class": "decorative bowl",
        "position": [
            0.5538456439971924,
            0.08975833654403687,
            -4.062861442565918
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8697474109031722,
            0.0,
            0.4934971542240425
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_212_computer_desk_997974",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the computer desk that is located below the floating shelves and next to the black office chair?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 212,
        "class": "computer desk",
        "position": [
            -3.251312255859375,
            0.08975833654403687,
            1.6958507299423218
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8533644390021587,
            0.0,
            0.5213148129935794
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_214_printer_192386",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the printer located?",
        "answer": "The printer is on top of a white drawer unit, next to the bookshelves and under the black desk in the study room.",
        "object_id": 214,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            -4.454451560974121,
            0.08975833654403687,
            2.2618353366851807
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6389707516570253,
            0.0,
            0.7692310306577966
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_231_speaker_711285",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the speaker on the shelf next to the black leather sectional sofa in the living room upright?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 231,
        "class": "speaker",
        "position": [
            -3.020932197570801,
            0.08975833654403687,
            1.1285392045974731
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7644287352286483,
            0.0,
            0.6447082353721947
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_360_washing_machine_589541",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash my clothes?",
        "answer": "The washing machine in the laundry area.",
        "object_id": 360,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -7.125495433807373,
            0.08975833654403687,
            -0.08547843247652054
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.29527757933431203,
            0.0,
            0.955411508797371
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_362_washing_machine_351841",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the washing machine that is stacked below the dryer in the laundry room near the hallway with blue walls and photo frames?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 362,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -7.141188621520996,
            0.08975833654403687,
            -0.1576891392469406
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2897035691799127,
            0.0,
            0.957116420298189
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw_469_bath_329797",
        "episode_history": "00016-qk9eeNeR4vw",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is hanging on the wall above the bath in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A yellow painting with a zebra.",
        "object_id": 469,
        "class": "bath",
        "position": [
            -9.213427543640137,
            0.08975833654403687,
            -4.9635844230651855
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9970751571240617,
            0.0,
            0.07642729254676603
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_16_electric_heater_29257",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the electric heater located?",
        "answer": "The electric heater is in the living room, positioned between the metal shelf with plants and the TV stand, under the window.",
        "object_id": 16,
        "class": "electric heater",
        "position": [
            1.4350439310073853,
            0.06534527987241745,
            -0.3783116042613983
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7632992371488229,
            0.0,
            0.6460451025803269
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_286_electric_heater_262112",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the electric heater that is placed near the window and behind the bicycle?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 286,
        "class": "electric heater",
        "position": [
            -6.139378547668457,
            0.014520451426506042,
            -0.7740124464035034
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.37071679786337736,
            0.0,
            0.9287459586894168
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_29_tv_320269",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the blinds that are next to the TV on the white stand?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 29,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            2.6953670978546143,
            0.014520451426506042,
            4.226128578186035
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.285034769276347,
            0.0,
            0.9585171778865413
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_30_speaker_370234",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the speaker placed below the TV in the living room properly aligned with the TV stand?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 30,
        "class": "speaker",
        "position": [
            2.741914987564087,
            0.014520451426506042,
            1.9963264465332031
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6489991446383225,
            0.0,
            0.7607891365278067
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_31_tv_stand_209864",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the white TV stand?",
        "answer": "The white TV stand is in the living room, positioned against the wall under the large flat-screen TV, near the windows and adjacent to the gray recliner sofa.",
        "object_id": 31,
        "class": "tv stand",
        "position": [
            3.359417676925659,
            0.014520451426506042,
            -0.5094732642173767
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9839717694766462,
            0.0,
            0.17832430253052556
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_32_rack_762183",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on the second shelf from the top of the rack near the window?",
        "answer": "A potted plant and a decorative item.",
        "object_id": 32,
        "class": "rack",
        "position": [
            3.2211971282958984,
            0.014520451426506042,
            0.8839519619941711
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2848183101337619,
            0.0,
            0.9585815198576217
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_112_table_213513",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the narrow wooden table with metal legs?",
        "answer": "The narrow wooden table with metal legs is placed in the corner of the hallway, next to the door and against the wall.",
        "object_id": 112,
        "class": "table",
        "position": [
            -2.487895965576172,
            0.014520451426506042,
            -0.06498617678880692
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.46222975064063215,
            0.0,
            0.8867602029989274
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_51_kitchen_cabinet_408139",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the kitchen cabinet next to the refrigerator?",
        "answer": "A potted plant.",
        "object_id": 51,
        "class": "kitchen cabinet",
        "position": [
            -2.3281631469726562,
            0.014520451426506042,
            1.9851239919662476
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.987291292460035,
            0.0,
            0.15892106163940067
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_56_dishwasher_784589",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the dishwasher in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The dishwasher is located under the counter, to the right of the sink and below the window with the black blind in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 56,
        "class": "dishwasher",
        "position": [
            -2.611402750015259,
            0.014520451426506042,
            1.6552000045776367
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9660147802463329,
            0.0,
            0.25848683592328153
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_59_sink_725083",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the sink in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A window with a plant on the windowsill.",
        "object_id": 59,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            -0.8200807571411133,
            0.014520451426506042,
            3.3782715797424316
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8808772580193382,
            0.0,
            0.4733447541743039
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_146_sink_665561",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the sink next to the washing machine in the laundry room empty?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 146,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            -5.006743431091309,
            0.014520451426506042,
            2.59480881690979
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9567989217389846,
            0.0,
            0.290750448596587
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_70_microwave_208910",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the kitchen counter next to the kettle and under the window?",
        "answer": "A microwave.",
        "object_id": 70,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -1.6563851833343506,
            0.014520451426506042,
            3.301758289337158
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9241117250826081,
            0.0,
            0.38212238820153693
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_72_washcloth_726488",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the washcloth in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The washcloth is hanging on the oven door, next to the countertop with cleaning supplies and utensils.",
        "object_id": 72,
        "class": "washcloth",
        "position": [
            -2.4145169258117676,
            0.014520451426506042,
            2.518238067626953
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9781202435205021,
            0.0,
            0.2080403547761699
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_73_oven_and_stove_351449",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located to the right of the sink and below the range hood in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "An oven and stove.",
        "object_id": 73,
        "class": "oven and stove",
        "position": [
            -1.493655800819397,
            0.014520451426506042,
            3.088465690612793
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8780024909197476,
            0.0,
            0.47865606226049046
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_76_trashcan_408952",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the black trashcan next to the refrigerator in the kitchen closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 76,
        "class": "trashcan",
        "position": [
            -1.3632620573043823,
            0.014520451426506042,
            3.2304046154022217
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6355744830819573,
            0.0,
            0.7720395562761683
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_87_refrigerator_719331",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the refrigerator that is next to the kitchen counter with a wooden bar stool?",
        "answer": "Silver.",
        "object_id": 87,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -0.8093850016593933,
            0.014520451426506042,
            0.6555004119873047
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8904153356854752,
            0.0,
            0.4551489096725629
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_91_vacuum_cleaner_341546",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the vacuum cleaner in the hallway?",
        "answer": "A white cabinet.",
        "object_id": 91,
        "class": "vacuum cleaner",
        "position": [
            -2.2993814945220947,
            0.014520451426506042,
            1.7100125551223755
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.416930057487602,
            0.0,
            0.9089385717216455
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_144_washer-dryer_272156",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the front-loading washer-dryer in the laundry room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 144,
        "class": "washer-dryer",
        "position": [
            -6.319929599761963,
            0.014520451426506042,
            1.422837257385254
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8711176799227586,
            0.0,
            0.4910743199618467
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_145_washer-dryer_835858",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the washer-dryer unit located?",
        "answer": "The washer-dryer unit is in the laundry room, next to the white washing machine and opposite the shelving unit filled with various household items.",
        "object_id": 145,
        "class": "washer-dryer",
        "position": [
            -5.846650123596191,
            0.014520451426506042,
            1.9241714477539062
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9104398252118491,
            0.0,
            0.41364154127483077
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_171_toilet_850715",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located in the small room between the laundry area and the bathroom with the bathtub?",
        "answer": "A toilet.",
        "object_id": 171,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -5.865678787231445,
            0.014520451426506042,
            1.6654884815216064
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9999951071138256,
            0.0,
            0.0031282191178582876
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_213_sink_cabinet_638647",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I store my bathroom toiletries?",
        "answer": "The sink cabinet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 213,
        "class": "sink cabinet",
        "position": [
            -6.251157760620117,
            0.014520451426506042,
            2.223510503768921
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8770709789453716,
            0.0,
            0.4803607997035223
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_255_mirror_548141",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to check my appearance before going out?",
        "answer": "The mirror next to the white drawers.",
        "object_id": 255,
        "class": "mirror",
        "position": [
            -8.776580810546875,
            0.014520451426506042,
            0.4696902334690094
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.09961648291922394,
            0.0,
            0.9950259073666393
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_225_bed_946561",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the bedspread of the bed that is in the room at the end of the hallway?",
        "answer": "The bedspread has a geometric pattern with various shapes and colors, including blue, beige, and orange.",
        "object_id": 225,
        "class": "bed",
        "position": [
            -8.69001293182373,
            0.014520451426506042,
            0.8955870270729065
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9893095497760753,
            0.0,
            0.14583077426200902
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_244_nightstand_531315",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the drawer of the white nightstand next to the bed in the bedroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 244,
        "class": "nightstand",
        "position": [
            -8.390595436096191,
            0.014520451426506042,
            0.6994209289550781
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.07056066539208138,
            0.0,
            0.99750748994653
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_261_wall_tv_545820",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the wall TV in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A shelf with various items on it.",
        "object_id": 261,
        "class": "wall tv",
        "position": [
            -8.763364791870117,
            0.014520451426506042,
            -0.3386281728744507
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8999267796379394,
            0.0,
            0.43604104312608877
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_288_printer_226757",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the printer on the small black table in the corner of the room turned on?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 288,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            -6.083775520324707,
            0.014520451426506042,
            -0.18049345910549164
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8314697955306962,
            0.0,
            0.5555699587991978
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL_296_desk_346993",
        "episode_history": "00017-oEPjPNSPmzL",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the desk that is positioned next to the window and has a black office chair in front of it?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 296,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            -5.802877426147461,
            0.014520451426506042,
            -0.32566699385643005
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.41930516027848436,
            0.0,
            0.9078453516782661
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_16_bedside_lamp_625947",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the nightstand next to the bed in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A bedside lamp.",
        "object_id": 16,
        "class": "bedside lamp",
        "position": [
            1.873732328414917,
            4.271398544311523,
            3.653179168701172
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9915628536476575,
            0.0,
            0.12962679995322107
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_27_sink_cabinet_166683",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly to the right of the sink cabinet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A round, woven ottoman.",
        "object_id": 27,
        "class": "sink cabinet",
        "position": [
            5.047479152679443,
            4.271398544311523,
            4.801296710968018
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3406281959867189,
            0.0,
            0.9401980813099086
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_60_bed_light_312498",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the bed light on the nightstand next to the bed in the bedroom turned on?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 60,
        "class": "bed light",
        "position": [
            6.399070739746094,
            4.271398544311523,
            2.1883912086486816
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8001486472012608,
            0.0,
            0.599801752566623
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_61_bed_table_546635",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bed table with the lamp on it?",
        "answer": "The bed table is in the bedroom, next to the bed and under the wall-mounted mirror.",
        "object_id": 61,
        "class": "bed table",
        "position": [
            5.362321853637695,
            4.271398544311523,
            2.1965038776397705
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.745482100828804,
            0.0,
            0.6665256464262069
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_64_bin_780480",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located on the floor to the right of the desk near the window?",
        "answer": "A bin.",
        "object_id": 64,
        "class": "bin",
        "position": [
            5.35155725479126,
            4.273660182952881,
            4.957766532897949
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.843723212096468,
            0.0,
            0.5367784844510989
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_508_book_rack_359888",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What material are the baskets in the book rack that is next to the window with blinds made of?",
        "answer": "Wicker.",
        "object_id": 508,
        "class": "book rack",
        "position": [
            1.4354444742202759,
            0.07139864563941956,
            4.26109504699707
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.233738921397007,
            0.0,
            0.9722993965976549
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_77_cardboard_box_742411",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the cardboard box that is placed on the middle shelf of the white bookshelf near the framed picture on the wall?",
        "answer": "The pattern is a blue and white checkered design.",
        "object_id": 77,
        "class": "cardboard box",
        "position": [
            4.607226848602295,
            4.271398544311523,
            4.097246170043945
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9995817372085513,
            0.0,
            0.02891972750896419
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_387_tv_481734",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the TV in the living room turned off?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 387,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            12.774364471435547,
            0.07139864563941956,
            -9.336819648742676
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8082107325134245,
            0.0,
            0.5888933790170457
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_174_computer_967750",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the desk near the window in the office room?",
        "answer": "A computer.",
        "object_id": 174,
        "class": "computer",
        "position": [
            6.931827545166016,
            4.271398544311523,
            -6.933229446411133
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.21961692876414557,
            0.0,
            0.9755861851216447
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_175_screen_288371",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the screen on the desk in the room?",
        "answer": "A stack of papers.",
        "object_id": 175,
        "class": "screen",
        "position": [
            5.249548435211182,
            4.271398544311523,
            -9.005427360534668
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.665172778107548,
            0.0,
            0.7466894771353663
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_386_basket_of_something_609108",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the basket next to the floor lamp and the speaker in the living room filled with items?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 386,
        "class": "basket of something",
        "position": [
            14.743553161621094,
            0.07139864563941956,
            -9.602931022644043
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.023607739097752475,
            0.0,
            0.9997212984900804
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_390_vase_476701",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the vase on the TV stand?",
        "answer": "A decorative sculpture.",
        "object_id": 390,
        "class": "vase",
        "position": [
            13.669005393981934,
            0.07139864563941956,
            -8.395225524902344
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6432461939719476,
            0.0,
            0.7656594111879013
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_395_kitchen_counter_351009",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the kitchen counter in the center of the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Ceiling lights.",
        "object_id": 395,
        "class": "kitchen counter",
        "position": [
            9.299018859863281,
            0.07139864563941956,
            -10.134599685668945
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8813204468821848,
            0.0,
            0.4725190683003029
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_413_oven_759150",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to bake a cake?",
        "answer": "The oven in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 413,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            7.9796271324157715,
            0.07139864563941956,
            -7.696459770202637
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8044246166159635,
            0.0,
            0.5940547417387222
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_414_stovetop_583359",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the stovetop in the kitchen clean?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 414,
        "class": "stovetop",
        "position": [
            6.162871837615967,
            0.07139864563941956,
            -9.577024459838867
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9141423185836858,
            0.0,
            0.4053934155538832
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_415_microwave_13972",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located above the oven in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A microwave.",
        "object_id": 415,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            7.4315571784973145,
            0.07139864563941956,
            -7.9047465324401855
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8430387702623353,
            0.0,
            0.5378527975520525
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_416_dishwasher_966222",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the dishwasher under the kitchen counter closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 416,
        "class": "dishwasher",
        "position": [
            7.148247241973877,
            0.07139864563941956,
            -10.217092514038086
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9028059055564613,
            0.0,
            0.43004824949344694
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_433_laundry_machine_954578",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash my clothes?",
        "answer": "The laundry machine under the countertop.",
        "object_id": 433,
        "class": "laundry machine",
        "position": [
            2.0251245498657227,
            0.07139864563941956,
            -5.892014503479004
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.23091485683288165,
            0.0,
            0.9729739610564354
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_506_wall_clock_336003",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to check the current time?",
        "answer": "The wall clock on the wall.",
        "object_id": 506,
        "class": "wall clock",
        "position": [
            1.1806665658950806,
            0.07139864563941956,
            3.041443347930908
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3681643422582721,
            0.0,
            0.9297607310967343
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_509_basket_82686",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located to the right of the basket near the filing cabinet?",
        "answer": "A black filing cabinet with a printer on top.",
        "object_id": 509,
        "class": "basket",
        "position": [
            -1.5658491849899292,
            0.1746840476989746,
            3.668466567993164
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.045785645863521435,
            0.0,
            0.9989512874173897
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_515_monitor_246004",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to view my computer's display?",
        "answer": "The monitor on the desk.",
        "object_id": 515,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            1.7101666927337646,
            0.07139864563941956,
            4.804040908813477
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.37255899899284306,
            0.0,
            0.9280085087268601
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_516_monitor_646919",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What brand is the monitor that is on the dark wooden desk near the large wall clock?",
        "answer": "ViewSonic.",
        "object_id": 516,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            -1.0739829540252686,
            0.1546245515346527,
            4.690324306488037
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.1962503099171882,
            0.0,
            0.9805538311879708
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_517_laptop_805013",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the laptop on the desk in the study room open?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 517,
        "class": "laptop",
        "position": [
            1.2192329168319702,
            0.07139864563941956,
            2.6016969680786133
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8510691138721279,
            0.0,
            0.525053676696879
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_554_bathtub_139479",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located between the two columns under the large window in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A bathtub.",
        "object_id": 554,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            0.7008795142173767,
            0.07139864563941956,
            6.321136474609375
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9894609458711752,
            0.0,
            0.14479998824489312
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_566_scale_823382",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bathroom scale located?",
        "answer": "The bathroom scale is placed in the corner near the base of the column next to the tiled wall.",
        "object_id": 566,
        "class": "scale",
        "position": [
            1.800880789756775,
            0.11283741146326065,
            8.410058975219727
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9981926913082861,
            0.0,
            0.06009451737653602
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_567_bottle_of_soap_864398",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash my hands or body in the shower?",
        "answer": "The bottle of soap on the shower shelf.",
        "object_id": 567,
        "class": "bottle of soap",
        "position": [
            4.063217639923096,
            0.07139864563941956,
            9.265861511230469
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6144937260289234,
            0.0,
            0.788921707567418
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_619_shoe_336652",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed under the white chair in front of the mirror in the closet?",
        "answer": "A shoe.",
        "object_id": 619,
        "class": "shoe",
        "position": [
            6.2659101486206055,
            0.07139864563941956,
            8.985870361328125
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6508826082161746,
            0.0,
            0.7591783916325002
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_667_tissue_box_766600",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly behind the tissue box on the nightstand?",
        "answer": "A lamp with a patterned lampshade.",
        "object_id": 667,
        "class": "tissue box",
        "position": [
            10.239534378051758,
            0.07139864563941956,
            6.47679328918457
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8762926804397495,
            0.0,
            0.4817791384106614
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_668_box_716913",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the black box on the desk in the room with large windows closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 668,
        "class": "box",
        "position": [
            10.802654266357422,
            0.07139864563941956,
            3.645443916320801
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9562364902745608,
            0.0,
            0.2925948985669268
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_715_grill_876478",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the cover on the grill on the patio properly secured?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 715,
        "class": "grill",
        "position": [
            17.885332107543945,
            -0.026590652763843536,
            -6.503470420837402
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8095858864764914,
            0.0,
            0.5870014415809159
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_716_barbecue_891122",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the barbecue grill located?",
        "answer": "The barbecue grill is on the patio, positioned against the wall near the large windows and close to the outdoor dining table.",
        "object_id": 716,
        "class": "barbecue",
        "position": [
            16.49246597290039,
            -0.12860135734081268,
            2.7827200889587402
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7908637412998869,
            0.0,
            0.6119922733966056
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_729_pot_879035",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to plant some flowers or herbs?",
        "answer": "The pot near the window on the patio.",
        "object_id": 729,
        "class": "pot",
        "position": [
            12.07250690460205,
            -0.12860135734081268,
            -0.2525561451911926
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2544280253367084,
            0.0,
            0.9670917122606641
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx_732_chest_328384",
        "episode_history": "00022-gmuS7Wgsbrx",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the chest on the patio closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 732,
        "class": "chest",
        "position": [
            19.013566970825195,
            0.058559224009513855,
            -7.924236297607422
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6557048234691147,
            0.0,
            0.7550173405156579
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2_37_fan_617184",
        "episode_history": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the floor near the dark brown cabinet with drawers in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "A fan.",
        "object_id": 37,
        "class": "fan",
        "position": [
            0.46314507722854614,
            3.207916259765625,
            -2.3610153198242188
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.27840084612289995,
            0.0,
            0.9604649753520705
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2_310_fan_46730",
        "episode_history": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object standing next to the red plant pot in the corner of the room near the door?",
        "answer": "A fan.",
        "object_id": 310,
        "class": "fan",
        "position": [
            -3.5240941047668457,
            0.007915973663330078,
            -2.683825969696045
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.09226073382750234,
            0.0,
            0.9957348828848023
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2_148_office_chair_501973",
        "episode_history": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the office chair behind the dark wooden desk in the study room pushed under the desk?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 148,
        "class": "office chair",
        "position": [
            3.7774171829223633,
            3.207916259765625,
            0.1751081794500351
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9921394722280017,
            0.0,
            0.1251369955174818
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2_151_board_997983",
        "episode_history": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the whiteboard located?",
        "answer": "The whiteboard is mounted on the wall next to the door in the small room with a large window.",
        "object_id": 151,
        "class": "board",
        "position": [
            4.236168384552002,
            3.207916259765625,
            1.6682332754135132
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.0031382812004326914,
            0.0,
            0.9999950755834286
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2_167_bath_sink_85489",
        "episode_history": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the white object with a faucet on the dark wooden counter in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A bath sink.",
        "object_id": 167,
        "class": "bath sink",
        "position": [
            1.8725900650024414,
            3.207916259765625,
            1.1208763122558594
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9575355957969658,
            0.0,
            0.28831507553672825
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2_204_bathtub_917763",
        "episode_history": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the bathtub that is located in the bathroom with a brown mat on the floor?",
        "answer": "Rectangular.",
        "object_id": 204,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            -2.3104372024536133,
            3.207916259765625,
            -0.306240439414978
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9985939289670994,
            0.0,
            0.0530109897101859
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2_235_scale_831814",
        "episode_history": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to measure my weight?",
        "answer": "The scale on the bathroom floor.",
        "object_id": 235,
        "class": "scale",
        "position": [
            -2.2733278274536133,
            3.207916259765625,
            1.8106582164764404
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.49702737895302906,
            0.0,
            0.8677348584510606
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2_264_bathroom_counter_659594",
        "episode_history": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the bathroom counter that is below the mirror and next to the sink?",
        "answer": "Dark brown.",
        "object_id": 264,
        "class": "bathroom counter",
        "position": [
            -2.401421070098877,
            0.207916259765625,
            0.898801326751709
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9618930834016649,
            0.0,
            0.2734258511992574
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2_293_tv_368930",
        "episode_history": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the TV on the cabinet in the living room turned off?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 293,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -3.4182090759277344,
            0.007915973663330078,
            -3.736997604370117
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9941671416776273,
            0.0,
            0.10785033337239007
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2_369_oven_316071",
        "episode_history": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the oven in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A chair.",
        "object_id": 369,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            3.3791511058807373,
            0.20791609585285187,
            1.4864914417266846
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5221321735249493,
            0.0,
            0.8528645809096027
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2_372_coffee_machine_276014",
        "episode_history": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the coffee machine that is placed on the kitchen counter next to the sink?",
        "answer": "Silver.",
        "object_id": 372,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            2.981311798095703,
            0.20791606605052948,
            1.4782911539077759
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9888013884617611,
            0.0,
            0.149237442272687
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2_373_microwave_511256",
        "episode_history": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the countertop between the sink and the stove in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A microwave.",
        "object_id": 373,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            2.6848812103271484,
            0.207916259765625,
            1.6973381042480469
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.876196092910884,
            0.0,
            0.48195477668314657
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2_374_cooker_951342",
        "episode_history": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the cooker in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The cooker is on the countertop, directly above the stove, between the microwave and a collection of bottles and jars.",
        "object_id": 374,
        "class": "cooker",
        "position": [
            2.4257407188415527,
            0.207916259765625,
            1.833471655845642
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6541913635125767,
            0.0,
            0.7563290685313871
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2_582_cooker_227372",
        "episode_history": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located on the kitchen counter to the right of the sink?",
        "answer": "A cooker.",
        "object_id": 582,
        "class": "cooker",
        "position": [
            -3.0178775787353516,
            -2.792083978652954,
            -3.9043948650360107
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9171638380575255,
            0.0,
            0.39851034385519907
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2_410_food_tray_493555",
        "episode_history": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the food tray with fruits and a red flower?",
        "answer": "The food tray with fruits and a red flower is on the kitchen island, near the sink, in the open-plan kitchen and living area.",
        "object_id": 410,
        "class": "food tray",
        "position": [
            5.054610252380371,
            0.207916259765625,
            1.9982599020004272
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.35844996631275067,
            0.0,
            0.9335489390762478
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2_415_range_hood_521471",
        "episode_history": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the range hood in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A kitchen island with various items on it.",
        "object_id": 415,
        "class": "range hood",
        "position": [
            2.3219735622406006,
            0.007915973663330078,
            -0.7933751344680786
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9578792817511044,
            0.0,
            0.2871711712411058
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2_692_bath_tub_69343",
        "episode_history": "00025-ixTj1aTMup2",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the bathtub that is next to the toilet and a metal bucket in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 692,
        "class": "bath tub",
        "position": [
            -2.004702568054199,
            -2.792083978652954,
            0.10252797603607178
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9657285361560152,
            0.0,
            0.25955422257008365
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7_227_tv_502658",
        "episode_history": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the TV located?",
        "answer": "The TV is on top of a wooden cabinet, near the sliding glass door and adjacent to the dining area.",
        "object_id": 227,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            3.3554372787475586,
            0.17635944485664368,
            -1.1679022312164307
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8228263942945448,
            0.0,
            0.5682928161188018
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7_164_tray_260824",
        "episode_history": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the white tray?",
        "answer": "The white tray is on the kitchen counter, near the edge closest to the living room area with the blue armchair and large windows.",
        "object_id": 164,
        "class": "tray",
        "position": [
            4.878712177276611,
            0.17635944485664368,
            4.514699935913086
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.015343322836896607,
            0.0,
            0.9998822842936677
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7_84_towel_552463",
        "episode_history": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the towel on the rack in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A window.",
        "object_id": 84,
        "class": "towel",
        "position": [
            0.8721154928207397,
            0.17635944485664368,
            3.8018431663513184
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9990511416407559,
            0.0,
            0.04355245557126325
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7_91_towel_456804",
        "episode_history": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the towel hanging on the ring in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A trash can.",
        "object_id": 91,
        "class": "towel",
        "position": [
            0.7185499668121338,
            0.17635944485664368,
            4.708499431610107
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6156219844678923,
            0.0,
            0.7880416056527816
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7_87_toilet_774180",
        "episode_history": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the toilet located?",
        "answer": "The toilet is in the bathroom, which is accessible through the hallway. It is positioned under the window, next to a small white table and a towel rack.",
        "object_id": 87,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            0.2775573432445526,
            0.17635944485664368,
            3.0351948738098145
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.959317291718487,
            0.0,
            0.2823301857929961
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7_93_bath_cabinet_905913",
        "episode_history": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located above the sink and below the mirror in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A bath cabinet.",
        "object_id": 93,
        "class": "bath cabinet",
        "position": [
            -0.2594873309135437,
            0.17635944485664368,
            5.351116180419922
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.46750446295819165,
            0.0,
            0.8839907109886239
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7_95_bath_sink_187552",
        "episode_history": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located below the mirror and next to the towel holder in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A bath sink.",
        "object_id": 95,
        "class": "bath sink",
        "position": [
            -0.027180062606930733,
            0.17635944485664368,
            5.134820461273193
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5186636272876299,
            0.0,
            0.8549783867027508
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7_138_refrigerator_664034",
        "episode_history": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on top of the refrigerator in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Several folded items, possibly linens or towels.",
        "object_id": 138,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            5.780247688293457,
            0.17635944485664368,
            2.3958966732025146
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9964918594515214,
            0.0,
            0.0836897487560596
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7_145_microwave_739503",
        "episode_history": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the microwave that is installed above the oven and near the blue backsplash in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 145,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            5.379545211791992,
            0.17635944485664368,
            4.572551727294922
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6586867463672158,
            0.0,
            0.7524172845968992
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7_146_oven_680315",
        "episode_history": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object installed above the counter and below the cabinets in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "An oven.",
        "object_id": 146,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            5.373995780944824,
            0.17635944485664368,
            4.649609565734863
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6459622205263565,
            0.0,
            0.7633693795618598
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7_153_ventilation_hood_615659",
        "episode_history": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to remove smoke and odors while cooking?",
        "answer": "The ventilation hood above the stove.",
        "object_id": 153,
        "class": "ventilation hood",
        "position": [
            3.754744052886963,
            0.17635944485664368,
            4.50924825668335
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8595655018768312,
            0.0,
            0.5110255844703192
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7_155_coffee_machine_589882",
        "episode_history": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the coffee machine in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The coffee machine is on the kitchen counter, next to the stove and under the window with the \"Bon Appetit\" sign.",
        "object_id": 155,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            3.3520121574401855,
            0.17635944485664368,
            4.351161956787109
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9562848528315863,
            0.0,
            0.29243679700898145
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7_156_stovetop_507964",
        "episode_history": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the stovetop on the kitchen counter?",
        "answer": "A kettle and a knife block with various knives and utensils.",
        "object_id": 156,
        "class": "stovetop",
        "position": [
            3.915390968322754,
            0.17635944485664368,
            4.656161785125732
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8079329870216532,
            0.0,
            0.5892743745338577
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7_163_kitchen_top_386105",
        "episode_history": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the kitchen top with the bar stools?",
        "answer": "The kitchen top with the bar stools is located in the open-plan area, adjacent to the living room and near the dining table. It is positioned next to the refrigerator and the white cabinets.",
        "object_id": 163,
        "class": "kitchen top",
        "position": [
            6.643129348754883,
            0.17635944485664368,
            1.343846321105957
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9136322156399483,
            0.0,
            0.40654172546595824
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7_159_dishwasher_147786",
        "episode_history": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the large stainless steel appliance located to the left of the kitchen island?",
        "answer": "A dishwasher.",
        "object_id": 159,
        "class": "dishwasher",
        "position": [
            4.617606163024902,
            0.17635944485664368,
            0.38057470321655273
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9922271452670142,
            0.0,
            0.12443991399575877
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7_160_cabinet_kitchen_496100",
        "episode_history": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located to the right of the cabinet in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A microwave oven.",
        "object_id": 160,
        "class": "cabinet kitchen",
        "position": [
            5.2955451011657715,
            0.17635944485664368,
            0.8664911389350891
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9847002850533351,
            0.0,
            0.174256559749926
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7_195_basket_781566",
        "episode_history": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is next to the basket near the large window?",
        "answer": "A blue armchair with a pillow.",
        "object_id": 195,
        "class": "basket",
        "position": [
            6.023246765136719,
            0.17635944485664368,
            2.1754207611083984
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.25724981718815443,
            0.0,
            0.9663449340461516
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7_214_couch_966445",
        "episode_history": "00031-Wo6kuutE9i7",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the white pillow on the gray couch in the living room positioned upright?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 214,
        "class": "couch",
        "position": [
            3.55788516998291,
            0.17635944485664368,
            -1.1405221223831177
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9894009116580744,
            0.0,
            0.14520962781499774
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4_6_ladder_334511",
        "episode_history": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the ladder next to the stairs?",
        "answer": "A wooden coat rack with hooks.",
        "object_id": 6,
        "class": "ladder",
        "position": [
            -3.333451986312866,
            -1.4899135828018188,
            -0.9899106621742249
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9635896056304302,
            0.0,
            0.26738562399835825
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4_18_grill_306780",
        "episode_history": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located between the two large machines in the garage?",
        "answer": "A grill.",
        "object_id": 18,
        "class": "grill",
        "position": [
            -5.656844139099121,
            -1.4899135828018188,
            -2.8577992916107178
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6402400236185287,
            0.0,
            0.7681749228899274
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4_19_bicycle_690097",
        "episode_history": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the primary color of the bicycle that is parked near the garage door and next to a black grill?",
        "answer": "Red.",
        "object_id": 19,
        "class": "bicycle",
        "position": [
            -6.530249118804932,
            -1.4899135828018188,
            -4.407702445983887
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7289626581268189,
            0.0,
            0.6845534625262534
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4_74_microwave_561433",
        "episode_history": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the microwave that is installed above the stove and next to the wooden cabinets?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 74,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -8.515703201293945,
            0.11008644104003906,
            3.8304905891418457
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.1310076172540499,
            0.0,
            0.9913813616471798
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4_80_dishwasher_229683",
        "episode_history": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the dishwasher under the counter in the kitchen closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 80,
        "class": "dishwasher",
        "position": [
            -6.257101535797119,
            0.11008644104003906,
            4.978918075561523
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5288509822048754,
            0.0,
            0.8487146980116101
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4_91_oven_and_stove_97561",
        "episode_history": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located below the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "An oven and stove.",
        "object_id": 91,
        "class": "oven and stove",
        "position": [
            -8.305364608764648,
            0.11008644104003906,
            4.117774486541748
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.10104937016073008,
            0.0,
            0.994881412425682
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4_136_pouffe_755420",
        "episode_history": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the pouffe that is placed between the two armchairs near the windows?",
        "answer": "The pouffe has a diamond pattern on its fabric.",
        "object_id": 136,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            -4.4920654296875,
            0.11008644104003906,
            4.087003707885742
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.927905847038962,
            0.0,
            0.3728146175123853
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4_156_fireplace_96971",
        "episode_history": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located below the \"gather\" sign and between the TV and the couch in the living room?",
        "answer": "A fireplace.",
        "object_id": 156,
        "class": "fireplace",
        "position": [
            1.4883272647857666,
            0.11008644104003906,
            3.5147008895874023
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9931078358305575,
            0.0,
            0.11720420816654183
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4_277_cabinet_667067",
        "episode_history": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly opposite the cabinet in the hallway?",
        "answer": "The entrance to the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 277,
        "class": "cabinet",
        "position": [
            6.5016937255859375,
            0.11008644104003906,
            5.129080772399902
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9392712442443297,
            0.0,
            0.34317565434585906
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4_302_toilet_69638",
        "episode_history": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the toilet that is next to the sink and below the towel rack?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 302,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            4.474423885345459,
            0.11008644104003906,
            2.4529476165771484
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9518555074536182,
            0.0,
            0.30654704847741604
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4_296_sink_cabinet_968155",
        "episode_history": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I store my bathroom toiletries?",
        "answer": "The sink cabinet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 296,
        "class": "sink cabinet",
        "position": [
            5.51739501953125,
            0.11008644104003906,
            2.2954812049865723
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8301284928648436,
            0.0,
            0.5575721346462207
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4_336_washing_machine_6761",
        "episode_history": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the washing machine in the laundry room open?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 336,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -6.019598960876465,
            -2.4899134635925293,
            3.254058837890625
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4781985384552761,
            0.0,
            0.8782517622067364
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4_351_clothes_bag_353870",
        "episode_history": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to collect and carry my dirty laundry?",
        "answer": "The clothes bag next to the washing machine.",
        "object_id": 351,
        "class": "clothes bag",
        "position": [
            -5.7007951736450195,
            -2.4899134635925293,
            3.571314573287964
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6667335861691019,
            0.0,
            0.7452961324695633
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4_449_fridge_252445",
        "episode_history": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the white chest fridge in the basement closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 449,
        "class": "fridge",
        "position": [
            1.7658592462539673,
            -2.4899134635925293,
            3.5525598526000977
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9982512752721612,
            0.0,
            0.05911337765266809
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4_452_chest_992744",
        "episode_history": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the chest that is placed near the wooden rocking chair and the decorative firewood holder?",
        "answer": "The chest is brown.",
        "object_id": 452,
        "class": "chest",
        "position": [
            -4.1858673095703125,
            -2.4899134635925293,
            4.13699197769165
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6585658103991477,
            0.0,
            0.7525231380983004
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4_462_cloth_86852",
        "episode_history": "00034-6imZUJGRUq4",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the cloth on top of the wire crate in the room folded?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 462,
        "class": "cloth",
        "position": [
            3.192317008972168,
            -2.4899134635925293,
            0.22026382386684418
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.15982995623702284,
            0.0,
            0.9871445613937562
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr_43_amplifier_638636",
        "episode_history": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to enhance the sound quality of my TV?",
        "answer": "The amplifier next to the TV.",
        "object_id": 43,
        "class": "amplifier",
        "position": [
            1.2780094146728516,
            -2.961580991744995,
            -2.5164361000061035
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6116514935916493,
            0.0,
            0.7911273288081411
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr_53_bottles_542167",
        "episode_history": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What colors are the bottles that are placed on top of the cabinet with wicker baskets in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The bottles are blue and clear.",
        "object_id": 53,
        "class": "bottles",
        "position": [
            0.23657548427581787,
            -2.961580991744995,
            -0.4853803515434265
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9392645593503515,
            0.0,
            0.34319395033769146
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr_109_bottles_262829",
        "episode_history": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are the wine bottles on the table in the dining area placed in a wine rack?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 109,
        "class": "bottles",
        "position": [
            6.39851713180542,
            -2.961580991744995,
            -1.2162153720855713
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3318616691423468,
            0.0,
            0.9433280619986112
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr_78_kitchen_counter_730808",
        "episode_history": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the kitchen counter that is located between the refrigerator and the stove?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 78,
        "class": "kitchen counter",
        "position": [
            6.608658313751221,
            -2.961580991744995,
            -0.592866063117981
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9719781784661511,
            0.0,
            0.23507109687416514
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr_80_sink_201217",
        "episode_history": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the kitchen sink?",
        "answer": "The kitchen sink is located in the middle of the countertop, between the dishwasher and the spice rack, under the cabinets.",
        "object_id": 80,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            3.9325664043426514,
            -2.961580991744995,
            -0.6469359993934631
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9949772071694326,
            0.0,
            0.10010173431722022
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr_87_oven_and_stove_153463",
        "episode_history": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located between the cabinets and below the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "An oven and stove.",
        "object_id": 87,
        "class": "oven and stove",
        "position": [
            6.7380571365356445,
            -2.961580991744995,
            -1.661197543144226
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9577932513780835,
            0.0,
            0.2874579753887514
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr_142_bed_cabinet_940715",
        "episode_history": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the bed cabinet that is next to the bed with floral-patterned bedding and purple pillows?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 142,
        "class": "bed cabinet",
        "position": [
            1.9097667932510376,
            0.03841900825500488,
            -3.2658164501190186
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6820570143175015,
            0.0,
            0.7312990012438794
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr_171_toilet_905001",
        "episode_history": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located next to the shower curtain and above the red bath mat in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A toilet.",
        "object_id": 171,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            2.8177411556243896,
            0.03841900825500488,
            0.5975226759910583
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5074528552961892,
            0.0,
            0.8616795225904726
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr_203_office_chair_417277",
        "episode_history": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly behind the office chair in the study room?",
        "answer": "A wooden desk with a computer monitor on top.",
        "object_id": 203,
        "class": "office chair",
        "position": [
            6.153564453125,
            0.03841900825500488,
            -1.0134928226470947
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.13321560617637898,
            0.0,
            0.991087081073636
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr_204_monitor_194598",
        "episode_history": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to view my computer's display?",
        "answer": "The monitor on the wooden desk.",
        "object_id": 204,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            6.083488464355469,
            0.03841900825500488,
            -3.226226806640625
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6933197268896838,
            0.0,
            0.7206301106015583
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr_205_desk_667886",
        "episode_history": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wooden desk with the computer on it?",
        "answer": "The wooden desk with the computer on it is in the room with large windows, positioned against the wall between the exercise bike and the white office chair.",
        "object_id": 205,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            5.434138774871826,
            0.03841900825500488,
            -1.1200077533721924
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.36277089530042655,
            0.0,
            0.9318783598318651
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr_210_cross-trainer_93760",
        "episode_history": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the exercise equipment located in the room at the end of the hallway?",
        "answer": "A cross-trainer.",
        "object_id": 210,
        "class": "cross-trainer",
        "position": [
            4.225246429443359,
            0.03841900825500488,
            -1.0364375114440918
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.68570366775973,
            0.0,
            0.7278808144338287
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr_219_printer_845665",
        "episode_history": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the printer located?",
        "answer": "The printer is on the floor next to the window, near the exercise weights and the white bookshelf in the corner of the room.",
        "object_id": 219,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            6.243632793426514,
            0.03841900825500488,
            -1.7643604278564453
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.18951096511838186,
            0.0,
            0.9818786045636698
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr_251_bedside_cabinet_875201",
        "episode_history": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bedside cabinet with the alarm clock on it?",
        "answer": "The bedside cabinet is in the bedroom, positioned next to the bed and near the door.",
        "object_id": 251,
        "class": "bedside cabinet",
        "position": [
            2.0689306259155273,
            2.838418960571289,
            -1.9860692024230957
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9972589063080285,
            0.0,
            0.07399103857437879
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr_253_armchair_991222",
        "episode_history": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the armchair next to the window in the bedroom occupied by a cushion?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 253,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            -0.7370508313179016,
            2.838418960571289,
            -0.6240566968917847
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.353858731213284,
            0.0,
            0.9352988818255503
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr_380_dishwasher_654501",
        "episode_history": "00035-3XYAD64HpDr",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash the dirty dishes quickly?",
        "answer": "The dishwasher under the kitchen counter.",
        "object_id": 380,
        "class": "dishwasher",
        "position": [
            1.4167267084121704,
            -2.961580991744995,
            -1.9076578617095947
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9589389273230685,
            0.0,
            0.28361264722237256
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_43_coffee_maker_504407",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the coffee maker in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "A small stove.",
        "object_id": 43,
        "class": "coffee maker",
        "position": [
            5.327497482299805,
            2.8991520404815674,
            6.233170509338379
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.1302598683066608,
            0.0,
            0.9914798871932459
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_138_workout_bike_230986",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to get some exercise indoors?",
        "answer": "The workout bike in the room.",
        "object_id": 138,
        "class": "workout bike",
        "position": [
            2.546818971633911,
            2.8587534427642822,
            4.895843505859375
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9944194278286141,
            0.0,
            0.1054988225385059
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_1083_tv_475765",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the wooden entertainment unit in the living room?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 1083,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -3.6877150535583496,
            0.05875343084335327,
            -4.298603057861328
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5774353435562151,
            0.0,
            0.8164364176175116
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_1031_dining_table_283214",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is hanging above the dining table in the dining room?",
        "answer": "A light fixture and a decorative curtain.",
        "object_id": 1031,
        "class": "dining table",
        "position": [
            -3.0656521320343018,
            0.05875343084335327,
            -2.227834701538086
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.05208520864670667,
            0.0,
            0.9986426443128839
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_210_chair__w_clutter_15505",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the chair that is next to the table with various items on it, near the open door to the balcony?",
        "answer": "Wood.",
        "object_id": 210,
        "class": "chair /w clutter",
        "position": [
            3.611721992492676,
            2.8587534427642822,
            2.671342372894287
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3964514831236523,
            0.0,
            0.9180556745258189
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_260_shelf_251065",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on top of the wooden shelf next to the doorway?",
        "answer": "Several stacks of books and other items.",
        "object_id": 260,
        "class": "shelf",
        "position": [
            1.5739725828170776,
            2.897611379623413,
            1.9359551668167114
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8552871534085367,
            0.0,
            0.518154306374387
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_43_coffee_maker_143523",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to make a cup of coffee?",
        "answer": "The coffee maker in the corner of the room.",
        "object_id": 43,
        "class": "coffee maker",
        "position": [
            5.327497482299805,
            2.8991520404815674,
            6.233170509338379
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.1302598683066608,
            0.0,
            0.9914798871932459
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_138_workout_bike_405172",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to get some indoor exercise?",
        "answer": "The workout bike in the corner of the room.",
        "object_id": 138,
        "class": "workout bike",
        "position": [
            2.546818971633911,
            2.8587534427642822,
            4.895843505859375
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9944194278286141,
            0.0,
            0.1054988225385059
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_1083_tv_525561",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the TV located?",
        "answer": "The TV is in the living room, placed on a wooden entertainment unit against the wall, near the window with curtains.",
        "object_id": 1083,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -3.6877150535583496,
            0.05875343084335327,
            -4.298603057861328
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5774353435562151,
            0.0,
            0.8164364176175116
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_1031_dining_table_416930",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the wooden object in the center of the dining room, surrounded by four chairs?",
        "answer": "A dining table.",
        "object_id": 1031,
        "class": "dining table",
        "position": [
            -3.0656521320343018,
            0.05875343084335327,
            -2.227834701538086
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.05208520864670667,
            0.0,
            0.9986426443128839
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_260_shelf_212882",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on top of the wooden shelf next to the doorway?",
        "answer": "Several stacks of books and some other items.",
        "object_id": 260,
        "class": "shelf",
        "position": [
            1.5739725828170776,
            2.897611379623413,
            1.9359551668167114
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8552871534085367,
            0.0,
            0.518154306374387
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_326_flowerpot_874485",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the flowerpot that is hanging near the handrail in the corner?",
        "answer": "The flowerpot has a hexagonal shape.",
        "object_id": 326,
        "class": "flowerpot",
        "position": [
            0.5758798718452454,
            2.6587533950805664,
            2.1756772994995117
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.09288900229933011,
            0.0,
            0.9956764701708256
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_359_bulletin_board_732524",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the bulletin board on the wall near the staircase?",
        "answer": "An electrical outlet.",
        "object_id": 359,
        "class": "bulletin board",
        "position": [
            -0.2191704362630844,
            2.6587533950805664,
            -1.8766753673553467
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9790225898618711,
            0.0,
            0.20375173260651022
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_490_beanbag_chair_902431",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the turquoise beanbag chair?",
        "answer": "The turquoise beanbag chair is in the bedroom, placed on the wooden floor between the wardrobe and the bed.",
        "object_id": 490,
        "class": "beanbag chair",
        "position": [
            -5.959641456604004,
            2.6587533950805664,
            -1.8348493576049805
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9640877617271342,
            0.0,
            0.2655838618741081
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_523_beanbag_chair_805466",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "Is there enough space between the beanbag chair and the bed for me to place a small side table?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 523,
        "class": "beanbag chair",
        "position": [
            -5.275215148925781,
            2.6877546310424805,
            -3.8730297088623047
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.816171995897,
            0.0,
            0.5778090282381433
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_491_exercise_ball_581550",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the exercise ball next to the bed in the corner of the room inflated?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 491,
        "class": "exercise ball",
        "position": [
            -6.465974807739258,
            2.6587533950805664,
            -1.1478599309921265
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9335402151883233,
            0.0,
            0.358472686025224
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_500_office_chair_912321",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the office chair with wheels?",
        "answer": "The office chair with wheels is in the bedroom, positioned in front of the desk and next to the bed with a green blanket.",
        "object_id": 500,
        "class": "office chair",
        "position": [
            -4.986283302307129,
            2.6587533950805664,
            -1.3112083673477173
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5562038135833429,
            0.0,
            0.8310459179584158
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_529_office_chair_134277",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the office chair located?",
        "answer": "The office chair is in the bedroom, positioned in front of the desk and shelves, next to the bed and near the window.",
        "object_id": 529,
        "class": "office chair",
        "position": [
            -5.736273288726807,
            2.6587533950805664,
            -2.5171725749969482
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.21107224684771334,
            0.0,
            0.9774704632932179
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_565_monitor_435079",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the monitor on the desk in the small room turned off?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 565,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            -2.9628734588623047,
            2.7447876930236816,
            -3.269749164581299
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3552034458067175,
            0.0,
            0.9347890200933227
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_570_monitor_182119",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located directly below the monitor on the desk?",
        "answer": "A keyboard.",
        "object_id": 570,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            -2.284478187561035,
            2.8587534427642822,
            -4.865943908691406
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5616991284207602,
            0.0,
            0.8273415794769161
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_567_computer_desk_130885",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located to the right of the computer desk near the window?",
        "answer": "A smaller monitor and a computer tower.",
        "object_id": 567,
        "class": "computer desk",
        "position": [
            -2.395009994506836,
            2.6847009658813477,
            -3.9180431365966797
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5444051287968604,
            0.0,
            0.8388224220534843
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_569_computer_tower_337863",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the computer tower on the floor next to the desk in the corner of the room plugged in?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 569,
        "class": "computer tower",
        "position": [
            -2.743319034576416,
            2.8587534427642822,
            -4.849401473999023
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4891917823805257,
            0.0,
            0.8721762436866556
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_819_vacuum_cleaner_367024",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the vacuum cleaner next to the blue laundry basket in the laundry room standing upright?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 819,
        "class": "vacuum cleaner",
        "position": [
            3.5962576866149902,
            -0.14124658703804016,
            -1.7059649229049683
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5584811629019841,
            0.0,
            0.8295172033681082
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_920_radiator_881971",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the radiator that is mounted on the wall near the kitchen entrance?",
        "answer": "Beige.",
        "object_id": 920,
        "class": "radiator",
        "position": [
            1.299762487411499,
            -0.14124658703804016,
            -3.5321192741394043
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.823834058044906,
            0.0,
            0.5668310549054828
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_980_coffee_machine_788750",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the kitchen counter next to the wall and under the cabinets?",
        "answer": "A coffee machine.",
        "object_id": 980,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            -1.7063677310943604,
            0.05875343084335327,
            -1.5048696994781494
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9912789708451513,
            0.0,
            0.1317801273340465
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_1055_coffee_table_77679",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the coffee table with the glass top?",
        "answer": "The coffee table with the glass top is in the living room, positioned in front of the large L-shaped sofa and near the two windows with curtains.",
        "object_id": 1055,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            -5.8990325927734375,
            0.05875343084335327,
            -4.593179225921631
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9993768975478073,
            0.0,
            0.03529612794205639
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ_1084_tv_stand_460469",
        "episode_history": "00043-Jfyvj3xn2aJ",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What material is the TV stand that is below the large flat-screen TV and surrounded by wooden cabinets made of?",
        "answer": "Wood.",
        "object_id": 1084,
        "class": "tv stand",
        "position": [
            -6.133450508117676,
            0.05875343084335327,
            -2.4923601150512695
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.021185923371451455,
            0.0,
            0.9997755531372524
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00055-HxmXPBbFCkH_108_armchair_404083",
        "episode_history": "00055-HxmXPBbFCkH",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the armchair near the windows?",
        "answer": "A light fixture hanging from the ceiling.",
        "object_id": 108,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            -14.22539234161377,
            0.03644251823425293,
            3.3663136959075928
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.27435383390944995,
            0.0,
            0.9616288129102549
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00055-HxmXPBbFCkH_119_tv_839969",
        "episode_history": "00055-HxmXPBbFCkH",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the desk against the striped wall in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 119,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -14.528263092041016,
            0.03644251823425293,
            1.3808058500289917
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9988061479349881,
            0.0,
            0.048849553194081435
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00055-HxmXPBbFCkH_257_tv_185180",
        "episode_history": "00055-HxmXPBbFCkH",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object mounted on the wall above the long cabinet in the living room?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 257,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -3.516533613204956,
            -2.7635574340820312,
            2.266591787338257
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9203236310525054,
            0.0,
            0.3911577867387175
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00055-HxmXPBbFCkH_170_step_stool_322092",
        "episode_history": "00055-HxmXPBbFCkH",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the white step stool in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The white step stool is in the bathroom, placed next to the sink and under the towel radiator, near the shower enclosure.",
        "object_id": 170,
        "class": "step stool",
        "position": [
            -9.445052146911621,
            0.03644251823425293,
            2.686993360519409
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8512829374560645,
            0.0,
            0.5247069281000337
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00055-HxmXPBbFCkH_185_shower_soap_shelf_431184",
        "episode_history": "00055-HxmXPBbFCkH",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object attached to the wall inside the shower that holds various bottles?",
        "answer": "A shower soap shelf.",
        "object_id": 185,
        "class": "shower soap shelf",
        "position": [
            -10.056519508361816,
            0.03644251823425293,
            2.2673439979553223
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5393617833704439,
            0.0,
            0.8420741455711928
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00055-HxmXPBbFCkH_319_kitchen_table_236815",
        "episode_history": "00055-HxmXPBbFCkH",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on the kitchen table near the sliding glass door?",
        "answer": "A vase with flowers.",
        "object_id": 319,
        "class": "kitchen table",
        "position": [
            -9.153785705566406,
            -2.7635574340820312,
            0.03059639409184456
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9506488238863549,
            0.0,
            0.310268937606538
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00055-HxmXPBbFCkH_322_stove_205633",
        "episode_history": "00055-HxmXPBbFCkH",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the backsplash behind the stove that is located in the corner of the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Light blue.",
        "object_id": 322,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            -7.060338020324707,
            -2.7635574340820312,
            3.065150499343872
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.914617515409321,
            0.0,
            0.4043201707885477
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A_29_shelf_132355",
        "episode_history": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the stuffed elephant that is placed on the shelf below the wall-mounted TV?",
        "answer": "Gray.",
        "object_id": 29,
        "class": "shelf",
        "position": [
            2.64766788482666,
            -2.799063205718994,
            -3.160170316696167
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.25764502776282744,
            0.0,
            0.9662396388417792
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A_46_fridge_27096",
        "episode_history": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the large white and black object located at the end of the dining table in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A fridge.",
        "object_id": 46,
        "class": "fridge",
        "position": [
            2.398970365524292,
            -2.799063205718994,
            -2.1760005950927734
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9919152911178558,
            0.0,
            0.1269017543085231
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A_51_calendar_331403",
        "episode_history": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the primary color of the calendar that is hanging on the wall next to the white door in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 51,
        "class": "calendar",
        "position": [
            1.2359833717346191,
            -2.799063205718994,
            2.38789701461792
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7372225629077628,
            0.0,
            0.675649977976548
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A_70_worktop_777976",
        "episode_history": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the worktop with the stove located?",
        "answer": "The worktop with the stove is in the kitchen, between the wooden cabinets and next to the door leading to another room.",
        "object_id": 70,
        "class": "worktop",
        "position": [
            1.6316413879394531,
            -2.799063205718994,
            0.9592511653900146
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7238314624593134,
            0.0,
            0.689976821316493
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A_73_microwave_760113",
        "episode_history": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the microwave on the kitchen counter next to the stove closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 73,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            0.5279366970062256,
            -2.799063205718994,
            0.8297028541564941
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9889566850175298,
            0.0,
            0.14820484188830382
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A_134_washing_machine_135283",
        "episode_history": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash my clothes?",
        "answer": "The washing machine under the staircase.",
        "object_id": 134,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            7.676840305328369,
            -2.799063205718994,
            -2.9233405590057373
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.43122131196090097,
            0.0,
            0.9022461859773746
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A_219_bedside_cabinet_512503",
        "episode_history": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lamp on the bedside cabinet next to the bed in the bedroom turned on?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 219,
        "class": "bedside cabinet",
        "position": [
            0.5388361811637878,
            0.20093679428100586,
            0.46573424339294434
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9739578071808835,
            0.0,
            0.22672933165209225
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A_441_bedside_cabinet_723102",
        "episode_history": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the bedside cabinet that is next to the bed with a patterned quilt and a lamp on top?",
        "answer": "Dark brown.",
        "object_id": 441,
        "class": "bedside cabinet",
        "position": [
            7.464003086090088,
            0.20093679428100586,
            2.146352767944336
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.04591793537641209,
            0.0,
            0.9989452153200232
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A_220_bedside_lamp_44063",
        "episode_history": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to read a book at night without disturbing others?",
        "answer": "The bedside lamp on the nightstand.",
        "object_id": 220,
        "class": "bedside lamp",
        "position": [
            2.4678359031677246,
            0.20093679428100586,
            1.8369166851043701
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.978990423266248,
            0.0,
            0.20390623127548554
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A_442_bedside_lamp_7750",
        "episode_history": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to read a book at night without disturbing others?",
        "answer": "The bedside lamp on the nightstand.",
        "object_id": 442,
        "class": "bedside lamp",
        "position": [
            6.576236248016357,
            0.0009367465972900391,
            0.42854130268096924
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.36398400234388606,
            0.0,
            0.9314051997051155
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A_269_bag_192835",
        "episode_history": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the colorful bag with patterns?",
        "answer": "The colorful bag with patterns is hanging on the wall in the hallway, between the bedroom and the bathroom doors.",
        "object_id": 269,
        "class": "bag",
        "position": [
            4.4006500244140625,
            0.11301443725824356,
            -1.1476085186004639
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9545244802691946,
            0.0,
            0.2981325486538233
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A_282_vase_360622",
        "episode_history": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the large decorative vase with a dark pattern?",
        "answer": "The large decorative vase with a dark pattern is placed on the floor next to the two chairs with floral cushions, near the door in the corner of the room.",
        "object_id": 282,
        "class": "vase",
        "position": [
            5.092081069946289,
            0.20093679428100586,
            -2.7380788326263428
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5003328577067194,
            0.0,
            0.8658331429894721
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A_333_bathtub_960258",
        "episode_history": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly in front of the bathtub in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A toilet.",
        "object_id": 333,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            2.953158378601074,
            0.20093679428100586,
            3.0343215465545654
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6546434189874817,
            0.0,
            0.7559378241471851
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A_404_doll_218850",
        "episode_history": "00057-1UnKg1rAb8A",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the doll standing next to the window in the children's room wearing a purple dress?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 404,
        "class": "doll",
        "position": [
            7.944490432739258,
            0.20093679428100586,
            -2.3206663131713867
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.45301527153765014,
            0.0,
            0.8915027558867494
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz_24_plant_522640",
        "episode_history": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What colors are the flowers in the vase on the nightstand next to the bed with white pillows?",
        "answer": "The flowers are a mix of red, yellow, and pink.",
        "object_id": 24,
        "class": "plant",
        "position": [
            11.418937683105469,
            2.8892838954925537,
            1.9078959226608276
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9998792683873614,
            0.0,
            0.015538617994089877
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz_21_cabinet_139588",
        "episode_history": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the cabinet that is placed in the hallway near the door?",
        "answer": "The cabinet is gray.",
        "object_id": 21,
        "class": "cabinet",
        "position": [
            6.2474751472473145,
            2.8892838954925537,
            0.17803795635700226
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6460502401055195,
            0.0,
            0.7632948887943641
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz_234_cabinet_349331",
        "episode_history": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the cabinet that is located between the hallway and the bathroom with a mirror?",
        "answer": "Yellow.",
        "object_id": 234,
        "class": "cabinet",
        "position": [
            6.30633544921875,
            2.8892838954925537,
            0.8753546476364136
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2928109272505491,
            0.0,
            0.9561703618512098
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz_74_toilet_613624",
        "episode_history": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the toilet in the bathroom closed?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 74,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            10.965740203857422,
            2.8892838954925537,
            -0.3876238763332367
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5535702350279638,
            0.0,
            0.8328024945274148
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz_563_toilet_252038",
        "episode_history": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the toilet in the bathroom next to the sink open?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 563,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            3.5968177318573,
            0.08928397297859192,
            -1.115126132965088
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.14291111352400002,
            0.0,
            0.9897355271138499
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz_88_bathtub_722210",
        "episode_history": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is hanging in front of the bathtub in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A colorful shower curtain.",
        "object_id": 88,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            11.040982246398926,
            2.8892838954925537,
            -0.5892390608787537
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.014699354273916108,
            0.0,
            0.9998919586554988
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz_223_shower_curtain_296462",
        "episode_history": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to keep water from splashing out of the shower?",
        "answer": "The shower curtain in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 223,
        "class": "shower curtain",
        "position": [
            4.398934364318848,
            2.8892838954925537,
            -0.19328905642032623
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.08506919499403331,
            0.0,
            0.996375045885367
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz_409_couch_383175",
        "episode_history": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the couch with blue and white pillows in the living room?",
        "answer": "A ceiling fan.",
        "object_id": 409,
        "class": "couch",
        "position": [
            1.463606357574463,
            0.08928397297859192,
            0.13593295216560364
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8581163954969844,
            0.0,
            0.5134552091266218
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz_410_microwave_160114",
        "episode_history": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The microwave is above the stove, integrated into the cabinetry in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 410,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            8.224308013916016,
            0.08928397297859192,
            1.0046287775039673
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9995782053058677,
            0.0,
            0.029041547436204945
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz_411_oven_40890",
        "episode_history": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located below the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "An oven.",
        "object_id": 411,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            8.121756553649902,
            0.08928397297859192,
            0.40078771114349365
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9999989199999147,
            0.0,
            0.0014696964590220367
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz_418_refrigerator_673491",
        "episode_history": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the refrigerator in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A set of white cabinets.",
        "object_id": 418,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            5.455827236175537,
            0.08928397297859192,
            0.213329017162323
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9734532504332654,
            0.0,
            0.228885930587507
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz_536_bathroom_towel_949407",
        "episode_history": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the bathroom towel that is hanging on the wall near the toilet and below a small wreath?",
        "answer": "Red.",
        "object_id": 536,
        "class": "bathroom towel",
        "position": [
            3.6043314933776855,
            0.08928397297859192,
            -1.1854170560836792
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.27933041278909554,
            0.0,
            0.9601950429423564
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz_548_washing_machine_81326",
        "episode_history": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the red object located next to the dryer in the laundry area?",
        "answer": "A washing machine.",
        "object_id": 548,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            4.228726863861084,
            0.08928397297859192,
            -1.173736572265625
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5257961715105796,
            0.0,
            0.8506105959984376
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz_553_washing_machine_74401",
        "episode_history": "00062-ACZZiU6BXLz",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the washing machine that is located next to the bathroom with a white toilet and a wooden cabinet?",
        "answer": "Red.",
        "object_id": 553,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            4.034682273864746,
            0.08928397297859192,
            -0.9767348766326904
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.27824156039486225,
            0.0,
            0.960511131673669
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00081-5biL7VEkByM_11_stool_354711",
        "episode_history": "00081-5biL7VEkByM",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located directly above the stool near the corner cabinet?",
        "answer": "A television.",
        "object_id": 11,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            -1.9582724571228027,
            3.0728349685668945,
            -4.322329521179199
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.987226381176588,
            0.0,
            0.1593237970580012
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00081-5biL7VEkByM_457_range_hood_817878",
        "episode_history": "00081-5biL7VEkByM",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the range hood in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The stove and oven.",
        "object_id": 457,
        "class": "range hood",
        "position": [
            -5.623327255249023,
            0.07283496856689453,
            0.4804851710796356
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.01685328215044446,
            0.0,
            0.9998579733545948
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00081-5biL7VEkByM_497_microwave_824197",
        "episode_history": "00081-5biL7VEkByM",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A set of drawers.",
        "object_id": 497,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -6.362614631652832,
            0.07283496856689453,
            0.178024023771286
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.746301791325137,
            0.0,
            0.6656077195051839
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00081-5biL7VEkByM_690_monitor_262619",
        "episode_history": "00081-5biL7VEkByM",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to view my computer's display?",
        "answer": "The monitor on the desk.",
        "object_id": 690,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            -6.0437445640563965,
            0.07283496856689453,
            4.479886531829834
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8950483870544013,
            0.0,
            0.44596904021615097
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00099-226REUyJh2K_15_bathtub_111960",
        "episode_history": "00099-226REUyJh2K",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the bathtub in the bathroom empty?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 15,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            -6.555051803588867,
            -0.02846813201904297,
            -7.730800628662109
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9966650647630717,
            0.0,
            0.08160115612434087
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00099-226REUyJh2K_130_piano_181910",
        "episode_history": "00099-226REUyJh2K",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the red object placed on the red rug near the large windows in the living room?",
        "answer": "A piano.",
        "object_id": 130,
        "class": "piano",
        "position": [
            2.211798667907715,
            0.17153185606002808,
            -0.5648208856582642
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6730386394472739,
            0.0,
            0.7396073213611142
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00099-226REUyJh2K_205_refrigerator_109270",
        "episode_history": "00099-226REUyJh2K",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly to the right of the refrigerator in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A built-in oven.",
        "object_id": 205,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            15.78919506072998,
            0.17153185606002808,
            13.058036804199219
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.29904838365914177,
            0.0,
            0.9542379494816032
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00099-226REUyJh2K_206_refrigerator_834548",
        "episode_history": "00099-226REUyJh2K",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the refrigerator that is next to the built-in oven in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Silver.",
        "object_id": 206,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            15.304832458496094,
            0.17153185606002808,
            9.986418724060059
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.99723466285601,
            0.0,
            0.0743170720525038
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00099-226REUyJh2K_212_range_hood_158021",
        "episode_history": "00099-226REUyJh2K",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the metallic object mounted on the wall above the stove in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A range hood.",
        "object_id": 212,
        "class": "range hood",
        "position": [
            15.360830307006836,
            0.17153185606002808,
            10.34449291229248
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2659766985745723,
            0.0,
            0.9639794581916002
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00105-xWvSkKiWQpC_150_hanging_clothes_69036",
        "episode_history": "00105-xWvSkKiWQpC",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What are the objects hanging on the wall above the couch with orange pillows in the living room?",
        "answer": "Hanging clothes.",
        "object_id": 150,
        "class": "hanging clothes",
        "position": [
            -4.7270941734313965,
            0.016809388995170593,
            -0.33026033639907837
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9840772954858277,
            0.0,
            0.17774103777490116
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00105-xWvSkKiWQpC_154_coffee_table_59540",
        "episode_history": "00105-xWvSkKiWQpC",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there an object placed on the orange coffee table in the room with colorful patterned carpet?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 154,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            -4.721871852874756,
            0.016809388995170593,
            -0.718037486076355
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9988185515803594,
            0.0,
            0.048595277743001014
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00105-xWvSkKiWQpC_234_blackboard_584592",
        "episode_history": "00105-xWvSkKiWQpC",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the blackboard with the Starbucks logo?",
        "answer": "The blackboard with the Starbucks logo is leaning against the wall under the white folding table, near the kitchen area with the water dispenser and the refrigerator.",
        "object_id": 234,
        "class": "blackboard",
        "position": [
            -9.502057075500488,
            0.016809388995170593,
            -0.281570166349411
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5624466942182594,
            0.0,
            0.8268335480391151
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00105-xWvSkKiWQpC_340_banner_909373",
        "episode_history": "00105-xWvSkKiWQpC",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly behind the banner with the map on it?",
        "answer": "Two bar stools and a large wooden world map on the wall.",
        "object_id": 340,
        "class": "banner",
        "position": [
            -7.843203067779541,
            0.016809388995170593,
            -4.209300518035889
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8290924232981368,
            0.0,
            0.5591115752956854
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00105-xWvSkKiWQpC_386_toilet_694680",
        "episode_history": "00105-xWvSkKiWQpC",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the toilet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The toilet is in the bathroom, positioned between the sink and the storage shelves, with a handrail on the wall beside it.",
        "object_id": 386,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -11.210857391357422,
            0.016809388995170593,
            -3.1449170112609863
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8541663640790844,
            0.0,
            0.5199998293037386
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00105-xWvSkKiWQpC_388_wash_cabinet_274983",
        "episode_history": "00105-xWvSkKiWQpC",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the wash cabinet that is located next to the toilet and below a bulletin board with various notes?",
        "answer": "Gray.",
        "object_id": 388,
        "class": "wash cabinet",
        "position": [
            -13.285972595214844,
            0.016809388995170593,
            -3.2943997383117676
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9478410731497378,
            0.0,
            0.3187433137343486
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00105-xWvSkKiWQpC_436_sink_835328",
        "episode_history": "00105-xWvSkKiWQpC",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located below the microwave and next to the cleaning bottles in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A sink.",
        "object_id": 436,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            -11.313173294067383,
            0.016809388995170593,
            -0.14330430328845978
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.39110256362728324,
            0.0,
            0.9203471001335132
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG_59_scale_874474",
        "episode_history": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the scale in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A trash can with a patterned cloth draped over it.",
        "object_id": 59,
        "class": "scale",
        "position": [
            -2.716153621673584,
            3.199007034301758,
            -4.587287425994873
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5357038375271107,
            0.0,
            0.8444059441161739
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG_85_cardboard_box_37583",
        "episode_history": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the cardboard box next to the window in the room filled with items?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 85,
        "class": "cardboard box",
        "position": [
            2.336451530456543,
            3.199007034301758,
            -5.982076168060303
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.42451471198751917,
            0.0,
            0.9054210397964881
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG_192_washing_machine_520459",
        "episode_history": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the washing machine located?",
        "answer": "The washing machine is in the laundry room, next to a window with an arched design, and near a white laundry basket filled with clothes.",
        "object_id": 192,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            4.7781829833984375,
            3.199007034301758,
            -1.7717511653900146
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8508063891070353,
            0.0,
            0.5254792938400599
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG_345_storage_shelving_218836",
        "episode_history": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the storage shelving unit that is placed next to the staircase with white railings?",
        "answer": "Plastic.",
        "object_id": 345,
        "class": "storage shelving",
        "position": [
            1.3842527866363525,
            -0.0009930133819580078,
            -5.630578994750977
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.985491929822753,
            0.0,
            0.16972229156544633
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG_438_armchair_628254",
        "episode_history": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the armchair with the patterned cushion?",
        "answer": "The armchair with the patterned cushion is in the living room, positioned between the TV stand and the fireplace.",
        "object_id": 438,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            -1.6160770654678345,
            0.07049937546253204,
            -4.925302028656006
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8675743646738098,
            0.0,
            0.49730747205409603
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG_439_pouffe_461284",
        "episode_history": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the pouffe that is placed in front of the armchair near the fireplace with a colorful painting above it?",
        "answer": "The pouffe is dark brown.",
        "object_id": 439,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            -1.1433292627334595,
            0.12921860814094543,
            -3.3936963081359863
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.620441662912617,
            0.0,
            0.784252601476225
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG_440_air_conditioner_302582",
        "episode_history": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the tall, white object standing next to the TV stand in the living room?",
        "answer": "An air conditioner.",
        "object_id": 440,
        "class": "air conditioner",
        "position": [
            -4.373023986816406,
            0.1261523813009262,
            -4.846477508544922
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9577759167167521,
            0.0,
            0.28751572714789847
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG_441_tv_861057",
        "episode_history": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on top of the dark wooden cabinet in the living room, near the entrance?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 441,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -0.8669676184654236,
            0.012197344563901424,
            -5.484710693359375
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9675631765374685,
            0.0,
            0.2526291737086652
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG_799_tv_733386",
        "episode_history": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to watch my favorite shows and movies?",
        "answer": "The TV on top of the dresser.",
        "object_id": 799,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -3.1323628425598145,
            3.199007034301758,
            0.5283477306365967
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6140852435882913,
            0.0,
            0.789239706050772
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG_476_wall_clock_992957",
        "episode_history": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the wall clock in the living room showing the correct time?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 476,
        "class": "wall clock",
        "position": [
            -3.626739025115967,
            0.0368364155292511,
            -4.639412879943848
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9949949214825711,
            0.0,
            0.09992550337072242
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG_482_toy_645627",
        "episode_history": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the green circular toy on the floor in the room empty?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 482,
        "class": "toy",
        "position": [
            -4.039225101470947,
            0.1296292394399643,
            -5.054969310760498
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.12087250626440388,
            0.0,
            0.992668039794453
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG_507_toy_713931",
        "episode_history": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the toy with the red base?",
        "answer": "A table with a lamp and a bowl.",
        "object_id": 507,
        "class": "toy",
        "position": [
            -4.155503749847412,
            0.1687372922897339,
            -5.325621604919434
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.04130796428504405,
            0.0,
            0.9991464617795659
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG_569_dishwasher_506957",
        "episode_history": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the dishwasher in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A set of drawers.",
        "object_id": 569,
        "class": "dishwasher",
        "position": [
            6.724277496337891,
            -0.0009930133819580078,
            -4.451567649841309
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.05978882438261186,
            0.0,
            0.9982110480649597
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG_584_microwave_967770",
        "episode_history": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The microwave is mounted above the stove, between the wooden cabinets in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 584,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            5.426242828369141,
            -0.0009930133819580078,
            -4.352202892303467
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5784607831185115,
            0.0,
            0.8157101951023529
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG_756_paper_619227",
        "episode_history": "00135-HeSYRw7eMtG",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the paper on the wooden dresser in the room crumpled?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 756,
        "class": "paper",
        "position": [
            0.8520762920379639,
            -2.6009929180145264,
            -4.752025127410889
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9597933781549975,
            0.0,
            0.2807074477989819
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00141-iigzG1rtanx_119_led_tv_357640",
        "episode_history": "00141-iigzG1rtanx",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the LED TV on the white stand in the room turned off?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 119,
        "class": "led tv",
        "position": [
            6.1593217849731445,
            1.6452302932739258,
            1.447596788406372
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9841461372276754,
            0.0,
            0.1773594671277629
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00141-iigzG1rtanx_337_bathtub_545290",
        "episode_history": "00141-iigzG1rtanx",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the bathtub that is next to the window and the shower area?",
        "answer": "The bathtub is rectangular.",
        "object_id": 337,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            -7.00383996963501,
            1.6452302932739258,
            1.73378324508667
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.35123053655576403,
            0.0,
            0.9362890099700787
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00141-iigzG1rtanx_249_lamp_899290",
        "episode_history": "00141-iigzG1rtanx",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object mounted on the wall above the dresser next to the mannequin?",
        "answer": "A lamp.",
        "object_id": 249,
        "class": "lamp",
        "position": [
            0.05760300159454346,
            1.6452302932739258,
            7.384822845458984
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6084649005539073,
            0.0,
            0.7935807865579432
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00141-iigzG1rtanx_258_statue_269801",
        "episode_history": "00141-iigzG1rtanx",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object wearing a dress and standing next to the window in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "A statue.",
        "object_id": 258,
        "class": "statue",
        "position": [
            -0.3365660309791565,
            1.6452302932739258,
            6.024135589599609
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9255348493889386,
            0.0,
            0.3786624388113963
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00141-iigzG1rtanx_300_cabinet_540296",
        "episode_history": "00141-iigzG1rtanx",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the cabinet that is below the TV and next to the full-length mirror in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "The cabinet is made of mirrored glass.",
        "object_id": 300,
        "class": "cabinet",
        "position": [
            -6.740635871887207,
            1.6452302932739258,
            3.980626106262207
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8281743532525859,
            0.0,
            0.5604705528523876
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh_57_stove_820828",
        "episode_history": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the stove that is located on the kitchen island with a white countertop?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 57,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            7.343706130981445,
            0.17214226722717285,
            10.619725227355957
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6988223826510526,
            0.0,
            0.7152952380003
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh_164_sink_cabinet_863943",
        "episode_history": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color are the doors of the sink cabinet that is located below the white countertop and near the washing machine?",
        "answer": "Light brown.",
        "object_id": 164,
        "class": "sink cabinet",
        "position": [
            3.551644802093506,
            0.17214226722717285,
            9.646974563598633
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7832313930311612,
            0.0,
            0.6217303153059749
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh_130_food_tray_965441",
        "episode_history": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the top shelf of the white cart, next to the vase with flowers in the hallway?",
        "answer": "A food tray.",
        "object_id": 130,
        "class": "food tray",
        "position": [
            6.672313690185547,
            0.17214226722717285,
            3.977449417114258
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8771185252569754,
            0.0,
            0.480273976653981
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh_163_washing_machine_242410",
        "episode_history": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the washing machine in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "A shelf with two teal storage bins.",
        "object_id": 163,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            1.9694441556930542,
            0.17214226722717285,
            8.79651165008545
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9879632261904467,
            0.0,
            0.15468892557440134
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh_381_computer_desk_200365",
        "episode_history": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wooden computer desk with the black chair?",
        "answer": "The wooden computer desk with the black chair is in the room with the large window, positioned against the wall under the window. There is a black metal shelf to the left of the desk.",
        "object_id": 381,
        "class": "computer desk",
        "position": [
            -2.733096122741699,
            0.17214226722717285,
            9.387136459350586
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9568936916528856,
            0.0,
            0.2904383977281791
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh_384_computer_chair_685399",
        "episode_history": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the black computer chair?",
        "answer": "The black computer chair is in the study room, positioned in front of the wooden desk and near the window with a view of the trees outside.",
        "object_id": 384,
        "class": "computer chair",
        "position": [
            -4.836928367614746,
            0.17214226722717285,
            9.877477645874023
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9901494047825189,
            0.0,
            0.14001484281612886
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh_386_globe_435357",
        "episode_history": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the primary color of the globe that is placed on the top shelf of the black metal rack near the window?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 386,
        "class": "globe",
        "position": [
            -2.725907564163208,
            0.17214226722717285,
            10.499543190002441
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9851460891369931,
            0.0,
            0.1717183247591485
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh_394_storage_shelving_379843",
        "episode_history": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are there any books on the storage shelving unit next to the window in the study room?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 394,
        "class": "storage shelving",
        "position": [
            -4.492049694061279,
            0.17214226722717285,
            9.687602043151855
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9250703822539265,
            0.0,
            0.3797957186127487
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh_443_bathtub_290055",
        "episode_history": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object with mosaic tiles surrounding it in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A bathtub.",
        "object_id": 443,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            -5.736623287200928,
            0.17214226722717285,
            8.555630683898926
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3138285939833139,
            0.0,
            0.9494796541255933
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh_771_bath_cabinet_442547",
        "episode_history": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located below the window in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A bath cabinet.",
        "object_id": 771,
        "class": "bath cabinet",
        "position": [
            -5.341974258422852,
            -2.6278576850891113,
            7.991429328918457
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7062069439389601,
            0.0,
            0.7080054747898454
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh_485_bath_sink_320957",
        "episode_history": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bath sink with the folded towels?",
        "answer": "The bath sink with the folded towels is in the bathroom, next to the toilet and under the large mirror.",
        "object_id": 485,
        "class": "bath sink",
        "position": [
            -8.409703254699707,
            0.17214226722717285,
            4.721258163452148
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9503412989387395,
            0.0,
            0.3112096006414805
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh_591_pouffe_553911",
        "episode_history": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are the two blue pouffes next to the wooden wall in the living room aligned evenly?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 591,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            0.7671772241592407,
            -2.6278576850891113,
            -0.24351249635219574
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7218478943313634,
            0.0,
            0.6920517447773518
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh_592_pouffe_222574",
        "episode_history": "00150-LcAd9dhvVwh",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What are the two blue objects placed against the wooden wall next to the stone wall in the living room?",
        "answer": "Two pouffes.",
        "object_id": 592,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            0.710564374923706,
            -2.6278576850891113,
            0.18111497163772583
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7469682987228128,
            0.0,
            0.6648596548920281
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1_13_refrigerator_515057",
        "episode_history": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the refrigerator that is next to the wooden cabinets in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Silver.",
        "object_id": 13,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -2.1404852867126465,
            0.058402180671691895,
            3.0930323600769043
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.35617742254703116,
            0.0,
            0.9344183451044578
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1_40_microwave_87600",
        "episode_history": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The stove.",
        "object_id": 40,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -3.256441831588745,
            0.058402180671691895,
            2.0471320152282715
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.09594785917352819,
            0.0,
            0.9953863613291156
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1_54_kitchen_island_224891",
        "episode_history": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the kitchen island in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Three pendant lights.",
        "object_id": 54,
        "class": "kitchen island",
        "position": [
            -2.058588981628418,
            0.058402180671691895,
            5.01998233795166
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.053972019699410345,
            0.0,
            0.998542448316328
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1_89_table_412129",
        "episode_history": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the dining table with the white table runners?",
        "answer": "The dining table with the white table runners is located in the dining area, next to the kitchen and near the entrance to the bedroom. It is set with plates and napkins, and there is a decorative wall piece above it.",
        "object_id": 89,
        "class": "table",
        "position": [
            -0.9924594163894653,
            0.058402180671691895,
            3.2136616706848145
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7331359658040576,
            0.0,
            0.680082094783087
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1_114_washing_machine_540229",
        "episode_history": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash my clothes?",
        "answer": "The washing machine in the laundry room.",
        "object_id": 114,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            0.07418310642242432,
            0.058402180671691895,
            2.4220476150512695
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2483358385835185,
            0.0,
            0.9686739963863078
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1_154_toilet_916471",
        "episode_history": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located between the sink and the bathtub in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A toilet.",
        "object_id": 154,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            0.9449925422668457,
            0.058402180671691895,
            2.8018743991851807
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5439609371352773,
            0.0,
            0.8391105403168947
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1_272_toilet_895152",
        "episode_history": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to flush waste away?",
        "answer": "The toilet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 272,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -6.1161208152771,
            0.058402180671691895,
            2.9207310676574707
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.42461853848404524,
            0.0,
            0.9053723525575946
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1_237_dresser_452180",
        "episode_history": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I store my clothes neatly?",
        "answer": "The dresser in the bedroom.",
        "object_id": 237,
        "class": "dresser",
        "position": [
            -5.90512752532959,
            0.058402180671691895,
            5.286998748779297
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9167674797033736,
            0.0,
            0.3994213166048155
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1_191_tv_237672",
        "episode_history": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the TV mounted above the fireplace in the living room turned on?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 191,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -1.6432929039001465,
            0.058402180671691895,
            5.783456802368164
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8463703392863043,
            0.0,
            0.5325948260886373
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1_215_book_982184",
        "episode_history": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the book with a black cover?",
        "answer": "The book with a black cover is on the coffee table in the living room, between the gray sofa and the two patterned armchairs.",
        "object_id": 215,
        "class": "book",
        "position": [
            -1.2644249200820923,
            0.058402180671691895,
            5.510171890258789
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9755043512813785,
            0.0,
            0.21998013690126106
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1_245_desk_856850",
        "episode_history": "00166-RaYrxWt5pR1",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the desk by the window in the bedroom cluttered with items?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 245,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            -4.55682373046875,
            0.058402180671691895,
            7.059582233428955
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.985193804835574,
            0.0,
            0.17144435515235515
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00179-MVVzj944atG_13_end_table_370700",
        "episode_history": "00179-MVVzj944atG",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on the end table next to the bed in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A lamp and a small object (possibly an alarm clock or a phone).",
        "object_id": 13,
        "class": "end table",
        "position": [
            1.3017526865005493,
            2.78171706199646,
            2.9409546852111816
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5470552084958867,
            0.0,
            0.8370965289962214
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00179-MVVzj944atG_63_toilet_478704",
        "episode_history": "00179-MVVzj944atG",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to flush away waste?",
        "answer": "The toilet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 63,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            1.5450727939605713,
            2.78171706199646,
            1.2761001586914062
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.09951018633856683,
            0.0,
            0.9950365434570048
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00179-MVVzj944atG_78_bathtub_212280",
        "episode_history": "00179-MVVzj944atG",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is hanging on the wall to the left of the bathtub in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A yellow towel.",
        "object_id": 78,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            3.9961633682250977,
            2.78171706199646,
            0.4585409462451935
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5765106786109536,
            0.0,
            0.8170896140862015
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00179-MVVzj944atG_93_clothes_hamper_873497",
        "episode_history": "00179-MVVzj944atG",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the white clothes hamper?",
        "answer": "The white clothes hamper is in the bedroom, next to the black rolling cart and under the wall hooks with hanging clothes.",
        "object_id": 93,
        "class": "clothes hamper",
        "position": [
            6.366678714752197,
            2.78171706199646,
            0.05596913397312164
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9235628822392618,
            0.0,
            0.3834470009661144
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00179-MVVzj944atG_123_basket_859745",
        "episode_history": "00179-MVVzj944atG",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the yellow-lidded basket next to the blue wall in the room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 123,
        "class": "basket",
        "position": [
            5.7372026443481445,
            2.78171706199646,
            3.090172290802002
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9730678467596742,
            0.0,
            0.23051890508696168
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00179-MVVzj944atG_125_bean_bag_chair_126590",
        "episode_history": "00179-MVVzj944atG",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the gray bean bag chair in the corner of the room next to the white wardrobe upright?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 125,
        "class": "bean bag chair",
        "position": [
            4.287563323974609,
            2.78171706199646,
            2.3838047981262207
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9773796742806377,
            0.0,
            0.2114922511655536
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00179-MVVzj944atG_144_globe_990054",
        "episode_history": "00179-MVVzj944atG",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the globe on the desk under the loft bed?",
        "answer": "A framed photo and a blue lamp.",
        "object_id": 144,
        "class": "globe",
        "position": [
            5.895325183868408,
            2.78171706199646,
            3.507441997528076
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4064091851740483,
            0.0,
            0.913691180983031
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00179-MVVzj944atG_229_armchair_983008",
        "episode_history": "00179-MVVzj944atG",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the armchair that is placed near the yellow curtains and the lamp in the living room?",
        "answer": "Yellow.",
        "object_id": 229,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            1.4507427215576172,
            0.1817169487476349,
            1.8849732875823975
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9988591375036212,
            0.0,
            0.04775377917541274
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00179-MVVzj944atG_230_floor_lamp_563525",
        "episode_history": "00179-MVVzj944atG",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the lampshade on the floor lamp that is next to the yellow armchair and golden curtains?",
        "answer": "Gray.",
        "object_id": 230,
        "class": "floor lamp",
        "position": [
            1.1286039352416992,
            0.1817169487476349,
            3.075068473815918
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9992643098883484,
            0.0,
            0.03835151865805631
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00179-MVVzj944atG_297_floor_lamp_884631",
        "episode_history": "00179-MVVzj944atG",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the floor lamp next to the television in the living room turned on?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 297,
        "class": "floor lamp",
        "position": [
            6.612103462219238,
            0.1817169338464737,
            3.6812844276428223
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8045662954172452,
            0.0,
            0.593862842985289
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00179-MVVzj944atG_237_coffee_table_738827",
        "episode_history": "00179-MVVzj944atG",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color are the curtains next to the coffee table that has a vase with flowers on it?",
        "answer": "Yellow.",
        "object_id": 237,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            3.25986909866333,
            0.1817169487476349,
            1.235011100769043
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7218625504807538,
            0.0,
            0.6920364572863349
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00179-MVVzj944atG_298_tv_stand_857434",
        "episode_history": "00179-MVVzj944atG",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object directly below the TV in the living room?",
        "answer": "A TV stand.",
        "object_id": 298,
        "class": "tv stand",
        "position": [
            6.687682628631592,
            0.1817169487476349,
            1.9613165855407715
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9694332636451717,
            0.0,
            0.2453551453266699
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00179-MVVzj944atG_314_highchair_60209",
        "episode_history": "00179-MVVzj944atG",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the highchair located?",
        "answer": "The highchair is in the dining area, next to the sliding glass door and near the potted plant.",
        "object_id": 314,
        "class": "highchair",
        "position": [
            7.912500381469727,
            0.1817169487476349,
            2.115900993347168
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8831599371627314,
            0.0,
            0.46907198316539916
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00179-MVVzj944atG_315_flower_vase_357755",
        "episode_history": "00179-MVVzj944atG",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are the flowers in the vase on the dining table fresh?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 315,
        "class": "flower vase",
        "position": [
            7.061220645904541,
            0.1817169487476349,
            2.7585244178771973
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7969472068724738,
            0.0,
            0.6040489627986811
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00179-MVVzj944atG_316_dining_table_708725",
        "episode_history": "00179-MVVzj944atG",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I set up a place to eat with my family?",
        "answer": "The dining table in the dining area.",
        "object_id": 316,
        "class": "dining table",
        "position": [
            7.14938497543335,
            0.1817169487476349,
            0.6084427833557129
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9716814870774549,
            0.0,
            0.23629449352650234
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00203-VoVGtfYrpuQ_444_tv_61434",
        "episode_history": "00203-VoVGtfYrpuQ",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the TV that is mounted on the wall above the wooden cabinet with a plant on it?",
        "answer": "It is in rectangular shape.",
        "object_id": 444,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -5.012259006500244,
            -1.84773588180542,
            0.570728063583374
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9256568728703598,
            0.0,
            0.3783640491746888
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00203-VoVGtfYrpuQ_109_cabinet_242717",
        "episode_history": "00203-VoVGtfYrpuQ",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the cabinet that is placed below the wall-mounted TV and next to a green plant?",
        "answer": "The color of the cabinet is light wood.",
        "object_id": 109,
        "class": "cabinet",
        "position": [
            1.315770149230957,
            1.15226411819458,
            -0.11969611048698425
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.1832500815030216,
            0.0,
            0.9830663292113793
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00203-VoVGtfYrpuQ_153_bathtub_448122",
        "episode_history": "00203-VoVGtfYrpuQ",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the bathtub in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A shower enclosure.",
        "object_id": 153,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            0.35802552103996277,
            1.15226411819458,
            0.49689340591430664
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9571305627967187,
            0.0,
            0.2896568413837934
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00203-VoVGtfYrpuQ_183_desk_191615",
        "episode_history": "00203-VoVGtfYrpuQ",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to do my homework?",
        "answer": "The desk in the corner of the room.",
        "object_id": 183,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            -5.420281887054443,
            1.15226411819458,
            2.887573719024658
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5990849192491318,
            0.0,
            0.8006854935168123
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00203-VoVGtfYrpuQ_350_armchair_150853",
        "episode_history": "00203-VoVGtfYrpuQ",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object with cushions near the window in the living room?",
        "answer": "An armchair.",
        "object_id": 350,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            5.125634670257568,
            -1.84773588180542,
            0.5650148391723633
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8504469647482259,
            0.0,
            0.5260607951088255
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00203-VoVGtfYrpuQ_353_armchair_228414",
        "episode_history": "00203-VoVGtfYrpuQ",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the armchair with the patterned cushion?",
        "answer": "The armchair with the patterned cushion is in the hallway, next to the wall with the large oval mirror.",
        "object_id": 353,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            6.540295600891113,
            -1.84773588180542,
            3.0490167140960693
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4124416621662202,
            0.0,
            0.9109840148485403
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00203-VoVGtfYrpuQ_411_air_conditioner_728660",
        "episode_history": "00203-VoVGtfYrpuQ",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the air conditioner located?",
        "answer": "The air conditioner is mounted on the wall above the framed picture, near the dining area with a wooden table and chairs, adjacent to the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 411,
        "class": "air conditioner",
        "position": [
            -6.594557285308838,
            -1.84773588180542,
            -2.5465927124023438
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.24191166948271148,
            0.0,
            0.9702982758760769
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00203-VoVGtfYrpuQ_472_bowl_542612",
        "episode_history": "00203-VoVGtfYrpuQ",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the bowl on the kitchen counter filled with fruits?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 472,
        "class": "bowl",
        "position": [
            -4.685005187988281,
            -1.84773588180542,
            -3.6622374057769775
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6635354997090107,
            0.0,
            0.7481447992373624
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00203-VoVGtfYrpuQ_474_dishwasher_220912",
        "episode_history": "00203-VoVGtfYrpuQ",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the stainless steel object located under the counter next to the sink in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A dishwasher.",
        "object_id": 474,
        "class": "dishwasher",
        "position": [
            -1.984997272491455,
            -1.84773588180542,
            -1.6310102939605713
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.26226689693160493,
            0.0,
            0.9649953755194203
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00203-VoVGtfYrpuQ_481_ventilation_hood_137613",
        "episode_history": "00203-VoVGtfYrpuQ",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the metallic object located above the stove in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A ventilation hood.",
        "object_id": 481,
        "class": "ventilation hood",
        "position": [
            -2.0950560569763184,
            -1.84773588180542,
            -3.8704800605773926
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9622768554905542,
            0.0,
            0.2720721473933168
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00205-NEVASPhcrxR_394_stand_758245",
        "episode_history": "00205-NEVASPhcrxR",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the stand with the bucket?",
        "answer": "The stand with the bucket is located in the hallway, next to the curved sofa with a cushion, near the door.",
        "object_id": 394,
        "class": "stand",
        "position": [
            -8.493782997131348,
            -0.0004429817199707031,
            5.206413269042969
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6971287886210407,
            0.0,
            0.7169459199101146
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00205-NEVASPhcrxR_395_double_armchair_99425",
        "episode_history": "00205-NEVASPhcrxR",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on the small table next to the double armchair in the dimly lit room?",
        "answer": "A few items, including a bowl with some fruit.",
        "object_id": 395,
        "class": "double armchair",
        "position": [
            -10.088764190673828,
            0.19955706596374512,
            6.120353698730469
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6577843939764053,
            0.0,
            0.7532062738991844
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00205-NEVASPhcrxR_684_beverage_dispenser_738969",
        "episode_history": "00205-NEVASPhcrxR",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the beverage dispenser that is placed on the counter below the shelf with multiple jars?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 684,
        "class": "beverage dispenser",
        "position": [
            -6.128361701965332,
            -0.0004429817199707031,
            -3.848820686340332
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8592457552236142,
            0.0,
            0.5115630285020613
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00205-NEVASPhcrxR_971_stool_187993",
        "episode_history": "00205-NEVASPhcrxR",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the stool that is near the gray door and the wall with a light switch?",
        "answer": "The stool is cylindrical in shape.",
        "object_id": 971,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            -5.2819132804870605,
            3.199557304382324,
            0.4275963604450226
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5592897980583278,
            0.0,
            0.828972208091366
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00205-NEVASPhcrxR_1506_toilet_384183",
        "episode_history": "00205-NEVASPhcrxR",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located directly to the left of the toilet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A small white trash can.",
        "object_id": 1506,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            2.208644390106201,
            3.199557304382324,
            -2.099358081817627
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.432271956789746,
            0.0,
            0.901743286846741
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00207-FRQ75PjD278_272_tv_37853",
        "episode_history": "00207-FRQ75PjD278",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to watch my favorite shows and movies?",
        "answer": "The TV on the red cabinet.",
        "object_id": 272,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            3.4619152545928955,
            0.08834502846002579,
            -1.1531131267547607
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9743978491934541,
            0.0,
            0.22483067292335998
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00207-FRQ75PjD278_103_sink_cabinet_252170",
        "episode_history": "00207-FRQ75PjD278",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object directly in front of the mirror in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A sink cabinet.",
        "object_id": 103,
        "class": "sink cabinet",
        "position": [
            -2.7614645957946777,
            0.08834502846002579,
            5.441744804382324
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.10352107075003084,
            0.0,
            0.9946272607920855
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00207-FRQ75PjD278_139_laptop_467674",
        "episode_history": "00207-FRQ75PjD278",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to browse the internet and check my emails?",
        "answer": "The laptop on the bedside table.",
        "object_id": 139,
        "class": "laptop",
        "position": [
            -0.11062159389257431,
            0.08834502846002579,
            5.695898056030273
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9991006091502336,
            0.0,
            0.042402509308542974
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00207-FRQ75PjD278_198_ventilation_hood_617389",
        "episode_history": "00207-FRQ75PjD278",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the metallic object above the stove in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A ventilation hood.",
        "object_id": 198,
        "class": "ventilation hood",
        "position": [
            0.9954544305801392,
            0.08834502846002579,
            -2.193774700164795
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5555858068759056,
            0.0,
            0.8314592059734793
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00207-FRQ75PjD278_277_sideboard_401469",
        "episode_history": "00207-FRQ75PjD278",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the red object below the TV in the living room?",
        "answer": "A sideboard.",
        "object_id": 277,
        "class": "sideboard",
        "position": [
            2.039250373840332,
            0.08834502846002579,
            0.4668302834033966
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7687784988427454,
            0.0,
            0.6395151442437427
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00207-FRQ75PjD278_295_pouffe_424052",
        "episode_history": "00207-FRQ75PjD278",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the black pouffe?",
        "answer": "The black pouffe is located in the room with the slanted ceiling, positioned between the two beige sofas and near the window with the radiator underneath.",
        "object_id": 295,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            4.461800575256348,
            0.08834502846002579,
            -2.6118106842041016
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6126831363266138,
            0.0,
            0.7903286496521457
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00207-FRQ75PjD278_294_coffee_table_664924",
        "episode_history": "00207-FRQ75PjD278",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the coffee table with a wooden top?",
        "answer": "The coffee table with a wooden top is in the living room, positioned between the two sofas and in front of the TV.",
        "object_id": 294,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            3.814785957336426,
            0.08834502846002579,
            -4.509692668914795
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9911127220070907,
            0.0,
            0.1330247055087718
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00207-FRQ75PjD278_317_fish_tank_526044",
        "episode_history": "00207-FRQ75PjD278",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the plant pot that is placed next to the fish tank below the butterfly frames?",
        "answer": "Green.",
        "object_id": 317,
        "class": "fish tank",
        "position": [
            3.0789260864257812,
            0.08834502846002579,
            -3.125697374343872
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.38976967200011625,
            0.0,
            0.9209123751958824
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00207-FRQ75PjD278_345_desk_165851",
        "episode_history": "00207-FRQ75PjD278",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the desk next to the fish tank in the room cluttered with items?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 345,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            3.627065658569336,
            0.08834502846002579,
            -4.332736968994141
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6979471026535486,
            0.0,
            0.7161493153648314
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00207-FRQ75PjD278_472_desk_322980",
        "episode_history": "00207-FRQ75PjD278",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located against the wall with butterfly pictures hanging above it, in the room with the shoe rack?",
        "answer": "A desk.",
        "object_id": 472,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            2.8225345611572266,
            0.08834502846002579,
            3.1230201721191406
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4451962339476638,
            0.0,
            0.8954330311524236
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf_94_footrest_684761",
        "episode_history": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the footrest at the end of the bed in the bedroom empty?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 94,
        "class": "footrest",
        "position": [
            -1.4127309322357178,
            2.8339812755584717,
            -0.48289021849632263
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.650104581570723,
            0.0,
            0.7598447427078476
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf_220_monitor_408913",
        "episode_history": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the monitor on the wooden cabinet?",
        "answer": "A small wooden cabinet with a drawer and a door.",
        "object_id": 220,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            4.61659049987793,
            2.8339812755584717,
            4.812073707580566
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.1576473596756068,
            0.0,
            0.9874954734009214
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf_612_monitor_905736",
        "episode_history": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the monitor that is placed on the wooden desk near the black office chair?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 612,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            4.9649505615234375,
            0.033981382846832275,
            -1.1196885108947754
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.969879536699689,
            0.0,
            0.2435850658213609
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf_223_desk_920797",
        "episode_history": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the desk in the room?",
        "answer": "A standing fan.",
        "object_id": 223,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            2.7246124744415283,
            2.8339812755584717,
            4.879072666168213
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6463323359869583,
            0.0,
            0.763056034284273
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf_519_led_tv_140230",
        "episode_history": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the LED TV located?",
        "answer": "The LED TV is mounted on the wall in the living room, next to a large vase with decorative branches and near the sliding glass door that leads to the patio.",
        "object_id": 519,
        "class": "led tv",
        "position": [
            3.287903308868408,
            0.033981382846832275,
            3.448294162750244
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9015153291908817,
            0.0,
            0.4327471677941475
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf_314_pouffe_344721",
        "episode_history": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the black pouffe with studs?",
        "answer": "The black pouffe with studs is located in the dining room, next to the wooden cabinet with glass doors and near the entrance to the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 314,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            -2.1484475135803223,
            0.033981382846832275,
            0.09992887079715729
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9759166041557966,
            0.0,
            0.2181439472756892
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf_366_coffee_machine_359421",
        "episode_history": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the coffee machine located?",
        "answer": "The coffee machine is on the kitchen counter, between a decorative item and a red jar, under the wooden cabinets.",
        "object_id": 366,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            -3.745070219039917,
            0.033981382846832275,
            3.6100945472717285
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.17621029607354727,
            0.0,
            0.9843525443445924
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf_395_kitchen_shelf_272467",
        "episode_history": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the black metal kitchen shelf?",
        "answer": "The black metal kitchen shelf is in the kitchen, next to the black refrigerator and near the entrance to the living room.",
        "object_id": 395,
        "class": "kitchen shelf",
        "position": [
            -3.7122538089752197,
            0.033981382846832275,
            3.1596102714538574
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8387808388636551,
            0.0,
            0.5444691950470504
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf_494_coffee_table_544063",
        "episode_history": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the coffee table that is placed on the colorful patterned rug in front of the brown sofa?",
        "answer": "Rectangular.",
        "object_id": 494,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            3.7154150009155273,
            0.033981382846832275,
            4.797304630279541
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.09022125021376828,
            0.0,
            0.9959217469308844
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf_520_tv_stand_159082",
        "episode_history": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the TV stand in the living room cluttered with items?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 520,
        "class": "tv stand",
        "position": [
            3.7330551147460938,
            0.053394198417663574,
            5.213840484619141
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6806338583570802,
            0.0,
            0.7326237443995068
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf_556_bedside_table_744406",
        "episode_history": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bedside table with the lamp on it?",
        "answer": "The bedside table is in the living room, positioned between the brown sofa and the brown armchair, with a lamp and some decorative items on top.",
        "object_id": 556,
        "class": "bedside table",
        "position": [
            3.2462549209594727,
            0.033981382846832275,
            3.496706962585449
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3498989719894026,
            0.0,
            0.936787440885476
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf_580_cat_bed_498647",
        "episode_history": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the floor between the cabinet and the rocking chair in the living room?",
        "answer": "A cat bed.",
        "object_id": 580,
        "class": "cat bed",
        "position": [
            0.8391143083572388,
            0.033981382846832275,
            0.16650532186031342
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.09787715133530735,
            0.0,
            0.9951985044434528
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf_616_printer_141769",
        "episode_history": "00217-qz3829g1Lzf",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the printer that is on the wooden side table near the lamp with a brown base?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 616,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            4.536520481109619,
            0.033981382846832275,
            -0.5235264897346497
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9907459768417392,
            0.0,
            0.13572917656829345
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00222-g8Xrdbe9fir_62_mirror_413832",
        "episode_history": "00222-g8Xrdbe9fir",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to check my appearance?",
        "answer": "The mirror above the sink in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 62,
        "class": "mirror",
        "position": [
            0.6480988264083862,
            0.16506898403167725,
            5.210463523864746
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8421995944359899,
            0.0,
            0.5391658771953713
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00222-g8Xrdbe9fir_63_sink_cabinet_719756",
        "episode_history": "00222-g8Xrdbe9fir",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the sink cabinet located?",
        "answer": "The sink cabinet is in the bathroom, next to the bathtub and under the mirror.",
        "object_id": 63,
        "class": "sink cabinet",
        "position": [
            -0.02392183244228363,
            0.16506898403167725,
            3.578641891479492
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.952320442958064,
            0.0,
            0.3050996131170232
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00222-g8Xrdbe9fir_140_sink_cabinet_261754",
        "episode_history": "00222-g8Xrdbe9fir",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the sink cabinet located?",
        "answer": "The sink cabinet is in the kitchen, directly below the sink and between the stove and the microwave.",
        "object_id": 140,
        "class": "sink cabinet",
        "position": [
            4.875818252563477,
            0.16506898403167725,
            4.198501110076904
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7562534818260805,
            0.0,
            0.6542787412303184
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00222-g8Xrdbe9fir_75_bathtub_718838",
        "episode_history": "00222-g8Xrdbe9fir",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the large white object in the center of the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A bathtub.",
        "object_id": 75,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            0.6782556772232056,
            0.16506898403167725,
            3.740025043487549
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9972398841047792,
            0.0,
            0.07424697671075792
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00222-g8Xrdbe9fir_119_armchair_625462",
        "episode_history": "00222-g8Xrdbe9fir",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there a cushion on the brown leather armchair in the living room?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 119,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            2.1997122764587402,
            0.16506898403167725,
            2.1050591468811035
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6684892180600921,
            0.0,
            0.7437218333069204
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00222-g8Xrdbe9fir_124_sink_580375",
        "episode_history": "00222-g8Xrdbe9fir",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash the dishes?",
        "answer": "The sink on the kitchen counter.",
        "object_id": 124,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            3.2565343379974365,
            0.16506898403167725,
            2.9067392349243164
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9648883773416164,
            0.0,
            0.2626602734923256
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00222-g8Xrdbe9fir_126_microwave_352907",
        "episode_history": "00222-g8Xrdbe9fir",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The microwave is on the countertop in the kitchen, next to the double sink and under the wooden cabinets.",
        "object_id": 126,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            2.938438892364502,
            0.16506898403167725,
            5.148360729217529
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2004902562559515,
            0.0,
            0.9796956961967439
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00222-g8Xrdbe9fir_129_refrigerator_251489",
        "episode_history": "00222-g8Xrdbe9fir",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the refrigerator in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The stove and oven.",
        "object_id": 129,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            5.328107833862305,
            0.16506898403167725,
            6.5290679931640625
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7041047309498337,
            0.0,
            0.710096139867034
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5_483_chest_of_drawers_64173",
        "episode_history": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the chest of drawers that is placed near the spiral staircase and the colorful patchwork armchair?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 483,
        "class": "chest of drawers",
        "position": [
            -2.4138686656951904,
            -2.7355449199676514,
            -2.1098437309265137
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7553287093338178,
            0.0,
            0.6553461229427614
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5_160_laundry_basket_87802",
        "episode_history": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "Is the laundry basket in the bathroom placed next to the radiator?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 160,
        "class": "laundry basket",
        "position": [
            3.977963447570801,
            0.06445503234863281,
            -2.209655284881592
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6534571025083356,
            0.0,
            0.7569635494404011
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5_206_tv_832377",
        "episode_history": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the TV that is placed on the wooden stand near the window with a potted plant?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 206,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            4.30722713470459,
            0.06445503234863281,
            1.8203809261322021
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.023282576975378905,
            0.0,
            0.9997289240636111
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5_221_scale_93829",
        "episode_history": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the digital scale in the corner of the room placed flat on the floor?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 221,
        "class": "scale",
        "position": [
            3.849001169204712,
            0.06445503234863281,
            0.2340739518404007
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.40551402242141216,
            0.0,
            0.9140888237034771
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5_468_toilet_619774",
        "episode_history": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the toilet that is located in the small bathroom with a window above it?",
        "answer": "The toilet has a rounded shape.",
        "object_id": 468,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -0.7132139205932617,
            -2.7355449199676514,
            -2.1870012283325195
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7354768506390925,
            0.0,
            0.6775498521688289
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5_272_washing_machine_171494",
        "episode_history": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the washing machine that is placed next to the window and a white appliance in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 272,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            9.278963088989258,
            -2.7355449199676514,
            -6.024004936218262
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6482787297979926,
            0.0,
            0.7614031051233645
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5_279_watering_can_900958",
        "episode_history": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to water the plants in the garden?",
        "answer": "The watering can next to the sink.",
        "object_id": 279,
        "class": "watering can",
        "position": [
            11.28958797454834,
            -2.7355449199676514,
            -4.702399730682373
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7961521130469819,
            0.0,
            0.605096531878035
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5_300_clothes_691772",
        "episode_history": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are the clothes hanging on the chair in the garage neatly folded?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 300,
        "class": "clothes",
        "position": [
            8.324380874633789,
            -2.7355449199676514,
            -5.46317720413208
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.07673134765307274,
            0.0,
            0.9970518042144768
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5_303_trash_bag_49463",
        "episode_history": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What are the colors of the trash bags that are placed on the floor near the white storage cabinets?",
        "answer": "Blue and pink.",
        "object_id": 303,
        "class": "trash bag",
        "position": [
            8.529510498046875,
            -2.7355449199676514,
            -5.067567348480225
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.03997334245588128,
            0.0,
            0.9992007465434085
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5_338_dishwasher_274277",
        "episode_history": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the dishwasher that is located between the white cabinets and below the kitchen window?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 338,
        "class": "dishwasher",
        "position": [
            5.553977966308594,
            -2.7355449199676514,
            -2.6735172271728516
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8458235685851978,
            0.0,
            0.5334627361173423
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5_350_oven_957036",
        "episode_history": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the oven that is built into the white kitchen cabinets next to the green door?",
        "answer": "Stainless steel (silver).",
        "object_id": 350,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            4.688405513763428,
            -2.7355449199676514,
            -0.9991843700408936
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.011419650547520126,
            0.0,
            0.9999347936647531
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5_357_cooker_881150",
        "episode_history": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object installed on the countertop in the kitchen, directly below the range hood?",
        "answer": "A cooker.",
        "object_id": 357,
        "class": "cooker",
        "position": [
            6.930862903594971,
            -2.7355449199676514,
            -2.613600730895996
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.385946180942666,
            0.0,
            0.9225212980824729
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5_377_fireplace_74659",
        "episode_history": "00234-nACV8wLu1u5",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What objects are hanging on the wall to the left of the fireplace?",
        "answer": "Two framed pictures.",
        "object_id": 377,
        "class": "fireplace",
        "position": [
            1.1687836647033691,
            -2.7355449199676514,
            1.2683937549591064
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.12793747894218432,
            0.0,
            0.9917822349094171
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00238-j6fHrce9pHR_126_refrigerator_160651",
        "episode_history": "00238-j6fHrce9pHR",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the refrigerator in the room with white cabinets and a wooden countertop closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 126,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -13.656002044677734,
            0.0835769772529602,
            0.043374449014663696
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3195742005521907,
            0.0,
            0.9475612541368649
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00238-j6fHrce9pHR_363_laundry_machine_737244",
        "episode_history": "00238-j6fHrce9pHR",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the laundry machine located?",
        "answer": "The laundry machine is in the laundry room, next to the sink and under the wooden cabinets, near the window with a white curtain.",
        "object_id": 363,
        "class": "laundry machine",
        "position": [
            -13.91253662109375,
            0.0835769772529602,
            7.929533958435059
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9743829854577061,
            0.0,
            0.22489508142804587
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00238-j6fHrce9pHR_296_oven_339466",
        "episode_history": "00238-j6fHrce9pHR",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the oven in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A wooden cabinet.",
        "object_id": 296,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            -5.447199821472168,
            0.0835769772529602,
            4.665107250213623
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9456109647701856,
            0.0,
            0.32529971304383015
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00238-j6fHrce9pHR_331_table_lamp_197905",
        "episode_history": "00238-j6fHrce9pHR",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the table lamp's base that is on the small table next to the brown armchair and under the painting with a golden frame?",
        "answer": "The base of the table lamp is round.",
        "object_id": 331,
        "class": "table lamp",
        "position": [
            -10.833684921264648,
            0.0835769772529602,
            8.074373245239258
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.940699639352733,
            0.0,
            0.3392406056497929
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00241-h6nwVLpAKQz_94_tv_690452",
        "episode_history": "00241-h6nwVLpAKQz",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the TV on top of the wooden dresser in the bedroom turned off?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 94,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            5.884246826171875,
            2.7986433506011963,
            -7.956277370452881
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7012008947130792,
            0.0,
            0.7129637475030389
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00241-h6nwVLpAKQz_135_bag_778335",
        "episode_history": "00241-h6nwVLpAKQz",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the blue bag on the floor of the closet in the bedroom zipped closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 135,
        "class": "bag",
        "position": [
            1.4620590209960938,
            2.5986435413360596,
            -5.837026596069336
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9836784692054847,
            0.0,
            0.17993518061111455
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00241-h6nwVLpAKQz_154_ladder_344918",
        "episode_history": "00241-h6nwVLpAKQz",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the ladder attached to the bunk bed in the bedroom properly aligned and stable?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 154,
        "class": "ladder",
        "position": [
            1.355392336845398,
            2.5986435413360596,
            -7.189802169799805
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9769185012641551,
            0.0,
            0.21361236361174485
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00241-h6nwVLpAKQz_394_fan_611573",
        "episode_history": "00241-h6nwVLpAKQz",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the fan that is placed near the sliding glass door and the fireplace?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 394,
        "class": "fan",
        "position": [
            2.8171753883361816,
            -0.0013566017150878906,
            -5.634873867034912
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.947369107528467,
            0.0,
            0.32014336491752576
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00241-h6nwVLpAKQz_320_microwave_368566",
        "episode_history": "00241-h6nwVLpAKQz",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to quickly heat up my leftovers?",
        "answer": "The microwave above the stove.",
        "object_id": 320,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            1.8000576496124268,
            -0.0013566017150878906,
            -8.267631530761719
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6015941026350508,
            0.0,
            0.7988019377009097
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00241-h6nwVLpAKQz_326_refrigerator_175946",
        "episode_history": "00241-h6nwVLpAKQz",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the stainless steel refrigerator?",
        "answer": "The stainless steel refrigerator is in the kitchen, to the right of the small counter and next to the white cabinets.",
        "object_id": 326,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            1.083838939666748,
            -0.0013566017150878906,
            -7.528264045715332
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2919415006913253,
            0.0,
            0.9564361767384675
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00241-h6nwVLpAKQz_392_pouffe_802321",
        "episode_history": "00241-h6nwVLpAKQz",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are the two pouffes next to the sliding glass door in the living room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 392,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            1.4436428546905518,
            -0.0013566017150878906,
            -5.22550106048584
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9088724453312347,
            0.0,
            0.41707418778632416
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8_47_bin_668342",
        "episode_history": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I throw away some trash?",
        "answer": "The bin next to the wooden cabinet.",
        "object_id": 47,
        "class": "bin",
        "position": [
            -9.170427322387695,
            0.07911548018455505,
            3.10261607170105
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.239713809158115,
            0.0,
            0.9708435969294471
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8_472_bin_560664",
        "episode_history": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I dispose of small bathroom waste items?",
        "answer": "The bin next to the toilet.",
        "object_id": 472,
        "class": "bin",
        "position": [
            4.670167446136475,
            0.07911548018455505,
            -4.645965576171875
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9630812404727709,
            0.0,
            0.26921092891899717
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8_48_speaker_83098",
        "episode_history": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the circular object mounted on the wall to the right of the TV in the living room?",
        "answer": "A speaker.",
        "object_id": 48,
        "class": "speaker",
        "position": [
            -5.09857702255249,
            0.07911548018455505,
            2.611837863922119
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3201141185677329,
            0.0,
            0.9473789902112055
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8_220_speaker_210276",
        "episode_history": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the black speaker on the wooden cabinet next to the large potted plant in the living room turned on?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 220,
        "class": "speaker",
        "position": [
            -8.123530387878418,
            0.07911548018455505,
            -5.480381011962891
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.24220250947745747,
            0.0,
            0.9702257182753001
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8_137_book_835245",
        "episode_history": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the primary color of the book that is placed on the uniquely shaped stone bench covered with a cloth?",
        "answer": "Blue.",
        "object_id": 137,
        "class": "book",
        "position": [
            -0.8033682107925415,
            0.07911548018455505,
            -4.644198417663574
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8098628594441547,
            0.0,
            0.5866192537693741
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8_334_book_451445",
        "episode_history": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the book on the small round table next to the sofa in the living room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 334,
        "class": "book",
        "position": [
            -10.201408386230469,
            0.07911548018455505,
            -10.157257080078125
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.974256472555489,
            0.0,
            0.22544251081758063
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8_151_microwave_883348",
        "episode_history": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the microwave built into the wooden cabinet in the kitchen closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 151,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -3.7378926277160645,
            0.07911548018455505,
            -4.625456809997559
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.29767585563751464,
            0.0,
            0.9546670021376426
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8_180_bathroom_counter_664750",
        "episode_history": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the bathroom counter?",
        "answer": "A wooden shelf with towels and other items.",
        "object_id": 180,
        "class": "bathroom counter",
        "position": [
            -0.2292831838130951,
            0.07911548018455505,
            -2.3761279582977295
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.713528264709414,
            0.0,
            0.7006264450195786
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8_212_chandelier_355362",
        "episode_history": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the chandelier with the woven design?",
        "answer": "The chandelier with the woven design is hanging above the wooden dining table in the dining area, near the large framed artwork on the wall.",
        "object_id": 212,
        "class": "chandelier",
        "position": [
            -10.012892723083496,
            0.07911548018455505,
            -2.1925418376922607
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9340911234063665,
            0.0,
            0.35703469463545434
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8_327_desk_330312",
        "episode_history": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the desk that is placed against the wall near the large window with curtains?",
        "answer": "The desk is brown.",
        "object_id": 327,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            -5.403069496154785,
            0.07911548018455505,
            -7.848954677581787
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.751899534775591,
            0.0,
            0.6592777029478928
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8_328_desk_chair_299848",
        "episode_history": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the desk chair in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "The desk chair is in the bedroom, positioned in front of the wooden desk with a lamp on it, near the wall with a framed picture.",
        "object_id": 328,
        "class": "desk chair",
        "position": [
            -9.559904098510742,
            0.07911548018455505,
            -10.601428985595703
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9829399258126317,
            0.0,
            0.1839268937471005
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8_329_desk_lamp_573999",
        "episode_history": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the texture of the desk lamp that is placed on the wooden desk below the cactus painting?",
        "answer": "The texture of the desk lamp is ribbed.",
        "object_id": 329,
        "class": "desk lamp",
        "position": [
            -7.3249616622924805,
            0.07911548018455505,
            -8.739777565002441
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9078765676098566,
            0.0,
            0.41923756747808927
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8_483_scale_234657",
        "episode_history": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the scale under the bathroom sink in the cabinet area properly aligned and placed flat?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 483,
        "class": "scale",
        "position": [
            4.896520614624023,
            0.07911548018455505,
            -6.865325927734375
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.852206863086497,
            0.0,
            0.5232049909053551
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8_537_pouffe_936909",
        "episode_history": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What are the two brown, square-shaped objects placed in front of the TV stand in the living room?",
        "answer": "Pouffes.",
        "object_id": 537,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            4.62199068069458,
            0.07911548018455505,
            -7.742997169494629
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.30935025429140245,
            0.0,
            0.9509481690238667
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8_538_pouffe_923291",
        "episode_history": "00250-U3oQjwTuMX8",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is above the pouffes near the hallway?",
        "answer": "Two framed pieces of artwork hung on the wall.",
        "object_id": 538,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            5.200478553771973,
            0.07911548018455505,
            -11.525479316711426
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9272078005854586,
            0.0,
            0.3745473194851039
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_16_laundry_machine_899209",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash my clothes?",
        "answer": "The laundry machine in the utility room.",
        "object_id": 16,
        "class": "laundry machine",
        "position": [
            8.824420928955078,
            0.01942509412765503,
            -1.4664230346679688
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7138215697228887,
            0.0,
            0.7003276137625527
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_17_laundry_machine_660312",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the left laundry machine in the garage closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 17,
        "class": "laundry machine",
        "position": [
            8.421256065368652,
            0.01446029543876648,
            -0.9827489256858826
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5188515567588886,
            0.0,
            0.8548643530109779
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_88_dog_bed_314460",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located to the right of the dog bed in the garage?",
        "answer": "A yellow vacuum cleaner.",
        "object_id": 88,
        "class": "dog bed",
        "position": [
            7.842167854309082,
            0.01446029543876648,
            -1.0076673030853271
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6171360669274544,
            0.0,
            0.7868564512649766
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_157_dog_bed_766897",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the dog bed in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "A wooden shelf with various items on it.",
        "object_id": 157,
        "class": "dog bed",
        "position": [
            10.26358413696289,
            0.01446029543876648,
            1.6981770992279053
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6346828652995988,
            0.0,
            0.7727727094657855
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_124_hat_748584",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the hat hanging on the wall?",
        "answer": "The hat is hanging on a hook on the wall in the hallway, next to a painting and near the entrance to the room with wooden flooring.",
        "object_id": 124,
        "class": "hat",
        "position": [
            7.869245529174805,
            0.01446029543876648,
            2.1036510467529297
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5723470163101607,
            0.0,
            0.8200115199927722
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_182_refrigerator_678284",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the large stainless steel object located between the pantry and the kitchen counter?",
        "answer": "A refrigerator.",
        "object_id": 182,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            1.9506115913391113,
            0.01446029543876648,
            1.5511935949325562
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.918300891935554,
            0.0,
            0.3958831543149643
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_200_sink_738367",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly to the right of the sink in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A dishwasher.",
        "object_id": 200,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            2.3401050567626953,
            0.01446029543876648,
            3.4408960342407227
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9879374981505353,
            0.0,
            0.15485315543463252
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_206_stove_759860",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the stove located?",
        "answer": "The stove is in the kitchen, built into the countertop between the dishwasher and the set of drawers, under the range hood.",
        "object_id": 206,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            2.748081684112549,
            0.01446029543876648,
            3.0910258293151855
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9238409856852539,
            0.0,
            0.3827764793820264
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_215_microwave_926647",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the microwave that is built into the wooden cabinet near the doorway?",
        "answer": "Silver.",
        "object_id": 215,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            3.712167739868164,
            0.01446029543876648,
            2.9956114292144775
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.37971399209068923,
            0.0,
            0.9251039315723136
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_250_dining_table_853379",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the dining table in the dining room?",
        "answer": "A hanging light fixture.",
        "object_id": 250,
        "class": "dining table",
        "position": [
            2.2192986011505127,
            0.01446029543876648,
            -3.165985107421875
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9768196969521075,
            0.0,
            0.21406372800264747
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_267_fireplace_516582",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the glass door of the fireplace in the living room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 267,
        "class": "fireplace",
        "position": [
            -1.3259555101394653,
            0.2144603133201599,
            -4.131685256958008
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9440679068122728,
            0.0,
            0.32975109905365546
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_271_armchair_410457",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there a blanket draped over the back of the armchair in the living room?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 271,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            -4.4677886962890625,
            0.01446029543876648,
            -3.258601665496826
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7229655709007806,
            0.0,
            0.6908840592256478
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_555_armchair_856966",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed near the sliding glass door and next to the small footstool in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "An armchair.",
        "object_id": 555,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            -13.309486389160156,
            0.01446029543876648,
            0.7202168703079224
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6575765887604789,
            0.0,
            0.7533877022583605
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_272_chair_55597",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the cushion on the chair near the window in the living room properly placed?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 272,
        "class": "chair",
        "position": [
            -0.4808691442012787,
            0.2523735761642456,
            -3.443218231201172
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.36416814493599536,
            0.0,
            0.9313332176046745
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_278_piano_978147",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the grand piano located?",
        "answer": "The grand piano is in the living room, near the windows with white shutters and next to the entrance to another room with a rocking chair.",
        "object_id": 278,
        "class": "piano",
        "position": [
            0.5234034061431885,
            0.3107861876487732,
            -3.017514228820801
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5305449371366222,
            0.0,
            0.8476568112619031
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_284_coffee_table_693328",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is the object to the left of the coffee table in the living room?",
        "answer": "An armchair with a blanket draped over it.",
        "object_id": 284,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            2.2862608432769775,
            0.11080821603536606,
            -2.267948865890503
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4237484444736727,
            0.0,
            0.9057799157665966
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_303_speaker_891905",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the speaker that is placed next to the wooden cabinet below the wall-mounted TV?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 303,
        "class": "speaker",
        "position": [
            -0.55064857006073,
            0.06304432451725006,
            -0.5130442976951599
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.852163221494919,
            0.0,
            0.5232760685636232
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_314_easy_chair_175195",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the black easy chair?",
        "answer": "The black easy chair is in the living room, positioned next to the sliding glass door and adjacent to the beige sectional sofa.",
        "object_id": 314,
        "class": "easy chair",
        "position": [
            0.7469930648803711,
            0.11233744770288467,
            2.7158873081207275
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7581094005725387,
            0.0,
            0.6521273930479735
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_441_lamp_257459",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the wooden table next to the bed in the corner of the room that provides light?",
        "answer": "A lamp.",
        "object_id": 441,
        "class": "lamp",
        "position": [
            -7.175397872924805,
            0.01446029543876648,
            -3.2515411376953125
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7489566126931038,
            0.0,
            0.662619040100171
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_471_table_lamp_275058",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the table lamp on the wooden side table?",
        "answer": "A decorative plate.",
        "object_id": 471,
        "class": "table lamp",
        "position": [
            -12.877620697021484,
            0.01446029543876648,
            -5.308910369873047
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7243917530075512,
            0.0,
            0.6893885610993608
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_542_nightstand_566472",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the drawer of the nightstand next to the bed in the bedroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 542,
        "class": "nightstand",
        "position": [
            -13.447173118591309,
            0.01446029543876648,
            0.8146998882293701
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9977414398032362,
            0.0,
            0.06717156615232343
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_493_hanging_clothes_531843",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the predominant color of the hanging clothes in the closet that is next to the shelves with folded clothes?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 493,
        "class": "hanging clothes",
        "position": [
            -12.242603302001953,
            0.01446029543876648,
            -5.346268653869629
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8294973777935171,
            0.0,
            0.5585106088819435
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_509_toilet_358102",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the toilet that is next to the shower area with beige tiles?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 509,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -16.735567092895508,
            0.01446029543876648,
            0.8215240836143494
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.514750913616864,
            0.0,
            0.8573397791602836
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_688_toilet_845966",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly to the right of the toilet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The bathtub with a shower curtain.",
        "object_id": 688,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -6.3838911056518555,
            0.01446029543876648,
            1.4367878437042236
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9941862518611144,
            0.0,
            0.10767402941448855
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_510_stool_734091",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the small stool in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The small stool is located next to the toilet, near the shower area in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 510,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            -17.424198150634766,
            0.01446029543876648,
            0.5372985601425171
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.38841947738190763,
            0.0,
            0.9214826691752622
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_539_desk_196588",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the drawer of the wooden desk in the bedroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 539,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            -14.782691955566406,
            0.01446029543876648,
            1.1998517513275146
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8633159442165369,
            0.0,
            0.5046638291590843
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_640_desk_365147",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the desk that is next to the black office chair and has a printer on top?",
        "answer": "Light wood.",
        "object_id": 640,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            -10.824892044067383,
            0.01446029543876648,
            3.186305284500122
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3081400418599773,
            0.0,
            0.9513410085781708
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_556_footrest_282258",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the small object with floral patterns in front of the armchair near the sliding glass door?",
        "answer": "A footrest.",
        "object_id": 556,
        "class": "footrest",
        "position": [
            -16.3551025390625,
            0.01446029543876648,
            1.885689377784729
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2270204341531896,
            0.0,
            0.973889995059451
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_593_guitar_530627",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the guitar in the corner of the room next to the bookshelf on its stand?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 593,
        "class": "guitar",
        "position": [
            -9.05459976196289,
            0.01446029543876648,
            1.9291183948516846
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9362871358902309,
            0.0,
            0.35123553232335164
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_639_swivel_chair_785289",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the black swivel chair?",
        "answer": "The black swivel chair is in the study room, positioned between the shelving unit and the wooden desk with a printer on it.",
        "object_id": 639,
        "class": "swivel chair",
        "position": [
            -9.416147232055664,
            0.01446029543876648,
            3.0399012565612793
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.21409736134029866,
            0.0,
            0.9768123258165418
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7_647_printer_33995",
        "episode_history": "00251-wsAYBFtQaL7",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the printer that is placed on the wooden desk near the wall with a photo collage?",
        "answer": "White and black.",
        "object_id": 647,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            -8.462383270263672,
            0.01446029543876648,
            2.314577579498291
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.36685964304416213,
            0.0,
            0.9302763042803519
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00254-YMNvYDhK8mB_28_tv_120440",
        "episode_history": "00254-YMNvYDhK8mB",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object mounted on the wall in the conference room, opposite to the table with chairs?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 28,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            2.663100242614746,
            0.13135623931884766,
            -4.291357517242432
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.17282811037409196,
            0.0,
            0.9849520009952366
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00254-YMNvYDhK8mB_98_calendar_381177",
        "episode_history": "00254-YMNvYDhK8mB",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the primary color of the calendar that is hanging on the white wall above the wooden cabinet?",
        "answer": "Blue.",
        "object_id": 98,
        "class": "calendar",
        "position": [
            6.662349700927734,
            0.13135623931884766,
            -6.100722312927246
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6375262453274859,
            0.0,
            0.7704286381739961
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00254-YMNvYDhK8mB_286_copier_machine_610098",
        "episode_history": "00254-YMNvYDhK8mB",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there any paper on top of the copier machine in the office?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 286,
        "class": "copier machine",
        "position": [
            12.37492561340332,
            0.13135623931884766,
            -1.42753267288208
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9510170440094334,
            0.0,
            0.3091384511890418
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00254-YMNvYDhK8mB_289_printer_315884",
        "episode_history": "00254-YMNvYDhK8mB",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to print my documents?",
        "answer": "The printer on the desk.",
        "object_id": 289,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            11.684209823608398,
            0.13135623931884766,
            -1.5213980674743652
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9540092545962795,
            0.0,
            0.29977715414062306
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00254-YMNvYDhK8mB_374_mirror_567650",
        "episode_history": "00254-YMNvYDhK8mB",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the flower-shaped mirror in the bathroom clean?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 374,
        "class": "mirror",
        "position": [
            12.678936004638672,
            0.13135623931884766,
            0.7756020426750183
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4626310508483021,
            0.0,
            0.8865509070498974
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00255-NGyoyh91xXJ_114_oven_118618",
        "episode_history": "00255-NGyoyh91xXJ",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the oven in the kitchen closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 114,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            2.9686472415924072,
            0.09208207577466965,
            -1.7984596490859985
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8706038624573481,
            0.0,
            0.49198466914564204
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00255-NGyoyh91xXJ_141_bath_cabinet_141229",
        "episode_history": "00255-NGyoyh91xXJ",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I find a place to store my bathroom essentials?",
        "answer": "The bath cabinet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 141,
        "class": "bath cabinet",
        "position": [
            7.389801502227783,
            0.09208207577466965,
            -2.7153329849243164
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6636421893818971,
            0.0,
            0.7480501617354295
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00255-NGyoyh91xXJ_167_desk_118731",
        "episode_history": "00255-NGyoyh91xXJ",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lamp on the desk next to the bed in the bedroom turned on?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 167,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            6.317337989807129,
            0.09208207577466965,
            -2.765273094177246
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7162688598960368,
            0.0,
            0.6978244194231322
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00255-NGyoyh91xXJ_239_desk_606134",
        "episode_history": "00255-NGyoyh91xXJ",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the desk that is next to the bed with the white headboard and butterfly decorations?",
        "answer": "Yellow.",
        "object_id": 239,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            6.7827911376953125,
            0.09208207577466965,
            3.1091361045837402
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7547969864893319,
            0.0,
            0.655958466053014
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00255-NGyoyh91xXJ_494_stool_638954",
        "episode_history": "00255-NGyoyh91xXJ",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the seat of the stool that is next to the bed with multiple pillows and a bedside table with a lamp?",
        "answer": "The seat of the stool is round.",
        "object_id": 494,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            11.921915054321289,
            0.09208207577466965,
            5.280227184295654
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6163483542804783,
            0.0,
            0.7874736225269682
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00263-GGBvSFddQgs_405_oven_431489",
        "episode_history": "00263-GGBvSFddQgs",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the oven located?",
        "answer": "The oven is built into the kitchen counter, below the cabinets and next to the sink, in the kitchen area with the tiled floor and wooden cabinets.",
        "object_id": 405,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            11.810318946838379,
            0.02891707420349121,
            6.470733165740967
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8937560804231702,
            0.0,
            0.4485533064270196
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00263-GGBvSFddQgs_324_pouffe_510072",
        "episode_history": "00263-GGBvSFddQgs",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the pouffe in the living room positioned in front of the sofa?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 324,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            3.34881591796875,
            0.02891707420349121,
            7.75209903717041
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9241034170890896,
            0.0,
            0.38214247935065854
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00263-GGBvSFddQgs_331_desk_681248",
        "episode_history": "00263-GGBvSFddQgs",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wooden desk with the green windows?",
        "answer": "The wooden desk is in the room with the brick floor, positioned near the green windows and adjacent to the door.",
        "object_id": 331,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            7.471860408782959,
            0.02891707420349121,
            3.56899094581604
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5791399834089309,
            0.0,
            0.8152281150801309
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00263-GGBvSFddQgs_434_trashcan_824132",
        "episode_history": "00263-GGBvSFddQgs",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the trashcan in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A kitchen counter with a coffee maker and a kettle.",
        "object_id": 434,
        "class": "trashcan",
        "position": [
            11.898025512695312,
            0.02891707420349121,
            9.859077453613281
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6223284691665081,
            0.0,
            0.7827562049992772
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00263-GGBvSFddQgs_489_desk_chair_664619",
        "episode_history": "00263-GGBvSFddQgs",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object in front of the small wooden desk near the staircase?",
        "answer": "A desk chair.",
        "object_id": 489,
        "class": "desk chair",
        "position": [
            10.246121406555176,
            2.8289172649383545,
            4.596719264984131
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6583586082373056,
            0.0,
            0.7527044193837564
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00267-gQ3xxshDiCz_13_nightstand_469416",
        "episode_history": "00267-gQ3xxshDiCz",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there a lamp on the nightstand next to the bed in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 13,
        "class": "nightstand",
        "position": [
            -2.140261650085449,
            2.75884747505188,
            -1.856982707977295
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.1387865211557331,
            0.0,
            0.9903223220474682
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00267-gQ3xxshDiCz_259_tv_472573",
        "episode_history": "00267-gQ3xxshDiCz",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the wooden stand in the corner of the room near the window with curtains?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 259,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -0.22331847250461578,
            0.15884733200073242,
            -3.565598726272583
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4054737620035707,
            0.0,
            0.9141066832305033
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00267-gQ3xxshDiCz_268_desk_396052",
        "episode_history": "00267-gQ3xxshDiCz",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the computer monitor on the desk in the study room turned on?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 268,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            -1.4865318536758423,
            0.15884733200073242,
            -3.49090838432312
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3810470608745982,
            0.0,
            0.9245556432139875
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00267-gQ3xxshDiCz_273_monitor_509258",
        "episode_history": "00267-gQ3xxshDiCz",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the monitor on the desk?",
        "answer": "A keyboard.",
        "object_id": 273,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            -0.7053553462028503,
            0.15884733200073242,
            -4.693514823913574
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3716344680646299,
            0.0,
            0.9283791370697209
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00267-gQ3xxshDiCz_325_stove_163486",
        "episode_history": "00267-gQ3xxshDiCz",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the stove that is visible through the doorway with the damaged white door?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 325,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            -2.697695732116699,
            0.15884733200073242,
            -3.3121867179870605
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5407830902073562,
            0.0,
            0.841162082684296
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00267-gQ3xxshDiCz_341_coffee_machine_672505",
        "episode_history": "00267-gQ3xxshDiCz",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the coffee machine located?",
        "answer": "The coffee machine is on the kitchen counter, between the set of canisters and the sink, near the window.",
        "object_id": 341,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            -6.752165794372559,
            0.15884733200073242,
            -5.065391540527344
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3772433581013237,
            0.0,
            0.9261141661633497
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00267-gQ3xxshDiCz_386_backpack_482243",
        "episode_history": "00267-gQ3xxshDiCz",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to carry my books and supplies to school?",
        "answer": "The backpack hanging on the wall.",
        "object_id": 386,
        "class": "backpack",
        "position": [
            -1.1995412111282349,
            0.15884733200073242,
            -0.8367999792098999
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8904752486232712,
            0.0,
            0.45503168196217225
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo_14_bench_630767",
        "episode_history": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the wooden seating object located near the wall with circular windows on the porch?",
        "answer": "A bench.",
        "object_id": 14,
        "class": "bench",
        "position": [
            4.046041488647461,
            -0.1347745656967163,
            1.617318034172058
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.37217879851533714,
            0.0,
            0.928161053877871
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo_17_elephant_sculpture_665083",
        "episode_history": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the large gray object next to the wooden bench on the porch?",
        "answer": "An elephant sculpture.",
        "object_id": 17,
        "class": "elephant sculpture",
        "position": [
            1.4027230739593506,
            -0.1347745656967163,
            0.4064587354660034
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5787612353887538,
            0.0,
            0.815497046230876
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo_139_lounge_chair_775462",
        "episode_history": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is the object to the right of the lounge chair near the windows?",
        "answer": "A floor lamp.",
        "object_id": 139,
        "class": "lounge chair",
        "position": [
            -4.012172698974609,
            -0.5347746014595032,
            -1.2553565502166748
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9144761046789219,
            0.0,
            0.4046399065481129
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo_140_lounge_chair_250491",
        "episode_history": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object with a striped cushion next to the small table and facing the large windows in the room?",
        "answer": "A lounge chair.",
        "object_id": 140,
        "class": "lounge chair",
        "position": [
            -3.9240822792053223,
            -0.5347746014595032,
            -1.297982931137085
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7842144029807137,
            0.0,
            0.6204899436393814
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo_254_chest_of_drawers_535628",
        "episode_history": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the chest of drawers with the floral design?",
        "answer": "The chest of drawers with the floral design is in the bedroom, directly in front of the doorway, with a mirror on top and surrounded by white wooden walls.",
        "object_id": 254,
        "class": "chest of drawers",
        "position": [
            -0.6192748546600342,
            0.06522542238235474,
            -4.9012932777404785
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7702767713271672,
            0.0,
            0.6377097267203905
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo_281_folding_chair_662498",
        "episode_history": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the turquoise folding chair?",
        "answer": "The turquoise folding chair is in the corner of the room, next to the shelf with colorful towels and near the small white wicker table with a framed painting above it.",
        "object_id": 281,
        "class": "folding chair",
        "position": [
            4.357497215270996,
            0.06522542238235474,
            -2.638446807861328
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.894730439863423,
            0.0,
            0.4466065830032126
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo_333_refrigerator_502628",
        "episode_history": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the refrigerator in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A wooden cabinet.",
        "object_id": 333,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            10.832622528076172,
            0.06522542238235474,
            -1.7681324481964111
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.25771859976109845,
            0.0,
            0.9662200180793082
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo_451_refrigerator_526081",
        "episode_history": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the refrigerator located?",
        "answer": "The refrigerator is in the kitchen, positioned between the wooden cabinets and near the entrance to the hallway.",
        "object_id": 451,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            16.061920166015625,
            0.06522542238235474,
            -2.4466168880462646
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4967037907418874,
            0.0,
            0.8679201255084706
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo_371_sofa_seat_388103",
        "episode_history": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the wooden object with a cushioned seat located against the wall near the glass doors in the hallway?",
        "answer": "A sofa seat.",
        "object_id": 371,
        "class": "sofa seat",
        "position": [
            13.675687789916992,
            0.06522542238235474,
            1.3374016284942627
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2596086843215366,
            0.0,
            0.9657138970859023
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo_577_sofa_seat_848834",
        "episode_history": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly behind the sofa seat in the living room?",
        "answer": "A wooden cabinet with decorative items on top.",
        "object_id": 577,
        "class": "sofa seat",
        "position": [
            13.228997230529785,
            -0.5347746014595032,
            3.3096892833709717
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7782537277992018,
            0.0,
            0.6279499463863709
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo_450_oven_7390",
        "episode_history": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the built-in oven located?",
        "answer": "The built-in oven is in the kitchen, embedded in the wooden cabinetry next to the window and countertop.",
        "object_id": 450,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            13.328291893005371,
            0.06522542238235474,
            -2.4732391834259033
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4639142259284393,
            0.0,
            0.885880122240711
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo_452_microwave_698652",
        "episode_history": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the microwave that is placed on the countertop below the wooden cabinets with green knobs?",
        "answer": "The microwave is silver.",
        "object_id": 452,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            14.32812213897705,
            0.06522542238235474,
            -4.936483383178711
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7810304550081708,
            0.0,
            0.6244929369894665
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo_453_stove_801231",
        "episode_history": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the stove located?",
        "answer": "The stove is in the kitchen, built into the countertop between the microwave and the kettle, under the wooden cabinets.",
        "object_id": 453,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            14.470147132873535,
            0.06522542238235474,
            -5.2775654792785645
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5853822662710474,
            0.0,
            0.81075742508803
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo_456_toaster_oven_632853",
        "episode_history": "00294-PPTLa8SkUfo",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the toaster oven on the kitchen counter next to the window closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 456,
        "class": "toaster oven",
        "position": [
            14.610320091247559,
            0.06522542238235474,
            -6.00581169128418
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.43344162809651465,
            0.0,
            0.9011816437506052
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00307-vDfkYo5VqEQ_75_refrigerator_720512",
        "episode_history": "00307-vDfkYo5VqEQ",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to keep my groceries cold and fresh?",
        "answer": "The refrigerator in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 75,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            4.568361759185791,
            -3.117990493774414,
            3.2554075717926025
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9723854966822898,
            0.0,
            0.23338047442306722
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00307-vDfkYo5VqEQ_92_chair_57056",
        "episode_history": "00307-vDfkYo5VqEQ",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object positioned at the dining table in the dining area, near the sliding glass door with curtains?",
        "answer": "A chair.",
        "object_id": 92,
        "class": "chair",
        "position": [
            5.833597183227539,
            -3.117990493774414,
            6.437593460083008
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5210396477161733,
            0.0,
            0.8535324747821879
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00307-vDfkYo5VqEQ_166_desk_chair_750570",
        "episode_history": "00307-vDfkYo5VqEQ",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the desk chair in the hallway next to the desk pushed in?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 166,
        "class": "desk chair",
        "position": [
            3.526387929916382,
            0.08200955390930176,
            3.7753524780273438
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.47756292173662135,
            0.0,
            0.8785975505215011
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00307-vDfkYo5VqEQ_167_printer_361057",
        "episode_history": "00307-vDfkYo5VqEQ",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the printer located?",
        "answer": "The printer is on the desk near the top of the stairs, next to a computer monitor and a vase with dried flowers.",
        "object_id": 167,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            2.378582000732422,
            0.08200955390930176,
            3.6802520751953125
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.0002327674903537451,
            0.0,
            0.9999999729096474
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00307-vDfkYo5VqEQ_213_chest_809063",
        "episode_history": "00307-vDfkYo5VqEQ",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the small wooden chest located?",
        "answer": "The small wooden chest is placed on the floor next to the armchair and near the door in the living room.",
        "object_id": 213,
        "class": "chest",
        "position": [
            -1.9780089855194092,
            0.08200955390930176,
            3.243553400039673
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3094078731722144,
            0.0,
            0.9509294232586595
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00307-vDfkYo5VqEQ_252_toilet_13752",
        "episode_history": "00307-vDfkYo5VqEQ",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located next to the sink and under the shower curtain in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A toilet.",
        "object_id": 252,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            2.699458599090576,
            0.08200955390930176,
            4.7131667137146
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.968324984008206,
            0.0,
            0.24969326251524657
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00307-vDfkYo5VqEQ_257_bathroom_cabinet_339542",
        "episode_history": "00307-vDfkYo5VqEQ",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the wooden object with drawers and a sink on top in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A bathroom cabinet.",
        "object_id": 257,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            1.1686475276947021,
            0.08200955390930176,
            3.7573599815368652
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8705990873052262,
            0.0,
            0.4919931190406094
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00307-vDfkYo5VqEQ_264_mirror_418272",
        "episode_history": "00307-vDfkYo5VqEQ",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is reflected in the mirror above the sink in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The reflection shows the bathroom wall with decorative items and a light fixture.",
        "object_id": 264,
        "class": "mirror",
        "position": [
            1.3103361129760742,
            0.08200955390930176,
            4.021181106567383
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8333278297473065,
            0.0,
            0.5527790952710172
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00307-vDfkYo5VqEQ_351_bathtub_917493",
        "episode_history": "00307-vDfkYo5VqEQ",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bathtub in the house?",
        "answer": "The bathtub is in the bathroom, next to the window and below a shelf with a plant on it.",
        "object_id": 351,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            7.736985683441162,
            0.08200955390930176,
            3.397409439086914
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3161108766396524,
            0.0,
            0.9487222531753486
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm_7_decorative_plant_86472",
        "episode_history": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the tall object with flowers next to the radiator in the living room?",
        "answer": "A decorative plant.",
        "object_id": 7,
        "class": "decorative plant",
        "position": [
            0.6035481691360474,
            0.0024145692586898804,
            3.757185459136963
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9971508273665352,
            0.0,
            0.0754335965087375
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm_19_fireplace_495536",
        "episode_history": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the fireplace in the living room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 19,
        "class": "fireplace",
        "position": [
            1.061722993850708,
            0.09619312733411789,
            6.5476555824279785
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8710928080872776,
            0.0,
            0.49111843754701506
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm_46_tv_57882",
        "episode_history": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the low white cabinet in the corner of the living room, near the fireplace?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 46,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            1.6660127639770508,
            0.22349640727043152,
            7.934069633483887
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9045275307727159,
            0.0,
            0.42641522730105824
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm_84_display_table_769459",
        "episode_history": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the primary color of the display table that is below the sunburst mirror near the entrance door?",
        "answer": "Red.",
        "object_id": 84,
        "class": "display table",
        "position": [
            0.46597227454185486,
            0.0024145692586898804,
            2.1196255683898926
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.40786280351239973,
            0.0,
            0.9130432265292842
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm_113_bathroom_cabinet_148833",
        "episode_history": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the bathroom cabinet that is visible through the doorway next to the red vase with a sunflower?",
        "answer": "The bathroom cabinet is brown.",
        "object_id": 113,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            -3.5985662937164307,
            0.0024145692586898804,
            2.53786039352417
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.25361613606103095,
            0.0,
            0.9673049444355553
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm_180_microwave_107908",
        "episode_history": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to quickly heat up my leftovers?",
        "answer": "The microwave in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 180,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -0.9803864359855652,
            0.0024145692586898804,
            4.702351093292236
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6717462330775251,
            0.0,
            0.7407813431412507
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm_181_oven_162608",
        "episode_history": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the built-in oven located?",
        "answer": "The built-in oven is in the kitchen, installed in the cabinetry next to the refrigerator.",
        "object_id": 181,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            -0.8126804232597351,
            0.0024145692586898804,
            3.167125701904297
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8855973138624884,
            0.0,
            0.46445387034617897
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm_199_dining_table_81579",
        "episode_history": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the dining table with the vase on it?",
        "answer": "The dining table with the vase on it is in the kitchen, positioned along the wall opposite the kitchen counter and cabinets, near the sliding glass doors.",
        "object_id": 199,
        "class": "dining table",
        "position": [
            -1.9812818765640259,
            0.0024145692586898804,
            3.84614896774292
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9806837908741334,
            0.0,
            0.19559985254784765
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm_256_bouquet_447900",
        "episode_history": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are the flowers in the bouquet on the wooden dresser in the hallway fresh?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 256,
        "class": "bouquet",
        "position": [
            -4.849484920501709,
            0.20241457223892212,
            7.894595623016357
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5321716791790373,
            0.0,
            0.8466364650071267
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm_267_table_444529",
        "episode_history": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on top of the round table with a purple cloth in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "A vase with a single flower.",
        "object_id": 267,
        "class": "table",
        "position": [
            -5.900125980377197,
            0.20241457223892212,
            7.654543876647949
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9437761685331375,
            0.0,
            0.3305851534913666
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm_279_laundry_basket_349955",
        "episode_history": "00323-yHLr6bvWsVm",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located between the toilet and the shower in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A laundry basket.",
        "object_id": 279,
        "class": "laundry basket",
        "position": [
            -6.267677307128906,
            0.1113823652267456,
            5.819876670837402
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8029022805172513,
            0.0,
            0.5961106675275969
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg_1_toilet_780469",
        "episode_history": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to flush away waste?",
        "answer": "The toilet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 1,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            1.9149950742721558,
            0.08375927805900574,
            1.7175633907318115
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.33344395299658103,
            0.0,
            0.9427699243240706
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg_76_toilet_295038",
        "episode_history": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the toilet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A wall-mounted television.",
        "object_id": 76,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            2.26176118850708,
            0.08375927805900574,
            7.781338691711426
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2835688953215319,
            0.0,
            0.9589518661570695
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg_234_sink_787370",
        "episode_history": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the kitchen sink?",
        "answer": "The kitchen sink is located on the countertop near the window, between the dishwasher and the corner of the kitchen counter.",
        "object_id": 234,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            -4.963858604431152,
            0.08375927805900574,
            7.207305431365967
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.41074642958522106,
            0.0,
            0.9117496205554423
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg_4_mirror_134759",
        "episode_history": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the light around the mirror in the bathroom turned on?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 4,
        "class": "mirror",
        "position": [
            3.303056001663208,
            0.10039128363132477,
            0.6750216484069824
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4543519016754173,
            0.0,
            0.890822288362798
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg_72_mirror_309297",
        "episode_history": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to check my appearance?",
        "answer": "The mirror above the sink in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 72,
        "class": "mirror",
        "position": [
            2.47196102142334,
            0.08375927805900574,
            7.9865570068359375
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.04965105666082697,
            0.0,
            0.9987666256801252
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg_74_bath_sink_612576",
        "episode_history": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the drawer of the bath sink in the bathroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 74,
        "class": "bath sink",
        "position": [
            0.9051123857498169,
            0.08375927805900574,
            7.670591354370117
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.33438761815240264,
            0.0,
            0.9424356321926517
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg_117_bedside_lamp_552462",
        "episode_history": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly behind the bedside lamp on the nightstand?",
        "answer": "A large window with a view of city buildings.",
        "object_id": 117,
        "class": "bedside lamp",
        "position": [
            3.791780948638916,
            0.08375927805900574,
            8.894628524780273
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9951093246184217,
            0.0,
            0.09877971480758552
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg_118_bedside_lamp_543106",
        "episode_history": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to read a book at night without disturbing others?",
        "answer": "The bedside lamp on the nightstand.",
        "object_id": 118,
        "class": "bedside lamp",
        "position": [
            0.5494038462638855,
            0.08375927805900574,
            8.937009811401367
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9960890553232967,
            0.0,
            0.08835493118746456
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg_199_armchair_26457",
        "episode_history": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there a cushion on the armchair next to the large windows in the living room?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 199,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            -1.872097134590149,
            0.08375927805900574,
            7.752949237823486
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9892099187828961,
            0.0,
            0.14650507356926565
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg_222_microwave_919176",
        "episode_history": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object mounted above the countertop and below the cabinet in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A microwave.",
        "object_id": 222,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -4.577480316162109,
            0.08375927805900574,
            6.369027614593506
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.39894858841690994,
            0.0,
            0.9169732950310794
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg_225_refrigerator_628737",
        "episode_history": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the refrigerator in the kitchen area?",
        "answer": "A wooden cabinet.",
        "object_id": 225,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -0.44334760308265686,
            0.08375927805900574,
            6.223377227783203
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6702220527920899,
            0.0,
            0.7421606294806785
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg_233_worktop_772491",
        "episode_history": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the worktop that is located between the stove and the refrigerator?",
        "answer": "Marble.",
        "object_id": 233,
        "class": "worktop",
        "position": [
            -4.030227184295654,
            0.08375927805900574,
            7.049328327178955
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -7.430177053214093e-05,
            0.0,
            0.9999999972396234
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg_1_toilet_493251",
        "episode_history": "00324-DoSbsoo4EAg",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the toilet in the bathroom closed?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 1,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            1.9149950742721558,
            0.08375927805900574,
            1.7175633907318115
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.33344395299658103,
            0.0,
            0.9427699243240706
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00326-u9rPN5cHWBg_80_side_table_771571",
        "episode_history": "00326-u9rPN5cHWBg",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the side table with the plant on it?",
        "answer": "The side table with the plant on it is in the living room, next to the brown leather armchair and near the large window.",
        "object_id": 80,
        "class": "side table",
        "position": [
            -6.6724724769592285,
            0.16440987586975098,
            0.21078066527843475
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.24807745072358822,
            0.0,
            0.9687402017272153
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00326-u9rPN5cHWBg_91_coffee_table_167584",
        "episode_history": "00326-u9rPN5cHWBg",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on the coffee table in the living room?",
        "answer": "A decorative centerpiece with green foliage.",
        "object_id": 91,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            -6.892460823059082,
            0.16440987586975098,
            -1.2011387348175049
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.27441827582901174,
            0.0,
            0.9616104252196065
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00326-u9rPN5cHWBg_793_coffee_table_491191",
        "episode_history": "00326-u9rPN5cHWBg",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed between the two beds with yellow covers in the living room?",
        "answer": "A coffee table.",
        "object_id": 793,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            13.59322738647461,
            0.16440987586975098,
            0.13292889297008514
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9999755246231258,
            0.0,
            0.0069964386599524996
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00326-u9rPN5cHWBg_147_range_hood_409675",
        "episode_history": "00326-u9rPN5cHWBg",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the range hood that is above the stove and between the white cabinets in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Stainless steel.",
        "object_id": 147,
        "class": "range hood",
        "position": [
            -0.02284550666809082,
            0.16440987586975098,
            -5.997986316680908
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8186505283677066,
            0.0,
            0.5742920096982674
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00326-u9rPN5cHWBg_264_washing_machine_758963",
        "episode_history": "00326-u9rPN5cHWBg",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the washing machine in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "A shelf with a potted plant and some other items.",
        "object_id": 264,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            4.896449565887451,
            0.16440987586975098,
            -4.463098049163818
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4130507153032522,
            0.0,
            0.910708024883646
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00326-u9rPN5cHWBg_342_wall_board_352716",
        "episode_history": "00326-u9rPN5cHWBg",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is attached to the wall board that is above the brown armchair with a tufted backrest?",
        "answer": "Various papers and notes are attached to the wall board.",
        "object_id": 342,
        "class": "wall board",
        "position": [
            5.00514554977417,
            0.16440987586975098,
            -7.568110942840576
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9955738952336552,
            0.0,
            0.09398201492459556
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00326-u9rPN5cHWBg_407_bathtub_926545",
        "episode_history": "00326-u9rPN5cHWBg",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the towel draped over the bathtub that is near the windows with white shutters?",
        "answer": "Gray.",
        "object_id": 407,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            10.193414688110352,
            0.16440987586975098,
            -3.825547218322754
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.23527407160691402,
            0.0,
            0.9719290669742852
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00326-u9rPN5cHWBg_684_microwave_412388",
        "episode_history": "00326-u9rPN5cHWBg",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located directly above the microwave on the kitchen counter?",
        "answer": "A scale.",
        "object_id": 684,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            15.080633163452148,
            0.16440987586975098,
            -2.4263288974761963
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.334684488127557,
            0.0,
            0.9423302464671264
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00326-u9rPN5cHWBg_769_kitchen_table_69392",
        "episode_history": "00326-u9rPN5cHWBg",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the rug that is placed under the kitchen table with a sewing machine base?",
        "answer": "The pattern on the rug consists of geometric shapes and floral motifs in shades of blue, beige, and brown.",
        "object_id": 769,
        "class": "kitchen table",
        "position": [
            15.030357360839844,
            0.16440987586975098,
            0.7891521453857422
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.17551946229043594,
            0.0,
            0.9844759612896987
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00326-u9rPN5cHWBg_858_computer_705096",
        "episode_history": "00326-u9rPN5cHWBg",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the computer that is placed on the black desk with bookshelves above it?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 858,
        "class": "computer",
        "position": [
            0.17638441920280457,
            0.16440987586975098,
            0.05022187530994415
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8945371204925782,
            0.0,
            0.44699366892702946
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF_25_desk_159284",
        "episode_history": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the desk that is positioned near the computer and the black office chair in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 25,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            19.60616111755371,
            0.0663905143737793,
            2.4964263439178467
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6477996299061729,
            0.0,
            0.7618107635715221
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF_271_wall_clock_537509",
        "episode_history": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to check the current time?",
        "answer": "The wall clock on the wall in the dining room.",
        "object_id": 271,
        "class": "wall clock",
        "position": [
            4.017465591430664,
            0.12132030725479126,
            4.36062479019165
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.18646473314451478,
            0.0,
            0.9824616548717536
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF_42_screen_33192",
        "episode_history": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the screen on the desk in the corner of the room turned off?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 42,
        "class": "screen",
        "position": [
            21.10771369934082,
            0.06136447191238403,
            3.2980337142944336
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.40728262542953436,
            0.0,
            0.9133021750895076
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF_360_screen_497510",
        "episode_history": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the desk in front of the chair in the office room?",
        "answer": "A screen.",
        "object_id": 360,
        "class": "screen",
        "position": [
            -2.0122814178466797,
            0.06136447191238403,
            6.628573417663574
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7643523469904577,
            0.0,
            0.6447987978045392
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF_359_printer_577386",
        "episode_history": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the printer that is placed on the wooden desk next to the computer monitor?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 359,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            -2.603850841522217,
            0.06136447191238403,
            6.957708358764648
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8308666840333514,
            0.0,
            0.5564715207119076
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF_81_keyboard_629739",
        "episode_history": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the keyboard on the white desk?",
        "answer": "A computer monitor.",
        "object_id": 81,
        "class": "keyboard",
        "position": [
            21.415082931518555,
            0.24724076688289642,
            2.6934056282043457
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4680158966560055,
            0.0,
            0.883720046438506
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF_228_treadmill_704963",
        "episode_history": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the treadmill in the living room folded up?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 228,
        "class": "treadmill",
        "position": [
            9.36811351776123,
            0.06136447191238403,
            5.267743110656738
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6823432213681032,
            0.0,
            0.7310319611706452
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF_231_basket_816433",
        "episode_history": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the basket on the wooden shelf?",
        "answer": "A decorative item and some small objects.",
        "object_id": 231,
        "class": "basket",
        "position": [
            7.453405380249023,
            0.06136447191238403,
            4.610846519470215
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9422272995882796,
            0.0,
            0.33497420185825966
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF_293_sofa_chair_657422",
        "episode_history": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the brown sofa chair?",
        "answer": "The brown sofa chair is in the living room, positioned near the brick fireplace and adjacent to a wooden shelf.",
        "object_id": 293,
        "class": "sofa chair",
        "position": [
            -0.5094597935676575,
            0.06136447191238403,
            4.187098503112793
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.874880575723196,
            0.0,
            0.4843387019661438
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF_446_refrigerator_941422",
        "episode_history": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to keep my groceries fresh and cold?",
        "answer": "The refrigerator in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 446,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            0.29593557119369507,
            0.06136447191238403,
            -0.8738981485366821
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8984410699190911,
            0.0,
            0.4390941173400518
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF_447_stove_696434",
        "episode_history": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to cook my meals?",
        "answer": "The stove on the kitchen island.",
        "object_id": 447,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            0.36273735761642456,
            0.06136447191238403,
            -1.5440924167633057
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7304476316748368,
            0.0,
            0.6829687089322773
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF_489_display_table_543357",
        "episode_history": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed near the large windows in the kitchen area?",
        "answer": "A display table.",
        "object_id": 489,
        "class": "display table",
        "position": [
            0.8071656823158264,
            0.06136447191238403,
            -4.077298641204834
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7626369630130055,
            0.0,
            0.6468267640151416
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF_601_air_conditioner_157209",
        "episode_history": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the portable air conditioner located?",
        "answer": "The portable air conditioner is in the bedroom, near the sliding door with curtains, next to a small round table with a lamp on it.",
        "object_id": 601,
        "class": "air conditioner",
        "position": [
            -6.429752349853516,
            0.06136447191238403,
            -3.8410019874572754
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4880502955518457,
            0.0,
            0.872815506857982
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF_687_shower_tub_510191",
        "episode_history": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located in the corner of the bathroom with a glass door and a showerhead?",
        "answer": "A shower tub.",
        "object_id": 687,
        "class": "shower tub",
        "position": [
            -8.95627212524414,
            0.06136447191238403,
            -2.2073190212249756
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.14805850808393023,
            0.0,
            0.9889786035015928
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF_769_rocking_chair_577018",
        "episode_history": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the wooden object in the corner of the bedroom near the window?",
        "answer": "A rocking chair.",
        "object_id": 769,
        "class": "rocking chair",
        "position": [
            -8.203333854675293,
            0.06136447191238403,
            3.413236618041992
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7598972839852663,
            0.0,
            0.6500431660988488
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF_874_laundry_machine_705338",
        "episode_history": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash my clothes?",
        "answer": "The laundry machine in the laundry room.",
        "object_id": 874,
        "class": "laundry machine",
        "position": [
            -6.5674848556518555,
            0.06136447191238403,
            5.448864459991455
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9606639476216141,
            0.0,
            0.27771348498057646
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF_875_laundry_machine_479613",
        "episode_history": "00327-xgLmjqzoAzF",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the laundry machine that is placed next to the wooden cabinets in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 875,
        "class": "laundry machine",
        "position": [
            -6.597921371459961,
            -0.18756425380706787,
            8.44925594329834
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.28293255185626004,
            0.0,
            0.9591398079008632
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q_108_magazine_rack_730745",
        "episode_history": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I find some magazines to read?",
        "answer": "The magazine rack near the window.",
        "object_id": 108,
        "class": "magazine rack",
        "position": [
            -0.15428325533866882,
            0.16482782363891602,
            -1.7384943962097168
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9929326474889629,
            0.0,
            0.11867922122492933
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q_621_bowl_26827",
        "episode_history": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the bowl of fruit on the kitchen island filled with various fruits?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 621,
        "class": "bowl",
        "position": [
            -9.758273124694824,
            -3.0351719856262207,
            -4.492320537567139
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9554369815895116,
            0.0,
            0.2951951459816429
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q_226_washing_machine_60113",
        "episode_history": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the washing machine in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "A laundry basket.",
        "object_id": 226,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -7.746418476104736,
            0.16482782363891602,
            -3.40403413772583
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.1813185101839297,
            0.0,
            0.9834244240736958
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q_227_washing_machine_838799",
        "episode_history": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash my clothes?",
        "answer": "The washing machine next to the sink.",
        "object_id": 227,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -7.910287857055664,
            0.16482782363891602,
            -4.624768257141113
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.1646865224694732,
            0.0,
            0.9863459582301292
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q_337_bath_tub_719773",
        "episode_history": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located between the two vanities under the window in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A bath tub.",
        "object_id": 337,
        "class": "bath tub",
        "position": [
            -8.942974090576172,
            0.16482782363891602,
            2.1515016555786133
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9526163478217535,
            0.0,
            0.30417444643287145
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q_343_stool_207156",
        "episode_history": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the small, patterned object in front of the bathtub in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A stool.",
        "object_id": 343,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            -9.108160018920898,
            0.1882944107055664,
            3.4106369018554688
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8126595680602113,
            0.0,
            0.5827387291404191
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q_666_printer_705073",
        "episode_history": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the printer located?",
        "answer": "The printer is on the long wooden desk in the room with the bulletin board, next to the sewing machine and near the pegboard with various tools.",
        "object_id": 666,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            -12.159732818603516,
            -3.0351719856262207,
            -5.253247261047363
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9479629911866937,
            0.0,
            0.3183805385703971
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q_488_office_chair_198099",
        "episode_history": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the black office chair?",
        "answer": "The black office chair is in the study room, positioned in front of the white cabinet with glass doors and next to the large wall clock.",
        "object_id": 488,
        "class": "office chair",
        "position": [
            -0.12357261031866074,
            -3.0351719856262207,
            2.4246487617492676
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9388652142156672,
            0.0,
            0.34428492493248875
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q_597_fridge_14721",
        "episode_history": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the stainless steel fridge located?",
        "answer": "The stainless steel fridge is in the kitchen, positioned between the built-in oven and the kitchen counter with white cabinets.",
        "object_id": 597,
        "class": "fridge",
        "position": [
            -10.829676628112793,
            -3.0351719856262207,
            -3.2376885414123535
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4088270794491428,
            0.0,
            0.9126118666273655
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q_606_electric_kettle_478753",
        "episode_history": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to boil water quickly?",
        "answer": "The electric kettle on the kitchen counter.",
        "object_id": 606,
        "class": "electric kettle",
        "position": [
            -7.188447952270508,
            -3.0351719856262207,
            -4.105251789093018
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.09522645338177199,
            0.0,
            0.995455635664558
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q_607_kitchen_lower_cabinet_315382",
        "episode_history": "00386-b3WpMbPFB6q",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the kitchen lower cabinet with the drawer handles?",
        "answer": "The kitchen lower cabinet with the drawer handles is located to the left of the stove, beneath the countertop in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 607,
        "class": "kitchen lower cabinet",
        "position": [
            -9.232030868530273,
            -3.0351719856262207,
            -4.228310585021973
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8113575674407585,
            0.0,
            0.5845501670144445
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00388-pcpn6mFqFCg_606_monitor_631188",
        "episode_history": "00388-pcpn6mFqFCg",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the monitor that is on the desk with various art supplies and a lamp?",
        "answer": "Silver.",
        "object_id": 606,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            11.538731575012207,
            -2.2457385063171387,
            2.359419345855713
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9141193881425576,
            0.0,
            0.4054451186312103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00388-pcpn6mFqFCg_506_oven_379423",
        "episode_history": "00388-pcpn6mFqFCg",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to bake a cake?",
        "answer": "The oven in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 506,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            6.380550861358643,
            -2.045738458633423,
            2.193563222885132
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7504415800417654,
            0.0,
            0.660936785891373
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00388-pcpn6mFqFCg_514_microwave_523044",
        "episode_history": "00388-pcpn6mFqFCg",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The microwave is on the countertop to the right of the staircase, next to the toaster and under the wooden cabinets.",
        "object_id": 514,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            7.185797214508057,
            -2.045738458633423,
            2.0388126373291016
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6379240083562431,
            0.0,
            0.7700993179861308
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00388-pcpn6mFqFCg_518_stovetop_274170",
        "episode_history": "00388-pcpn6mFqFCg",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the burners on the stovetop that is located in the corner of the kitchen counter near the window?",
        "answer": "The burners are circular in shape.",
        "object_id": 518,
        "class": "stovetop",
        "position": [
            8.277970314025879,
            -2.045738458633423,
            1.8861103057861328
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9829563697886904,
            0.0,
            0.18383899230532613
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00388-pcpn6mFqFCg_624_jacket_465124",
        "episode_history": "00388-pcpn6mFqFCg",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the red object hanging on the shelf in the study room?",
        "answer": "A jacket.",
        "object_id": 624,
        "class": "jacket",
        "position": [
            10.985437393188477,
            -2.2457385063171387,
            3.505312442779541
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.34143841343425446,
            0.0,
            0.9399041492787971
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00388-pcpn6mFqFCg_769_coffee_table_980025",
        "episode_history": "00388-pcpn6mFqFCg",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object in front of the couch with a yellow cover in the living room?",
        "answer": "A coffee table.",
        "object_id": 769,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            0.7309187054634094,
            -2.045738458633423,
            2.8739726543426514
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.08128128480301167,
            0.0,
            0.9966912022992737
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00388-pcpn6mFqFCg_772_tv_698509",
        "episode_history": "00388-pcpn6mFqFCg",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the TV located?",
        "answer": "The TV is on a small wooden stand in the living room, between a large wooden cabinet and a bookshelf filled with various items.",
        "object_id": 772,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            2.005108594894409,
            -2.045738458633423,
            0.44514986872673035
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.739728592484386,
            0.0,
            0.6729053495559901
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00388-pcpn6mFqFCg_775_tv_stand_786596",
        "episode_history": "00388-pcpn6mFqFCg",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the TV stand in the living room?",
        "answer": "A framed poster.",
        "object_id": 775,
        "class": "tv stand",
        "position": [
            1.905166506767273,
            -2.045738458633423,
            1.815222144126892
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5381983578993773,
            0.0,
            0.8428182055190868
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00404-QN2dRqwd84J_511_tv_stand_811349",
        "episode_history": "00404-QN2dRqwd84J",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the dark wooden object below the TV in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A TV stand.",
        "object_id": 511,
        "class": "tv stand",
        "position": [
            -3.6542110443115234,
            0.1914040446281433,
            -1.4570645093917847
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.39984206069274925,
            0.0,
            0.9165840531565973
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_4_fridge_261002",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the small fridge next to the sofa in the room with the red flag closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 4,
        "class": "fridge",
        "position": [
            14.707293510437012,
            0.10536885261535645,
            -1.1856173276901245
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.29048315922396123,
            0.0,
            0.9568801044055973
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_33_flag_974101",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the flag on the wall?",
        "answer": "A tall white lamp.",
        "object_id": 33,
        "class": "flag",
        "position": [
            15.01840591430664,
            0.10536885261535645,
            0.9162730574607849
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7565803558101947,
            0.0,
            0.6539007303881219
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_13_footstool_416330",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object in the center of the living room, in front of the couches?",
        "answer": "A footstool.",
        "object_id": 13,
        "class": "footstool",
        "position": [
            13.343279838562012,
            0.10536885261535645,
            -3.163433790206909
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.987314649603929,
            0.0,
            0.1587758882118809
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_15_calendar_852097",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the calendar with the green background?",
        "answer": "The calendar with the green background is hanging on the wall in the corner of the room, above a blue chair and a small table with a Mickey Mouse design.",
        "object_id": 15,
        "class": "calendar",
        "position": [
            14.651942253112793,
            0.10536885261535645,
            0.2888734042644501
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9347636371884601,
            0.0,
            0.3552702388185662
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_34_calendar_865779",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to check the date and plan my schedule?",
        "answer": "The calendar hanging on the wall.",
        "object_id": 34,
        "class": "calendar",
        "position": [
            15.22580337524414,
            0.10536885261535645,
            0.5818324685096741
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8374829225475959,
            0.0,
            0.5464634978121935
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_125_sink_cabinet_407943",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the sink cabinet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A toilet.",
        "object_id": 125,
        "class": "sink cabinet",
        "position": [
            9.160514831542969,
            0.10536885261535645,
            -0.03349358215928078
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5798535818766621,
            0.0,
            0.8147207028085177
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_166_printer_66550",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the printer in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "A trash can.",
        "object_id": 166,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            7.153358459472656,
            0.10536885261535645,
            -0.06024252623319626
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.35143617459015586,
            0.0,
            0.9362118431153482
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_181_keyboard_987108",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the keyboard?",
        "answer": "The keyboard is on the white desk in the home office, positioned between two computer monitors and in front of a black office chair with pillows.",
        "object_id": 181,
        "class": "keyboard",
        "position": [
            6.742602348327637,
            0.10536885261535645,
            -0.1461753249168396
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8963095843918821,
            0.0,
            0.44342883186285004
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_184_monitor_836988",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the computer monitor located?",
        "answer": "The computer monitor is on a desk under the window with blinds, next to another monitor and surrounded by various wall decorations and posters.",
        "object_id": 184,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            8.647597312927246,
            0.10536885261535645,
            -0.0742761418223381
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9651303834241378,
            0.0,
            0.26176963726065894
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_195_cabinet__w_cluttered_art_780364",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the top surface of the white cabinet with various items on it in the room cluttered?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 195,
        "class": "cabinet /w cluttered art",
        "position": [
            9.012558937072754,
            0.10536885261535645,
            0.7028809785842896
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3134424960565537,
            0.0,
            0.9496071828213165
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_196_cabinet__w_cluttered_art_863401",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the top shelf of the cabinet with cluttered art in the office filled with items?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 196,
        "class": "cabinet /w cluttered art",
        "position": [
            9.021464347839355,
            0.10536885261535645,
            0.010350684635341167
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7503521672224869,
            0.0,
            0.6610382932512436
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_197_desk_653568",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the desk that is positioned below the window with two pink signs above it?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 197,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            9.5728759765625,
            0.10536885261535645,
            -0.9255514144897461
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9104560768399946,
            0.0,
            0.41360576899400947
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_323_bathtub_903857",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the bathtub in the bathroom empty?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 323,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            2.3104710578918457,
            0.10536885261535645,
            -4.644751071929932
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.39946749602534937,
            0.0,
            0.9167473586649909
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_377_dresser_237089",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the dresser with decorative items?",
        "answer": "The dresser is in the bedroom, positioned against the wall under the mounted TV, near the door and adjacent to the chair with a blue cushion.",
        "object_id": 377,
        "class": "dresser",
        "position": [
            3.9177937507629395,
            0.10536885261535645,
            -2.0572102069854736
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9072130494243145,
            0.0,
            0.4206714667697777
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_431_washer-dryer_32392",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the washer next to the dryer in the laundry room open?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 431,
        "class": "washer-dryer",
        "position": [
            6.078235626220703,
            0.10536885261535645,
            -2.2428719997406006
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3708295098707981,
            0.0,
            0.9287009608097666
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_524_sideboard_646299",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wooden sideboard with decorative items?",
        "answer": "The wooden sideboard is in the entryway, against the wall next to the staircase and beneath a mirror.",
        "object_id": 524,
        "class": "sideboard",
        "position": [
            0.7418665885925293,
            -3.0946311950683594,
            -1.1434787511825562
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9919590292989685,
            0.0,
            0.12655940973411928
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_534_blackboard_357985",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there any writing or drawing on the blackboard in the hallway near the stairs?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 534,
        "class": "blackboard",
        "position": [
            3.096994400024414,
            -3.0946311950683594,
            -0.4701004922389984
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7741946313550455,
            0.0,
            0.6329476066634783
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_564_speaker_481469",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to play music loudly in the room?",
        "answer": "The speaker on the small table.",
        "object_id": 564,
        "class": "speaker",
        "position": [
            12.48810863494873,
            -3.0946311950683594,
            -5.7629523277282715
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.10708600306130726,
            0.0,
            0.9942497613519219
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_570_fireplace_506316",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located below the TV in the living room?",
        "answer": "A fireplace.",
        "object_id": 570,
        "class": "fireplace",
        "position": [
            11.64853286743164,
            -3.0946311950683594,
            -5.596645832061768
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.43112820469851576,
            0.0,
            0.9022906799437943
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_579_footrest_855495",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the patterned footrest located?",
        "answer": "The patterned footrest is in the living room, positioned on a rug between the fireplace and the sectional sofa.",
        "object_id": 579,
        "class": "footrest",
        "position": [
            11.948984146118164,
            -3.0946311950683594,
            -6.383567810058594
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7605033644748403,
            0.0,
            0.6493339915809493
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_728_refrigerator_260766",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on top of the refrigerator in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A basket and a box.",
        "object_id": 728,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            7.428491592407227,
            -3.0946311950683594,
            -1.6991124153137207
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.990928601476645,
            0.0,
            0.134389384906478
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_729_microwave_75953",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A drawer with two towels hanging from it.",
        "object_id": 729,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            6.895548343658447,
            -3.0946311950683594,
            -1.132643699645996
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9860060538956857,
            0.0,
            0.1667095128691137
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_753_stove_366490",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the countertop surrounding the stove that is located beneath the metallic range hood?",
        "answer": "Granite.",
        "object_id": 753,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            10.267061233520508,
            -3.0946311950683594,
            0.5645655989646912
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3863110569525692,
            0.0,
            0.9223685636860077
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_771_cabinet_704830",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the bread box on top of the wooden cabinet near the entrance door closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 771,
        "class": "cabinet",
        "position": [
            4.854158401489258,
            -3.0946311950683594,
            -1.0792163610458374
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4033464467937566,
            0.0,
            0.9150473451460592
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD_774_ventilation_hood_202222",
        "episode_history": "00410-v7DzfFFEpsD",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What material is the ventilation hood that is above the kitchen island made of?",
        "answer": "Stainless steel.",
        "object_id": 774,
        "class": "ventilation hood",
        "position": [
            7.440069198608398,
            -3.0946311950683594,
            -1.2992247343063354
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.839031879330859,
            0.0,
            0.5440822598344178
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00414-77mMEyxhs44_8_hat_183457",
        "episode_history": "00414-77mMEyxhs44",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the hat leaning against the wooden dresser in the bedroom upright or fallen over?",
        "answer": "Fallen over.",
        "object_id": 8,
        "class": "hat",
        "position": [
            1.4232865571975708,
            2.560441017150879,
            -4.249507904052734
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5880276867496077,
            0.0,
            0.8088407999204202
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00414-77mMEyxhs44_19_bed_cabinet_568536",
        "episode_history": "00414-77mMEyxhs44",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the drawer of the bed cabinet next to the bed in the bedroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 19,
        "class": "bed cabinet",
        "position": [
            -0.7463371753692627,
            2.603372812271118,
            -4.197720050811768
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.00854531186620984,
            0.0,
            0.9999634881559972
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00414-77mMEyxhs44_71_music_album_shelf_439285",
        "episode_history": "00414-77mMEyxhs44",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the tall, narrow object next to the bed in the bedroom that holds multiple music albums?",
        "answer": "A music album shelf.",
        "object_id": 71,
        "class": "music album shelf",
        "position": [
            -0.0734233558177948,
            2.560441017150879,
            -1.7099580764770508
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9776689534867284,
            0.0,
            0.21015093953671748
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00414-77mMEyxhs44_216_basket_819172",
        "episode_history": "00414-77mMEyxhs44",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are the red towels in the basket next to the radiator in the bathroom neatly folded?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 216,
        "class": "basket",
        "position": [
            3.8632736206054688,
            2.560441017150879,
            -0.8428208827972412
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9812807513359211,
            0.0,
            0.1925826759020944
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00414-77mMEyxhs44_539_desk_485983",
        "episode_history": "00414-77mMEyxhs44",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the drawer of the wooden desk in the study room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 539,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            4.171293258666992,
            0.16044098138809204,
            -4.730932235717773
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3473175304144097,
            0.0,
            0.9377475849432169
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00414-77mMEyxhs44_380_wash_cabinet_405688",
        "episode_history": "00414-77mMEyxhs44",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash my hands and face?",
        "answer": "The wash cabinet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 380,
        "class": "wash cabinet",
        "position": [
            7.688179016113281,
            2.560441017150879,
            -1.2495579719543457
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9091463089859081,
            0.0,
            0.41647687673783235
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00414-77mMEyxhs44_425_pile_of_magazines_784152",
        "episode_history": "00414-77mMEyxhs44",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the pile of magazines on the woven bench near the wall?",
        "answer": "A small stack of firewood.",
        "object_id": 425,
        "class": "pile of magazines",
        "position": [
            2.3387999534606934,
            0.16044098138809204,
            -2.8871190547943115
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9986203888257112,
            0.0,
            0.05251018017080543
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00414-77mMEyxhs44_459_tv_448088",
        "episode_history": "00414-77mMEyxhs44",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the TV that is placed near the brick fireplace and below the wooden mantel?",
        "answer": "The TV is rectangular.",
        "object_id": 459,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            1.1257487535476685,
            0.16044098138809204,
            -6.628568649291992
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5319543405368641,
            0.0,
            0.846773039003953
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00414-77mMEyxhs44_750_tv_372562",
        "episode_history": "00414-77mMEyxhs44",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on top of the wooden cabinet in the living room, next to the fireplace?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 750,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            10.008781433105469,
            0.16044098138809204,
            -1.6295573711395264
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3288446505315534,
            0.0,
            0.9443840298399696
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00414-77mMEyxhs44_540_monitor_824422",
        "episode_history": "00414-77mMEyxhs44",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the computer monitor located?",
        "answer": "The computer monitor is on the wooden desk in the study room, next to the keyboard and mouse, with a chair in front of it and a framed picture hanging on the wall above.",
        "object_id": 540,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            4.058625221252441,
            0.16044098138809204,
            -7.126230239868164
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8111504509853699,
            0.0,
            0.5848375380105411
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00414-77mMEyxhs44_567_luggage_103402",
        "episode_history": "00414-77mMEyxhs44",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the brown luggage under the wooden dresser in the corner of the room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 567,
        "class": "luggage",
        "position": [
            4.836628437042236,
            0.16044098138809204,
            -7.571658134460449
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7127461511627114,
            0.0,
            0.7014220726515108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00414-77mMEyxhs44_568_luggage_120975",
        "episode_history": "00414-77mMEyxhs44",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the floor next to the wooden cabinet in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "A luggage.",
        "object_id": 568,
        "class": "luggage",
        "position": [
            4.912357330322266,
            0.16044098138809204,
            -7.524631500244141
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7458566662847533,
            0.0,
            0.666106472989562
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00414-77mMEyxhs44_572_car_model_226104",
        "episode_history": "00414-77mMEyxhs44",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the car model that is placed on the wooden cabinet below the racing-themed painting?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 572,
        "class": "car model",
        "position": [
            4.683464527130127,
            0.16044098138809204,
            -5.804148197174072
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.47859651089162986,
            0.0,
            0.8780349536108218
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00414-77mMEyxhs44_675_rocking_chair_724379",
        "episode_history": "00414-77mMEyxhs44",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the wooden object with a cushion near the large window with shutters in the dining room?",
        "answer": "A rocking chair.",
        "object_id": 675,
        "class": "rocking chair",
        "position": [
            10.152604103088379,
            0.16044098138809204,
            -7.703299522399902
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7258341848829503,
            0.0,
            0.6878697086333305
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00414-77mMEyxhs44_777_firewood_chest_984667",
        "episode_history": "00414-77mMEyxhs44",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the firewood chest located?",
        "answer": "The firewood chest is on the hearth of the brick fireplace, next to a lantern and near the TV stand in the living room.",
        "object_id": 777,
        "class": "firewood chest",
        "position": [
            8.575032234191895,
            0.16044098138809204,
            -1.6730992794036865
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.20810778339669592,
            0.0,
            0.9781058994248597
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00414-77mMEyxhs44_799_microwave_260225",
        "episode_history": "00414-77mMEyxhs44",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the microwave that is placed on the wooden countertop below the cream-colored cabinets?",
        "answer": "Silver.",
        "object_id": 799,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            1.9499726295471191,
            0.16044098138809204,
            1.0410666465759277
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.1703252993580792,
            0.0,
            0.9853878893098802
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG_132_wall_tv_789946",
        "episode_history": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wall-mounted TV located?",
        "answer": "The wall-mounted TV is in the living room, above the fireplace and next to a wooden cabinet.",
        "object_id": 132,
        "class": "wall tv",
        "position": [
            0.11805960536003113,
            0.18441589176654816,
            -2.461247682571411
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5096783283296482,
            0.0,
            0.8603650397541123
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG_442_wall_tv_614624",
        "episode_history": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the wall TV that is mounted above the bed and near the bathroom door?",
        "answer": "It is in rectangular shape.",
        "object_id": 442,
        "class": "wall tv",
        "position": [
            -3.4834988117218018,
            3.1844160556793213,
            -2.3168129920959473
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9083040325340794,
            0.0,
            0.41831063156741505
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG_133_pouffe_277533",
        "episode_history": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the pouffe next to the armchair in the living room?",
        "answer": "A floor lamp.",
        "object_id": 133,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            -3.3932690620422363,
            0.18441589176654816,
            -2.784839391708374
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5484158005272984,
            0.0,
            0.8362057819293063
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG_161_armchair_964313",
        "episode_history": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the armchair with the leopard print pillow?",
        "answer": "The armchair with the leopard print pillow is in the living room, positioned next to a small wooden dresser and under a wall-mounted lamp, near the staircase.",
        "object_id": 161,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            -1.9267735481262207,
            0.18441589176654816,
            -0.22554582357406616
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.13441444814003697,
            0.0,
            0.990925202087024
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG_170_dining_table_325403",
        "episode_history": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the table runner on the dining table that is near the white hutch and large window?",
        "answer": "Blue.",
        "object_id": 170,
        "class": "dining table",
        "position": [
            -1.7964637279510498,
            0.18441589176654816,
            -0.624292254447937
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9757845718356312,
            0.0,
            0.21873378652497752
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG_205_side_table_96896",
        "episode_history": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the side table that is placed in the corner near the window with white shutters?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 205,
        "class": "side table",
        "position": [
            2.8801658153533936,
            0.18441589176654816,
            1.0262575149536133
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8524460924731669,
            0.0,
            0.5228151293021548
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG_214_sink_402674",
        "episode_history": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the sink in the kitchen empty?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 214,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            0.7070896029472351,
            0.128665953874588,
            1.6580710411071777
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.29157937493763186,
            0.0,
            0.956546636662834
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG_216_microwave_343929",
        "episode_history": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the microwave that is installed above the stove and next to the white cabinets in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Stainless steel.",
        "object_id": 216,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            0.2917947769165039,
            0.1464393138885498,
            2.103384017944336
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.22796155844829788,
            0.0,
            0.9736701329864357
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG_243_display_cabinet_326986",
        "episode_history": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the display cabinet that is near the window with white shutters and has plants on top of it?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 243,
        "class": "display cabinet",
        "position": [
            1.4879781007766724,
            0.02784285694360733,
            1.517608404159546
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.46985719709117707,
            0.0,
            0.8827424394134581
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG_258_sink_cabinet_790567",
        "episode_history": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the sink cabinet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A large mirror with a silver frame.",
        "object_id": 258,
        "class": "sink cabinet",
        "position": [
            2.514157772064209,
            0.18441589176654816,
            -1.5967422723770142
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8506653306237241,
            0.0,
            0.5257076138642377
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG_377_printer_658845",
        "episode_history": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the printer on the wooden desk in the study room?",
        "answer": "A table lamp.",
        "object_id": 377,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            -0.03163059800863266,
            3.1844160556793213,
            -0.43820902705192566
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.941014360467615,
            0.0,
            0.338366625709046
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG_397_bathroom_towel_94729",
        "episode_history": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bathroom towel located?",
        "answer": "The bathroom towel is hanging on a ring next to the sink and under the small mirror in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 397,
        "class": "bathroom towel",
        "position": [
            1.6590280532836914,
            3.1375794410705566,
            1.8340860605239868
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8293335885886836,
            0.0,
            0.5587537908941791
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG_444_painting_frame_602108",
        "episode_history": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the painting frame in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A nightstand with a lamp on it.",
        "object_id": 444,
        "class": "painting frame",
        "position": [
            -1.6414778232574463,
            3.1844160556793213,
            -0.8101097345352173
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9498149996049904,
            0.0,
            0.3128121904999417
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG_454_bedside_lamp_417462",
        "episode_history": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the bedside lamp on the nightstand next to the bed in the bedroom turned on?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 454,
        "class": "bedside lamp",
        "position": [
            -2.306370258331299,
            3.1844160556793213,
            0.6851783990859985
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7268384054347028,
            0.0,
            0.6868085121670658
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG_455_bedside_lamp_969927",
        "episode_history": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the base of the bedside lamp that is placed on the nightstand next to the bed with a decorative headboard?",
        "answer": "The base of the bedside lamp has a floral pattern.",
        "object_id": 455,
        "class": "bedside lamp",
        "position": [
            -2.501755952835083,
            3.1844160556793213,
            -3.1239161491394043
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8697746480129072,
            0.0,
            0.49344914801225814
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG_474_nightstand_212758",
        "episode_history": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the nightstand with the lamp on it?",
        "answer": "The nightstand is in the bedroom, to the right of the bed, and has a lamp and some items on it.",
        "object_id": 474,
        "class": "nightstand",
        "position": [
            -1.721440076828003,
            3.1844160556793213,
            -3.4642176628112793
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8601875702293407,
            0.0,
            0.5099777877740783
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG_478_nightstand_890348",
        "episode_history": "00422-8wJuSPJ9FXG",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on the nightstand next to the bed in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A lamp and a phone.",
        "object_id": 478,
        "class": "nightstand",
        "position": [
            -1.5490187406539917,
            3.1844160556793213,
            0.5497512221336365
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7320561686197197,
            0.0,
            0.6812442777637231
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00440-wPLokgvCnuk_1_tv_89193",
        "episode_history": "00440-wPLokgvCnuk",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the TV mounted on the wall in the living room turned off?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 1,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -0.07327021658420563,
            0.8802165985107422,
            -0.22924205660820007
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.46487893392503643,
            0.0,
            0.8853742580359572
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00440-wPLokgvCnuk_273_tv_321786",
        "episode_history": "00440-wPLokgvCnuk",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the TV that is placed on the wooden cabinet in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 273,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -3.1013119220733643,
            -2.719783306121826,
            -1.2028924226760864
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4221960065032144,
            0.0,
            0.9065045681587809
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00440-wPLokgvCnuk_14_book_410895",
        "episode_history": "00440-wPLokgvCnuk",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the book on the round wooden coffee table in the living room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 14,
        "class": "book",
        "position": [
            0.1237904280424118,
            0.8802165985107422,
            -0.5962494015693665
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.33854732483159156,
            0.0,
            0.940949365720267
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00440-wPLokgvCnuk_15_coffee_table_523881",
        "episode_history": "00440-wPLokgvCnuk",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the round wooden object in the center of the living room between the armchair and the sofa?",
        "answer": "A coffee table.",
        "object_id": 15,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            -0.21059982478618622,
            0.8802165985107422,
            -4.384282112121582
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9789955435429141,
            0.0,
            0.2038816463615933
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00440-wPLokgvCnuk_17_armchair_764902",
        "episode_history": "00440-wPLokgvCnuk",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the armchair located?",
        "answer": "The armchair is in the living room, positioned near the large window and next to the sofa.",
        "object_id": 17,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            0.1062685176730156,
            0.8802165985107422,
            -6.0915327072143555
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9875749373902302,
            0.0,
            0.15714879267332404
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00440-wPLokgvCnuk_297_cushion_54676",
        "episode_history": "00440-wPLokgvCnuk",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the cushion on the beige sofa that is near the large abstract painting on the wall?",
        "answer": "Beige.",
        "object_id": 297,
        "class": "cushion",
        "position": [
            1.1496390104293823,
            0.8802165985107422,
            -0.3302712142467499
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5004836658688269,
            0.0,
            0.8657459790253146
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00440-wPLokgvCnuk_38_stool_965334",
        "episode_history": "00440-wPLokgvCnuk",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What are the round wooden objects with metal legs located in front of the kitchen counter?",
        "answer": "Stools.",
        "object_id": 38,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            -4.083256244659424,
            0.8802165985107422,
            -4.073208808898926
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.32286099249838024,
            0.0,
            0.9464463954831044
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00440-wPLokgvCnuk_39_stool_843582",
        "episode_history": "00440-wPLokgvCnuk",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "How many stools are placed under the kitchen counter?",
        "answer": "Two stools.",
        "object_id": 39,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            -4.005265235900879,
            0.8802165985107422,
            -3.7828736305236816
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.03585694560953166,
            0.0,
            0.9993569329581674
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00440-wPLokgvCnuk_292_nightstand_80831",
        "episode_history": "00440-wPLokgvCnuk",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the nightstand with the lamp on it?",
        "answer": "The nightstand with the lamp on it is in the bedroom, positioned next to the bed and near the sliding glass door.",
        "object_id": 292,
        "class": "nightstand",
        "position": [
            -1.9041656255722046,
            -2.719783306121826,
            -1.7566242218017578
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7115012114279128,
            0.0,
            0.7026848697222763
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00440-wPLokgvCnuk_293_nightstand_573783",
        "episode_history": "00440-wPLokgvCnuk",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the drawer of the nightstand next to the bed in the bedroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 293,
        "class": "nightstand",
        "position": [
            -1.2081453800201416,
            -2.719783306121826,
            -4.323627471923828
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7050348898069839,
            0.0,
            0.709172619433981
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00463-URjpCob8MGw_12_bench_409205",
        "episode_history": "00463-URjpCob8MGw",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the bench leaning against the wall in the basement upright?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 12,
        "class": "bench",
        "position": [
            4.977806091308594,
            0.04263806343078613,
            3.1774067878723145
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8509743794678296,
            0.0,
            0.5252072024347555
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00463-URjpCob8MGw_21_fan_908380",
        "episode_history": "00463-URjpCob8MGw",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the fan that is placed near the wooden cabinets and a heater?",
        "answer": "The fan is blue and white.",
        "object_id": 21,
        "class": "fan",
        "position": [
            6.476468086242676,
            0.04263806343078613,
            2.085918664932251
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.12874664954588783,
            0.0,
            0.9916775182642331
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00463-URjpCob8MGw_171_coffee_table_888578",
        "episode_history": "00463-URjpCob8MGw",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the small object located near the doorway and next to the wall in the room with the bunk bed?",
        "answer": "A coffee table.",
        "object_id": 171,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            -0.49743393063545227,
            0.04263806343078613,
            5.082404136657715
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.956357688758718,
            0.0,
            0.2921985132612465
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00463-URjpCob8MGw_212_bath_809380",
        "episode_history": "00463-URjpCob8MGw",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located under the window in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A bath.",
        "object_id": 212,
        "class": "bath",
        "position": [
            -1.4361761808395386,
            0.04263806343078613,
            6.16810941696167
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9929600420848642,
            0.0,
            0.11844979874540426
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00463-URjpCob8MGw_240_desk_chair_470841",
        "episode_history": "00463-URjpCob8MGw",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the desk chair with a blue backrest?",
        "answer": "The desk chair with a blue backrest is in the room with a large mirror on the wall, positioned in front of a wooden desk that has a globe on it.",
        "object_id": 240,
        "class": "desk chair",
        "position": [
            -3.5993757247924805,
            0.04263806343078613,
            6.087050437927246
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.987807136500869,
            0.0,
            0.155682565105904
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00463-URjpCob8MGw_432_towel_670732",
        "episode_history": "00463-URjpCob8MGw",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the blue towel hanging under the sink in the bathroom dry?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 432,
        "class": "towel",
        "position": [
            -3.851513624191284,
            3.0426383018493652,
            1.3485660552978516
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9384213372330836,
            0.0,
            0.3454929721798565
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00463-URjpCob8MGw_446_tv_200873",
        "episode_history": "00463-URjpCob8MGw",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the old TV located?",
        "answer": "The old TV is in the living room, placed on a small stand between the window and the armchair, near the wall with the air conditioning unit.",
        "object_id": 446,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            0.30418938398361206,
            3.0426383018493652,
            5.529507160186768
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5261313860071605,
            0.0,
            0.8504032953006381
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00463-URjpCob8MGw_520_microwave_30860",
        "episode_history": "00463-URjpCob8MGw",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the white appliance on the kitchen counter, located between the sink and the spice rack?",
        "answer": "A microwave.",
        "object_id": 520,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -2.751432180404663,
            3.0426383018493652,
            6.581342697143555
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6989702606792055,
            0.0,
            0.7151507356397276
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00466-xAHnY3QzFUN_21_armchair_56730",
        "episode_history": "00466-xAHnY3QzFUN",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object with a yellow pillow on it, located near the entrance door in the living room?",
        "answer": "An armchair.",
        "object_id": 21,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            -0.39425691962242126,
            0.05698297917842865,
            1.0335865020751953
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2364804850573991,
            0.0,
            0.9716362386135139
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00466-xAHnY3QzFUN_58_tv_234987",
        "episode_history": "00466-xAHnY3QzFUN",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the TV on the black TV stand in the living room turned off?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 58,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -2.2010586261749268,
            0.05698297917842865,
            11.174421310424805
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8094947703216361,
            0.0,
            0.5871270874537485
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00466-xAHnY3QzFUN_95_cabinet_375882",
        "episode_history": "00466-xAHnY3QzFUN",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the cabinet that is located above the kitchen counter and near the refrigerator?",
        "answer": "Brown.",
        "object_id": 95,
        "class": "cabinet",
        "position": [
            -5.956417560577393,
            0.05698297917842865,
            10.597439765930176
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.0028631714735118563,
            0.0,
            0.9999959011161562
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00466-xAHnY3QzFUN_162_wash_cabinet_267772",
        "episode_history": "00466-xAHnY3QzFUN",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the wash cabinet that is located near the hallway with the black and white abstract paintings?",
        "answer": "Dark brown.",
        "object_id": 162,
        "class": "wash cabinet",
        "position": [
            -3.5451271533966064,
            0.05698297917842865,
            2.029052734375
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8566568417538586,
            0.0,
            0.515886669217479
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00466-xAHnY3QzFUN_338_wash_cabinet_869605",
        "episode_history": "00466-xAHnY3QzFUN",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the cabinet under the sink in the bathroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 338,
        "class": "wash cabinet",
        "position": [
            2.5347187519073486,
            0.05698297917842865,
            13.536417007446289
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2501233776967033,
            0.0,
            0.9682139721825916
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00466-xAHnY3QzFUN_339_washbasin_161025",
        "episode_history": "00466-xAHnY3QzFUN",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the washbasin in the bathroom clean?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 339,
        "class": "washbasin",
        "position": [
            2.636183023452759,
            0.05698297917842865,
            12.587607383728027
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3733527155768553,
            0.0,
            0.9276894683952103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00466-xAHnY3QzFUN_172_toilet_183995",
        "episode_history": "00466-xAHnY3QzFUN",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to flush away waste?",
        "answer": "The toilet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 172,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -2.2031757831573486,
            0.05698297917842865,
            2.682281255722046
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.982806051208144,
            0.0,
            0.18464091017067313
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00466-xAHnY3QzFUN_362_toilet_843506",
        "episode_history": "00466-xAHnY3QzFUN",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to relieve myself?",
        "answer": "The toilet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 362,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            3.2074429988861084,
            0.05698297917842865,
            13.647771835327148
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7181192864206166,
            0.0,
            0.6959200316636563
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00466-xAHnY3QzFUN_301_desk_547776",
        "episode_history": "00466-xAHnY3QzFUN",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the desk that is positioned near the window and has a plant beside it?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 301,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            0.40514159202575684,
            0.05698297917842865,
            10.241048812866211
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7762184485206831,
            0.0,
            0.630464051454279
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00466-xAHnY3QzFUN_434_hat_129107",
        "episode_history": "00466-xAHnY3QzFUN",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the hat with the floral pattern?",
        "answer": "The hat with the floral pattern is hanging on a hook on the wall, next to the window in the room.",
        "object_id": 434,
        "class": "hat",
        "position": [
            3.491946220397949,
            0.05698297917842865,
            8.518157958984375
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6349362351779818,
            0.0,
            0.7725645456905271
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00475-g7hUFVNac26_101_plant_582021",
        "episode_history": "00475-g7hUFVNac26",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the plant on the desk in the hallway next to the computer healthy?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 101,
        "class": "plant",
        "position": [
            7.811091899871826,
            3.1903183460235596,
            -1.9671497344970703
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.75392884420141,
            0.0,
            0.6569560851998603
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00475-g7hUFVNac26_105_screen_184234",
        "episode_history": "00475-g7hUFVNac26",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the screen that is on the wooden desk next to the printer and a potted plant?",
        "answer": "It is rectangular.",
        "object_id": 105,
        "class": "screen",
        "position": [
            5.4727253913879395,
            3.1903183460235596,
            -3.004647970199585
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9585181987366406,
            0.0,
            0.2850313363310521
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00475-g7hUFVNac26_106_printer_670840",
        "episode_history": "00475-g7hUFVNac26",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the printer located?",
        "answer": "The printer is on the wooden desk in the room with the computer and the potted plant, near the doorway leading to another room.",
        "object_id": 106,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            5.337614059448242,
            3.1903183460235596,
            -2.886645793914795
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9743241227660432,
            0.0,
            0.22514995846364141
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00475-g7hUFVNac26_345_wall_clock_708615",
        "episode_history": "00475-g7hUFVNac26",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object hanging on the wall above the wooden chair near the window with blinds?",
        "answer": "A wall clock.",
        "object_id": 345,
        "class": "wall clock",
        "position": [
            -0.3734118342399597,
            0.1869969367980957,
            4.737384796142578
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8923705431038728,
            0.0,
            0.45130346087804296
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00475-g7hUFVNac26_383_sofa_chair_99729",
        "episode_history": "00475-g7hUFVNac26",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is mounted on the wall above the sofa chair in the living room?",
        "answer": "A deer head.",
        "object_id": 383,
        "class": "sofa chair",
        "position": [
            7.492556571960449,
            0.19031834602355957,
            3.156871795654297
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.895632463133392,
            0.0,
            0.444794886415765
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00475-g7hUFVNac26_472_calendar_209710",
        "episode_history": "00475-g7hUFVNac26",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to check the date and plan my schedule?",
        "answer": "The calendar on the wooden pillar.",
        "object_id": 472,
        "class": "calendar",
        "position": [
            0.9312160015106201,
            0.19031834602355957,
            -1.5143040418624878
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9995701185700053,
            0.0,
            0.02931856173082573
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00475-g7hUFVNac26_675_laundry_machine_904825",
        "episode_history": "00475-g7hUFVNac26",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object to the right of the cabinet and below the green laundry basket in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "A laundry machine.",
        "object_id": 675,
        "class": "laundry machine",
        "position": [
            6.020931243896484,
            0.19031834602355957,
            0.7566095590591431
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3184011598849329,
            0.0,
            0.9479560651126873
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00475-g7hUFVNac26_676_laundry_machine_715676",
        "episode_history": "00475-g7hUFVNac26",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the laundry machine located?",
        "answer": "The laundry machine is in the small room next to the wooden cabinet with cleaning supplies on top.",
        "object_id": 676,
        "class": "laundry machine",
        "position": [
            6.280645847320557,
            0.19031834602355957,
            0.6978246569633484
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.14846829135622394,
            0.0,
            0.9889171686555772
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00475-g7hUFVNac26_775_bathtub_309660",
        "episode_history": "00475-g7hUFVNac26",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the bathtub that is located between two wooden cabinets and below a window?",
        "answer": "Oval.",
        "object_id": 775,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            13.654982566833496,
            0.05183285102248192,
            -4.649722576141357
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.06997704505711831,
            0.0,
            0.99754860190623
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00475-g7hUFVNac26_1088_treadmill_118079",
        "episode_history": "00475-g7hUFVNac26",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the treadmill in the exercise room folded up?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 1088,
        "class": "treadmill",
        "position": [
            4.510852336883545,
            -2.8096816539764404,
            -4.391611576080322
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.31129577688251864,
            0.0,
            0.9503130743576609
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00475-g7hUFVNac26_1089_exercise_bike_259387",
        "episode_history": "00475-g7hUFVNac26",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the seat of the exercise bike in the basement gym adjusted to a high position?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 1089,
        "class": "exercise bike",
        "position": [
            6.896063804626465,
            -2.8096816539764404,
            -5.1898674964904785
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.38310491510154693,
            0.0,
            0.9237048359866026
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00475-g7hUFVNac26_1213_bin_950592",
        "episode_history": "00475-g7hUFVNac26",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the bin that is placed on the floor next to the white dresser with multiple drawers?",
        "answer": "Beige.",
        "object_id": 1213,
        "class": "bin",
        "position": [
            12.14605712890625,
            -2.8096816539764404,
            -2.815389633178711
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.22649450532069956,
            0.0,
            0.9740124429695606
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00475-g7hUFVNac26_1220_ladder_32734",
        "episode_history": "00475-g7hUFVNac26",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color pattern of the ladder that is leaning against the wooden bunk bed in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "The ladder has a red and orange color pattern.",
        "object_id": 1220,
        "class": "ladder",
        "position": [
            9.197489738464355,
            -2.8096816539764404,
            -3.7939045429229736
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.79676397830923,
            0.0,
            0.604290627818146
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00495-CQWES1bawee_72_recycle_bin_862666",
        "episode_history": "00495-CQWES1bawee",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the yellow recycle bin in the corner of the room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 72,
        "class": "recycle bin",
        "position": [
            5.4474968910217285,
            -3.009823799133301,
            -1.18516206741333
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.20805852059299237,
            0.0,
            0.9781163795830511
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00495-CQWES1bawee_73_recycle_bin_492910",
        "episode_history": "00495-CQWES1bawee",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the yellow recycle bin near the wall?",
        "answer": "A black trash can.",
        "object_id": 73,
        "class": "recycle bin",
        "position": [
            6.904250144958496,
            -3.009823799133301,
            -1.0787427425384521
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.11212122625415277,
            0.0,
            0.9936945358727022
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00495-CQWES1bawee_88_box_of_fruit_7301",
        "episode_history": "00495-CQWES1bawee",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I find some fresh fruit to eat?",
        "answer": "The box of fruit on the floor near the shelves.",
        "object_id": 88,
        "class": "box of fruit",
        "position": [
            2.8990306854248047,
            -3.009823799133301,
            -0.507714569568634
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4329566885490841,
            0.0,
            0.901414724663743
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00495-CQWES1bawee_256_washing_machine_451712",
        "episode_history": "00495-CQWES1bawee",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash my clothes?",
        "answer": "The washing machine in the laundry room.",
        "object_id": 256,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -0.42951998114585876,
            -3.009823799133301,
            2.849931001663208
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8254921742310688,
            0.0,
            0.5644135631638053
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00495-CQWES1bawee_1046_wall_board_138477",
        "episode_history": "00495-CQWES1bawee",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I pin up my notes and reminders?",
        "answer": "The wall board above the bed.",
        "object_id": 1046,
        "class": "wall board",
        "position": [
            -3.60426926612854,
            2.7901763916015625,
            -0.9033704996109009
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.20648616240993017,
            0.0,
            0.9784495207895091
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00506-QVAA6zecMHu_1_washer-dryer_622124",
        "episode_history": "00506-QVAA6zecMHu",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash and dry my clothes?",
        "answer": "The washer-dryer in the laundry area.",
        "object_id": 1,
        "class": "washer-dryer",
        "position": [
            1.6032217741012573,
            0.03892159461975098,
            5.181547164916992
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9060512332735718,
            0.0,
            0.42316800763224
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00506-QVAA6zecMHu_2_washer-dryer_317462",
        "episode_history": "00506-QVAA6zecMHu",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the washer-dryer that is located in the small room with exposed brick walls and a white door?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 2,
        "class": "washer-dryer",
        "position": [
            0.6838287711143494,
            0.03892159461975098,
            6.1044440269470215
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6730274618494401,
            0.0,
            0.7396174927599404
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00506-QVAA6zecMHu_67_tv_417189",
        "episode_history": "00506-QVAA6zecMHu",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the TV located?",
        "answer": "The TV is in the living room, mounted on the wall above a decorative console table, opposite the beige sofa and near the sliding glass door that leads outside.",
        "object_id": 67,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            1.3239446878433228,
            0.03892159461975098,
            0.9072006344795227
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9213123685901284,
            0.0,
            0.3888232496685961
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00506-QVAA6zecMHu_160_refrigerator_964315",
        "episode_history": "00506-QVAA6zecMHu",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to keep my groceries cold and fresh?",
        "answer": "The refrigerator in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 160,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            2.3376684188842773,
            0.03892159461975098,
            -1.5885510444641113
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.30425405714736853,
            0.0,
            0.952590924116625
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00506-QVAA6zecMHu_230_sink_20778",
        "episode_history": "00506-QVAA6zecMHu",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the sink with the marble countertop?",
        "answer": "The sink with the marble countertop is in the bathroom, next to the toilet and near the entrance door.",
        "object_id": 230,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            5.871773719787598,
            0.03892159461975098,
            -1.2429307699203491
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8999923875134063,
            0.0,
            0.4359056118220073
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00506-QVAA6zecMHu_188_microwave_46269",
        "episode_history": "00506-QVAA6zecMHu",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to quickly heat up my leftovers?",
        "answer": "The microwave on the wooden cabinet.",
        "object_id": 188,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            1.7842683792114258,
            0.03892159461975098,
            -0.8342246413230896
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5271065718911102,
            0.0,
            0.8497991891436482
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00506-QVAA6zecMHu_226_toilet_806156",
        "episode_history": "00506-QVAA6zecMHu",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the toilet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The toilet is located next to the bathtub and across from the sink with a granite countertop in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 226,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            3.9726414680480957,
            0.03892159461975098,
            -1.1650103330612183
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8314903789847818,
            0.0,
            0.5555391522257849
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00506-QVAA6zecMHu_227_bathtub_858507",
        "episode_history": "00506-QVAA6zecMHu",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color pattern of the shower curtain next to the bathtub in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The shower curtain has a blue and white pattern with floral and abstract designs.",
        "object_id": 227,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            4.037871360778809,
            0.03892159461975098,
            -0.7919073700904846
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6957033345571059,
            0.0,
            0.7183292213784175
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00508-4vwGX7U38Ux_26_desk_37278",
        "episode_history": "00508-4vwGX7U38Ux",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the desk that is positioned below the window with red blinds?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 26,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            3.2671408653259277,
            0.13024532794952393,
            -0.06155283749103546
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5377030253384927,
            0.0,
            0.8431343051624886
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00508-4vwGX7U38Ux_185_window_curtain_651804",
        "episode_history": "00508-4vwGX7U38Ux",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the window curtain in the bedroom drawn open?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 185,
        "class": "window curtain",
        "position": [
            3.1792080402374268,
            0.13024532794952393,
            5.522079944610596
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7351201140174654,
            0.0,
            0.677936883468475
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00508-4vwGX7U38Ux_270_toilet_749925",
        "episode_history": "00508-4vwGX7U38Ux",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the toilet in the bathroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 270,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            1.8243769407272339,
            0.13024532794952393,
            6.418831825256348
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9959809084976033,
            0.0,
            0.08956578536634886
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00508-4vwGX7U38Ux_257_mirror_943969",
        "episode_history": "00508-4vwGX7U38Ux",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object above the sink in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A mirror.",
        "object_id": 257,
        "class": "mirror",
        "position": [
            1.7237837314605713,
            0.13024532794952393,
            6.781177997589111
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6785007844117603,
            0.0,
            0.7345996770708696
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00508-4vwGX7U38Ux_330_speaker_861243",
        "episode_history": "00508-4vwGX7U38Ux",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the black speaker on the floor next to the wooden cabinet in the living room upright?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 330,
        "class": "speaker",
        "position": [
            -2.0325701236724854,
            0.13024532794952393,
            3.3951737880706787
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9408684775874286,
            0.0,
            0.33877205888667117
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00508-4vwGX7U38Ux_361_armchair_383869",
        "episode_history": "00508-4vwGX7U38Ux",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on the side table next to the armchair in the living room?",
        "answer": "A stack of books and some papers.",
        "object_id": 361,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            -1.6001299619674683,
            0.13024532794952393,
            7.451808929443359
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3669918711205735,
            0.0,
            0.9302241485423931
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00508-4vwGX7U38Ux_398_stove_435852",
        "episode_history": "00508-4vwGX7U38Ux",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located in the center of the kitchen cabinets, directly below the microwave?",
        "answer": "A stove.",
        "object_id": 398,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            -1.9282357692718506,
            0.13024532794952393,
            -1.8652067184448242
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7623299939955935,
            0.0,
            0.647188519872439
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs_46_pouffe_889246",
        "episode_history": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the dark pouffe in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "The dark pouffe is in the bedroom, placed against the wall between the two windows and near the nightstand with a lamp.",
        "object_id": 46,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            1.0732693672180176,
            0.19266152381896973,
            0.09951970726251602
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3281264373608341,
            0.0,
            0.944633813233936
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs_493_pouffe_309758",
        "episode_history": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the pouffe near the fireplace?",
        "answer": "A side table with a lamp on it.",
        "object_id": 493,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            -1.0911482572555542,
            -3.007338523864746,
            0.7080509662628174
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.46578306311865336,
            0.0,
            0.8848989423159034
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs_77_bathtub_900838",
        "episode_history": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to take a relaxing bath?",
        "answer": "The bathtub next to the window.",
        "object_id": 77,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            1.891370177268982,
            0.19266152381896973,
            -1.1253340244293213
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6688477847074641,
            0.0,
            0.7433993818210489
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs_323_monitor_7103",
        "episode_history": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the monitor on the desk in the home office turned on?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 323,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            8.386622428894043,
            0.19266152381896973,
            6.398955345153809
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8770534984322704,
            0.0,
            0.4803927152733638
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs_324_monitor_460034",
        "episode_history": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the computer monitor located?",
        "answer": "The computer monitor is on the black desk in the corner of the room, next to the window with blinds and above the keyboard.",
        "object_id": 324,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            8.40123462677002,
            0.19266152381896973,
            6.327495574951172
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8274661071191786,
            0.0,
            0.5615156645802787
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs_325_desk_28120",
        "episode_history": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the desk that is positioned near the window with white curtains and a lamp with a paisley-patterned shade?",
        "answer": "The desk is dark gray.",
        "object_id": 325,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            9.10942554473877,
            0.19266152381896973,
            5.787478446960449
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.889344912671256,
            0.0,
            0.45723694766035244
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs_330_printer_240640",
        "episode_history": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the printer located?",
        "answer": "The printer is on top of a black desk with white drawers, near the open door in the room.",
        "object_id": 330,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            8.125636100769043,
            0.19266152381896973,
            6.9857497215271
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4684526754503147,
            0.0,
            0.8834885912469057
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs_375_washing_machine_1346",
        "episode_history": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the washing machine that is placed next to the dryer in the laundry closet near the staircase?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 375,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            1.1108099222183228,
            0.19266152381896973,
            2.2411282062530518
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9995881815244078,
            0.0,
            0.028696120934762648
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs_412_dresser_338104",
        "episode_history": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I store my clothes neatly?",
        "answer": "The dresser under the window.",
        "object_id": 412,
        "class": "dresser",
        "position": [
            -1.8009049892425537,
            0.19266152381896973,
            5.354413986206055
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.99517202410175,
            0.0,
            0.09814602613059839
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs_450_wall_clock_696323",
        "episode_history": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the large wall clock with a black frame?",
        "answer": "The large wall clock with a black frame is hanging on the wall above the television in the living room, between two windows with white blinds.",
        "object_id": 450,
        "class": "wall clock",
        "position": [
            0.20496395230293274,
            -3.007338523864746,
            -0.7718892693519592
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8098062746845307,
            0.0,
            0.586697364474703
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs_455_fireplace_812222",
        "episode_history": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to warm up the living room?",
        "answer": "The fireplace.",
        "object_id": 455,
        "class": "fireplace",
        "position": [
            2.169985294342041,
            -3.007338523864746,
            -0.10177046805620193
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.39672289534268,
            0.0,
            0.9179384207619381
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs_531_microwave_626955",
        "episode_history": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Decorative items, including a large plate and a glass container.",
        "object_id": 531,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            5.94511079788208,
            -3.007338523864746,
            2.9409940242767334
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.15892220362699364,
            0.0,
            0.9872911086373362
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs_554_coffee_machine_314422",
        "episode_history": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the coffee machine located?",
        "answer": "The coffee machine is on the kitchen counter, in the corner between the stove and the white cabinets.",
        "object_id": 554,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            5.333292484283447,
            -3.007338523864746,
            1.89485502243042
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.34893017008897237,
            0.0,
            0.9371487269380889
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs_574_refrigerator_47283",
        "episode_history": "00525-iKFn6fzyRqs",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the stainless steel refrigerator?",
        "answer": "The stainless steel refrigerator is in the kitchen, positioned between two sets of white cabinets and near the doorway leading to the dining area.",
        "object_id": 574,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            3.933028221130371,
            -3.007338523864746,
            0.9056640863418579
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9754733455191762,
            0.0,
            0.2201175871701893
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00529-W9YAR9qcuvN_95_dresser_388226",
        "episode_history": "00529-W9YAR9qcuvN",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the wooden object with drawers near the window in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A dresser.",
        "object_id": 95,
        "class": "dresser",
        "position": [
            5.965760231018066,
            0.0479886531829834,
            3.290619373321533
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3273018093000906,
            0.0,
            0.9449198514312667
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00529-W9YAR9qcuvN_96_tv_723018",
        "episode_history": "00529-W9YAR9qcuvN",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the TV that is placed on top of the wooden dresser near the window?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 96,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            6.497438907623291,
            0.0479886531829834,
            1.6716759204864502
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5206434850623424,
            0.0,
            0.8537741864580696
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00529-W9YAR9qcuvN_250_microwave_230756",
        "episode_history": "00529-W9YAR9qcuvN",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The stove.",
        "object_id": 250,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            4.4864630699157715,
            -2.9520113468170166,
            2.4491868019104004
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9956091413997066,
            0.0,
            0.09360789262313529
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00529-W9YAR9qcuvN_255_refrigerator_95940",
        "episode_history": "00529-W9YAR9qcuvN",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the stainless steel refrigerator located?",
        "answer": "The stainless steel refrigerator is in the kitchen, positioned between the white cabinets and across from the kitchen island with a marble countertop.",
        "object_id": 255,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            2.6559791564941406,
            -2.9520113468170166,
            1.0718300342559814
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8267345214398526,
            0.0,
            0.5625922422675395
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00537-oahi4u45xMf_76_refrigerator_693821",
        "episode_history": "00537-oahi4u45xMf",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to keep my groceries fresh and cold?",
        "answer": "The refrigerator next to the blue recycling bin.",
        "object_id": 76,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -4.534994602203369,
            0.11611390113830566,
            -0.9546734094619751
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6406599514670135,
            0.0,
            0.7678247368939632
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00537-oahi4u45xMf_83_microwave_596706",
        "episode_history": "00537-oahi4u45xMf",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to quickly heat up my leftovers?",
        "answer": "The microwave on the kitchen counter.",
        "object_id": 83,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -3.997344732284546,
            0.11611390113830566,
            -1.0867125988006592
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9878455128198912,
            0.0,
            0.15543887159139147
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00537-oahi4u45xMf_107_trashcan_884362",
        "episode_history": "00537-oahi4u45xMf",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the blue recycling bin next to the refrigerator in the hallway empty?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 107,
        "class": "trashcan",
        "position": [
            -5.045466423034668,
            0.11611390113830566,
            -0.9397282600402832
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7111955234202438,
            0.0,
            0.7029942584879378
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00537-oahi4u45xMf_109_calendar_911077",
        "episode_history": "00537-oahi4u45xMf",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the calendar on the wall next to the refrigerator in the kitchen displaying the current month?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 109,
        "class": "calendar",
        "position": [
            -6.148531436920166,
            0.11611390113830566,
            -0.6718682050704956
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.23672973882959,
            0.0,
            0.9715755404257942
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00537-oahi4u45xMf_202_display_cabinet_424030",
        "episode_history": "00537-oahi4u45xMf",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the display cabinet in the living room?",
        "answer": "A sofa.",
        "object_id": 202,
        "class": "display cabinet",
        "position": [
            2.4737110137939453,
            0.11611390113830566,
            3.2685742378234863
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9327347406358648,
            0.0,
            0.36056331428883087
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00537-oahi4u45xMf_218_mirror_176228",
        "episode_history": "00537-oahi4u45xMf",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the mirror on the wall near the staircase?",
        "answer": "A small wooden ledge.",
        "object_id": 218,
        "class": "mirror",
        "position": [
            2.7690930366516113,
            0.11611390113830566,
            1.0444964170455933
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3336432223942447,
            0.0,
            0.942699421952928
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00537-oahi4u45xMf_296_dresser_23981",
        "episode_history": "00537-oahi4u45xMf",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the top drawer of the white dresser in the bedroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 296,
        "class": "dresser",
        "position": [
            1.7974631786346436,
            2.916114091873169,
            3.9331815242767334
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8411598551364866,
            0.0,
            0.5407865550351312
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00537-oahi4u45xMf_314_air_conditioning_682682",
        "episode_history": "00537-oahi4u45xMf",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the air conditioning unit located?",
        "answer": "The air conditioning unit is installed in the window between the bed and the floral-patterned chair in the bedroom.",
        "object_id": 314,
        "class": "air conditioning",
        "position": [
            -0.9467712640762329,
            2.916114091873169,
            3.389183521270752
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7349827071539579,
            0.0,
            0.6780858501581045
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00537-oahi4u45xMf_345_toilet_970814",
        "episode_history": "00537-oahi4u45xMf",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the toilet in the bathroom closed?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 345,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -0.4999104142189026,
            2.916114091873169,
            1.2187352180480957
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5927868355292742,
            0.0,
            0.8053594027657398
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00537-oahi4u45xMf_349_bathroom_cabinet_898464",
        "episode_history": "00537-oahi4u45xMf",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bathroom cabinet located?",
        "answer": "The bathroom cabinet is in the bathroom, to the left of the sink and under the mirror, near the window.",
        "object_id": 349,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            0.4270917475223541,
            3.031341314315796,
            1.0337187051773071
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7573886157115833,
            0.0,
            0.6529643824823002
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW_56_bathroom_towel_957428",
        "episode_history": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to dry my hands after washing them?",
        "answer": "The bathroom towel hanging on the wall.",
        "object_id": 56,
        "class": "bathroom towel",
        "position": [
            -12.638531684875488,
            -2.9073855876922607,
            8.489974975585938
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8777720763751027,
            0.0,
            0.47907847158491773
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW_155_pouffe_225399",
        "episode_history": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the pouffe under the wooden coffee table in the living room properly aligned?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 155,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            -14.854640007019043,
            -2.9073855876922607,
            -0.3897078037261963
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8866294235707348,
            0.0,
            0.4624805566276561
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW_118_workout_bike_201508",
        "episode_history": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the seat of the workout bike in the exercise area adjusted to a high position?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 118,
        "class": "workout bike",
        "position": [
            -15.626856803894043,
            -2.9073855876922607,
            3.9180898666381836
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9999992817618463,
            0.0,
            0.0011985147666298448
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW_1287_desk_chair_855906",
        "episode_history": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the design style of the desk chair that is placed next to the wooden nightstand with a lamp on it?",
        "answer": "The design style of the desk chair is ornate and carved, featuring intricate wooden details.",
        "object_id": 1287,
        "class": "desk chair",
        "position": [
            -4.858175277709961,
            0.09261441230773926,
            1.2880644798278809
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7227219372173938,
            0.0,
            0.6911389161845377
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW_132_monitor_200117",
        "episode_history": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the monitor that is on the desk near the staircase?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 132,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            -13.305342674255371,
            -2.9073855876922607,
            5.588474273681641
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8253428054346855,
            0.0,
            0.5646319628901669
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW_174_folding_chair_590349",
        "episode_history": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object leaning against the wall to the left of the bar stools in the room?",
        "answer": "A folding chair.",
        "object_id": 174,
        "class": "folding chair",
        "position": [
            -8.965312004089355,
            -2.9073855876922607,
            1.2093619108200073
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3301639309363153,
            0.0,
            0.9439236085132525
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW_821_newspaper_802798",
        "episode_history": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the newspaper on the wooden coffee table in the living room open or folded?",
        "answer": "Folded.",
        "object_id": 821,
        "class": "newspaper",
        "position": [
            -12.744667053222656,
            0.09261441230773926,
            4.272913932800293
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9086677818805328,
            0.0,
            0.41751989434314724
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW_855_refrigerator_514333",
        "episode_history": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the refrigerator in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A built-in oven and microwave unit.",
        "object_id": 855,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -14.33266830444336,
            0.09261441230773926,
            -0.32622677087783813
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8962666336252946,
            0.0,
            0.44351563833757
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW_876_coffee_machine_798384",
        "episode_history": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to make a cup of coffee in the morning?",
        "answer": "The coffee machine on the kitchen counter.",
        "object_id": 876,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            -15.71495532989502,
            0.09261441230773926,
            0.1105772852897644
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2465525844447451,
            0.0,
            0.969129415044047
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW_883_stove_880441",
        "episode_history": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to cook my food?",
        "answer": "The stove on the kitchen counter.",
        "object_id": 883,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            -12.831979751586914,
            0.09261441230773926,
            -0.1127699464559555
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5143708477093225,
            0.0,
            0.8575678579720634
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW_1076_storage_bin_832104",
        "episode_history": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to store my dirty laundry?",
        "answer": "The storage bin in the closet.",
        "object_id": 1076,
        "class": "storage bin",
        "position": [
            -8.577362060546875,
            0.09261441230773926,
            8.242986679077148
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6624252737665384,
            0.0,
            0.7491279975246732
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW_1077_storage_bin_557753",
        "episode_history": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the gray storage bin under the hanging clothes in the closet closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 1077,
        "class": "storage bin",
        "position": [
            -6.904768943786621,
            0.09261441230773926,
            9.434200286865234
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2634404127880176,
            0.0,
            0.9646756703214189
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW_1142_clock_305230",
        "episode_history": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object mounted on the wall at the corner of the hallway?",
        "answer": "A clock.",
        "object_id": 1142,
        "class": "clock",
        "position": [
            -9.274030685424805,
            0.09261441230773926,
            2.860893726348877
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6585305540970277,
            0.0,
            0.7525539909672008
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW_1154_piano_996195",
        "episode_history": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed against the wall near the staircase in the hallway?",
        "answer": "A piano.",
        "object_id": 1154,
        "class": "piano",
        "position": [
            -10.825966835021973,
            0.09261441230773926,
            2.064502477645874
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9431232631590142,
            0.0,
            0.3324432440106028
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW_1225_washing_machine_634380",
        "episode_history": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the washing machine in the laundry room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 1225,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -7.455597400665283,
            0.09261441230773926,
            4.726743698120117
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9104827067898993,
            0.0,
            0.4135471443941287
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW_1228_washing_machine_776763",
        "episode_history": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the washing machine located?",
        "answer": "The washing machine is in the laundry room, directly ahead as you enter through the doorway from the hallway with wooden flooring. It is positioned against the back wall, beneath a wire shelf.",
        "object_id": 1228,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -6.644321441650391,
            0.09261441230773926,
            5.496087074279785
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7339439314085958,
            0.0,
            0.6792100599582535
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW_1313_file_cabinet_891221",
        "episode_history": "00538-3CBBjsNkhqW",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the file cabinet that is placed between the black office chair and the brown leather armchair?",
        "answer": "Dark brown.",
        "object_id": 1313,
        "class": "file cabinet",
        "position": [
            -1.17887544631958,
            0.09261441230773926,
            0.46868011355400085
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9304740985928169,
            0.0,
            0.36635768293825177
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh_106_electric_box_922364",
        "episode_history": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the electric box located in the basement?",
        "answer": "The electric box is mounted on the wall in the basement, above a television and next to some stacked boards and a red air compressor.",
        "object_id": 106,
        "class": "electric box",
        "position": [
            -3.6323699951171875,
            -2.5538082122802734,
            -2.0791687965393066
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.17002220721206143,
            0.0,
            0.9854402310920428
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh_111_tv_stand_906163",
        "episode_history": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the TV stand in the basement cluttered with items?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 111,
        "class": "tv stand",
        "position": [
            -6.328402519226074,
            -2.512690782546997,
            -1.8830764293670654
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.46572356168943124,
            0.0,
            0.8849302594483424
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh_660_tv_stand_439484",
        "episode_history": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are there any blankets on the TV stand in the living room?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 660,
        "class": "tv stand",
        "position": [
            -4.2033233642578125,
            0.04619193077087402,
            2.34212589263916
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.641276780462141,
            0.0,
            0.7673096446937905
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh_178_water_tank_312550",
        "episode_history": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to store and heat water for the house?",
        "answer": "The water tank in the basement.",
        "object_id": 178,
        "class": "water tank",
        "position": [
            -4.925973415374756,
            -2.5538082122802734,
            1.5933274030685425
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8283183698597569,
            0.0,
            0.560257689061806
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh_209_cat_food_bag_268202",
        "episode_history": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located on the floor next to the wooden beams and under the shelf in the storage room?",
        "answer": "A cat food bag.",
        "object_id": 209,
        "class": "cat food bag",
        "position": [
            -6.411449909210205,
            -2.5538082122802734,
            0.18307609856128693
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7592594970205663,
            0.0,
            0.6507879963429539
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh_331_toilet_818935",
        "episode_history": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly to the right of the toilet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A sink with a vanity and a roll of toilet paper on top.",
        "object_id": 331,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            0.0010729208588600159,
            -2.5538082122802734,
            0.47280633449554443
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9325492258185646,
            0.0,
            0.3610428526161347
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh_467_microwave_845667",
        "episode_history": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the microwave on the kitchen counter?",
        "answer": "A collection of jars and containers.",
        "object_id": 467,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -3.578869342803955,
            0.04619193077087402,
            -2.5388855934143066
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9006636796994038,
            0.0,
            0.43451689963720636
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh_540_ball_chair_871917",
        "episode_history": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the ball chair located?",
        "answer": "The ball chair is next to the small desk with a computer on it, near the railing and the wall with mounted animal heads.",
        "object_id": 540,
        "class": "ball chair",
        "position": [
            -5.411048412322998,
            0.08500374853610992,
            -3.5428218841552734
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9039809952126006,
            0.0,
            0.42757263744823054
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh_541_desk_153000",
        "episode_history": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the exercise ball under the desk in the room next to the staircase properly inflated?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 541,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            -6.356907844543457,
            0.04619193077087402,
            -3.538148880004883
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9682214063436956,
            0.0,
            0.2500945986978466
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh_561_coat_509483",
        "episode_history": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the coat hanging near the staircase?",
        "answer": "A wall-mounted decorative piece.",
        "object_id": 561,
        "class": "coat",
        "position": [
            -6.4114670753479,
            0.04619193077087402,
            0.8166363835334778
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5532563090820839,
            0.0,
            0.8330110782341791
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh_562_coat_695301",
        "episode_history": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the yellow coat?",
        "answer": "The yellow coat is hanging on the wall near the staircase, next to the door with the light switches.",
        "object_id": 562,
        "class": "coat",
        "position": [
            -7.3380608558654785,
            0.04619193077087402,
            0.6485574841499329
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3941202427573037,
            0.0,
            0.9190588850824108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh_642_laptop_880067",
        "episode_history": "00541-FnDDfrBZPhh",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the laptop in the living room?",
        "answer": "The laptop is on the wooden coffee table between the two sofas in the living room.",
        "object_id": 642,
        "class": "laptop",
        "position": [
            -4.217972278594971,
            0.04619193077087402,
            2.0898990631103516
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.33893410810885943,
            0.0,
            0.9408101138701964
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00546-nS8T59Aw3sf_118_stuffed_animal_786631",
        "episode_history": "00546-nS8T59Aw3sf",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the stuffed animal with a blue hat?",
        "answer": "The stuffed animal with a blue hat is on the bed in the bedroom, near the pillows and next to the window.",
        "object_id": 118,
        "class": "stuffed animal",
        "position": [
            2.743030071258545,
            0.15547633171081543,
            -3.057874917984009
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8914505425623827,
            0.0,
            0.4531180090939154
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00546-nS8T59Aw3sf_128_desk_907947",
        "episode_history": "00546-nS8T59Aw3sf",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located in front of the window and next to the bed in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A desk.",
        "object_id": 128,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            1.4481346607208252,
            0.15547633171081543,
            -4.089221000671387
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9652768747220958,
            0.0,
            0.2612289324074627
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00546-nS8T59Aw3sf_223_desk_576697",
        "episode_history": "00546-nS8T59Aw3sf",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located against the wall with a whiteboard above it and a chair in front of it in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A desk.",
        "object_id": 223,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            3.580676555633545,
            0.15547633171081543,
            -2.168247699737549
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.0326997717898115,
            0.0,
            0.999465219467338
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00546-nS8T59Aw3sf_140_gramophone_533385",
        "episode_history": "00546-nS8T59Aw3sf",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on top of the white dresser next to the gramophone in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A lamp with a pink shade, a decorative box, and a small jar.",
        "object_id": 140,
        "class": "gramophone",
        "position": [
            -0.3189210891723633,
            0.15547633171081543,
            -3.4588170051574707
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.35745145469811035,
            0.0,
            0.9339317199529121
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00546-nS8T59Aw3sf_441_dining_table_684836",
        "episode_history": "00546-nS8T59Aw3sf",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the dining table with the blue tablecloth?",
        "answer": "The dining table with the blue tablecloth is in the dining room, positioned centrally between the wooden hutch filled with dishes and the fireplace. It is surrounded by wooden chairs and has a vase of flowers on top.",
        "object_id": 441,
        "class": "dining table",
        "position": [
            8.107782363891602,
            -2.8445236682891846,
            -2.770932912826538
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7440186685568208,
            0.0,
            0.6681588290510989
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00546-nS8T59Aw3sf_493_cutting_board_738795",
        "episode_history": "00546-nS8T59Aw3sf",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the wooden object placed against the backsplash behind the stove in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A cutting board.",
        "object_id": 493,
        "class": "cutting board",
        "position": [
            8.339822769165039,
            -2.8445236682891846,
            -0.239921435713768
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9466347741073959,
            0.0,
            0.3223082444658207
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00560-gjhYih4upQ9_12_printer_705611",
        "episode_history": "00560-gjhYih4upQ9",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to print my documents?",
        "answer": "The printer on the wooden cabinet.",
        "object_id": 12,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            -3.214282989501953,
            0.09558707475662231,
            1.5819371938705444
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.25146515412356335,
            0.0,
            0.9678663524793144
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00560-gjhYih4upQ9_138_microwave_424562",
        "episode_history": "00560-gjhYih4upQ9",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to quickly heat up my leftovers?",
        "answer": "The microwave above the stove.",
        "object_id": 138,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            8.296056747436523,
            0.028740406036376953,
            -2.6165924072265625
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.12491985589337358,
            0.0,
            0.9921668355692902
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00560-gjhYih4upQ9_143_coffee_machine_102763",
        "episode_history": "00560-gjhYih4upQ9",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located to the left of the coffee machine on the kitchen counter?",
        "answer": "A microwave oven.",
        "object_id": 143,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            8.59488582611084,
            0.028740406036376953,
            -3.6877622604370117
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3153647066603096,
            0.0,
            0.9489705484329094
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00560-gjhYih4upQ9_234_washing_machine_147990",
        "episode_history": "00560-gjhYih4upQ9",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the washing machine in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "A utility sink.",
        "object_id": 234,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            4.354423522949219,
            -2.3712596893310547,
            0.2940210998058319
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9936209581285755,
            0.0,
            0.1127714129008483
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h_27_table_491405",
        "episode_history": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the tablecloth on the table that is surrounded by four wooden chairs in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 27,
        "class": "table",
        "position": [
            -5.155891418457031,
            0.02857268787920475,
            -4.76319694519043
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8900428295700095,
            0.0,
            0.4558769148915208
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h_44_microwave_757000",
        "episode_history": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to quickly heat up my leftovers?",
        "answer": "The microwave above the stove.",
        "object_id": 44,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -4.045215129852295,
            0.010577410459518433,
            -3.2256762981414795
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9977724168677901,
            0.0,
            0.0667098503805956
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h_47_refrigerator_588602",
        "episode_history": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the white refrigerator located?",
        "answer": "The white refrigerator is in the kitchen, positioned between the dark wooden cabinets and next to the dining table with wooden chairs.",
        "object_id": 47,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -3.3413846492767334,
            0.010577410459518433,
            -1.7045314311981201
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5211664129594878,
            0.0,
            0.8534550779056509
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h_66_washing_machine_259285",
        "episode_history": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the washing machine located?",
        "answer": "The washing machine is in the laundry room, next to the dryer and near the wooden door with a window.",
        "object_id": 66,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            1.2334095239639282,
            0.010577410459518433,
            -4.687402725219727
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9043470799228438,
            0.0,
            0.42679779642709725
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h_67_washing_machine_699922",
        "episode_history": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the large white appliance next to the door and under the window in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "A washing machine.",
        "object_id": 67,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            0.4742662012577057,
            0.010577410459518433,
            -4.569652557373047
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8734050397790175,
            0.0,
            0.4869944932836639
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h_69_office_chair_50276",
        "episode_history": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the office chair in front of the wooden desk in the study room pushed in?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 69,
        "class": "office chair",
        "position": [
            2.5965664386749268,
            0.010577410459518433,
            -4.672019004821777
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8624692551176261,
            0.0,
            0.5061094584937602
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h_250_office_chair_346123",
        "episode_history": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the black office chair?",
        "answer": "The black office chair is in the room with wooden flooring, positioned in front of the desk near the window with white curtains.",
        "object_id": 250,
        "class": "office chair",
        "position": [
            -0.512156069278717,
            0.010577410459518433,
            0.2194051593542099
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9930807675283673,
            0.0,
            0.11743333924090385
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h_70_desk_879851",
        "episode_history": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the desk in the room?",
        "answer": "A washing machine.",
        "object_id": 70,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            3.150040864944458,
            0.010577410459518433,
            -4.231354713439941
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.862327809360146,
            0.0,
            0.5063504213527739
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h_71_wall_board_431003",
        "episode_history": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the cork board located?",
        "answer": "The cork board is mounted on the wall above the wooden desk in the room with the wooden ceiling beams, near the hallway.",
        "object_id": 71,
        "class": "wall board",
        "position": [
            1.6531240940093994,
            0.010577410459518433,
            -4.072525501251221
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8737109820482039,
            0.0,
            0.48644539246287777
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h_258_monitor_244017",
        "episode_history": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the monitor on the desk in the study room turned off?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 258,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            -2.289238214492798,
            0.010577410459518433,
            2.6026859283447266
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8521594745303799,
            0.0,
            0.5232821705046973
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h_92_toilet_333198",
        "episode_history": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the toilet that is located next to the frosted glass door in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 92,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            1.759067177772522,
            0.010577410459518433,
            0.3779315948486328
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4797202519273845,
            0.0,
            0.8774214950015339
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h_217_led_tv_241412",
        "episode_history": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to watch TV shows and movies?",
        "answer": "The LED TV on top of the tall dresser.",
        "object_id": 217,
        "class": "led tv",
        "position": [
            2.509716749191284,
            0.010577410459518433,
            3.1794185638427734
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7713212473341415,
            0.0,
            0.6364460176722799
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h_246_locker_727717",
        "episode_history": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the white locker located?",
        "answer": "The white locker is in the room with wooden flooring, positioned against the wall near the mirrored closet doors and adjacent to the doorway leading to the hallway.",
        "object_id": 246,
        "class": "locker",
        "position": [
            -2.389448404312134,
            0.010577410459518433,
            3.1208012104034424
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.017070959087609222,
            0.0,
            0.9998542805608371
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h_247_tv_688841",
        "episode_history": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on top of the small white cabinet next to the curtain in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 247,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -1.871233582496643,
            0.010577410459518433,
            2.1267707347869873
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9021400722699214,
            0.0,
            0.43144326394651344
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h_264_computer_desk_171046",
        "episode_history": "00569-YJDUB7hWg9h",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the computer desk in the room cluttered with items?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 264,
        "class": "computer desk",
        "position": [
            -2.5509629249572754,
            0.010577410459518433,
            3.0613999366760254
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5162082182119341,
            0.0,
            0.856463119725806
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy_2_chest_304397",
        "episode_history": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the chest under the window in the empty room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 2,
        "class": "chest",
        "position": [
            3.6092042922973633,
            3.1120338439941406,
            -0.9174270033836365
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9784542288847677,
            0.0,
            0.20646385150315083
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy_331_trashcan_103015",
        "episode_history": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the stainless steel trashcan next to the kitchen counter closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 331,
        "class": "trashcan",
        "position": [
            3.5225882530212402,
            0.11203360557556152,
            -7.457880020141602
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5932827598036133,
            0.0,
            0.8049941409226579
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy_176_ladder_143605",
        "episode_history": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the black ladder?",
        "answer": "The black ladder is in the basement, leaning against the wall near the door and next to the water heater.",
        "object_id": 176,
        "class": "ladder",
        "position": [
            0.375733882188797,
            -2.6879663467407227,
            -1.1181833744049072
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9815571415879321,
            0.0,
            0.19116897707978084
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy_141_laundry_machine_534334",
        "episode_history": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the laundry machine that is next to the utility sink in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 141,
        "class": "laundry machine",
        "position": [
            1.013432264328003,
            0.11203360557556152,
            -2.4292030334472656
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5734956609271797,
            0.0,
            0.8192085979149005
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy_142_laundry_machine_565928",
        "episode_history": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the laundry machine in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "A shelf with various items, including a wooden crate and some cleaning supplies.",
        "object_id": 142,
        "class": "laundry machine",
        "position": [
            1.4780794382095337,
            0.11203360557556152,
            -1.962405800819397
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4574639243077468,
            0.0,
            0.8892281810407023
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy_179_exercise_ball_941298",
        "episode_history": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "Is there enough space around the exercise ball for me to do some stretching exercises?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 179,
        "class": "exercise ball",
        "position": [
            -0.42009538412094116,
            -2.6879663467407227,
            -1.6301597356796265
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9969417299988959,
            0.0,
            0.07814849318325343
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy_203_electric_box_189136",
        "episode_history": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to turn off the electricity in the house for maintenance?",
        "answer": "The electric box in the basement.",
        "object_id": 203,
        "class": "electric box",
        "position": [
            -0.11204350739717484,
            -2.6879663467407227,
            -0.14071574807167053
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9733770730909982,
            0.0,
            0.2292096716563288
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy_231_refrigerator_364337",
        "episode_history": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to store my frozen food?",
        "answer": "The refrigerator next to the door.",
        "object_id": 231,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            6.315395355224609,
            -2.6879663467407227,
            -8.261164665222168
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2573474838617635,
            0.0,
            0.9663189290032662
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy_330_refrigerator_559311",
        "episode_history": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on top of the refrigerator in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A basket and a plant.",
        "object_id": 330,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            1.6083955764770508,
            0.11203360557556152,
            -9.19310188293457
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9939946266020613,
            0.0,
            0.10942889146026774
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy_288_sofa_seat_255914",
        "episode_history": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the sofa seat that is positioned near the front door and a ladder with blankets?",
        "answer": "Light beige.",
        "object_id": 288,
        "class": "sofa seat",
        "position": [
            2.5502045154571533,
            0.11203360557556152,
            -7.201969146728516
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6675337355249013,
            0.0,
            0.7445795537994386
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy_289_sofa_chair_657997",
        "episode_history": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the sofa chair with the blanket draped over it?",
        "answer": "The sofa chair with the blanket draped over it is in the living room, next to the fireplace and near the large window with curtains.",
        "object_id": 289,
        "class": "sofa chair",
        "position": [
            4.84847354888916,
            0.11203360557556152,
            -8.384160995483398
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.25786309116254863,
            0.0,
            0.9661814665041424
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy_301_tv_557211",
        "episode_history": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the TV mounted on the stone wall in the living room?",
        "answer": "A fireplace.",
        "object_id": 301,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            5.4503984451293945,
            0.11203360557556152,
            -8.478182792663574
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.11332585888051838,
            0.0,
            0.9935578743631359
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy_333_microwave_252853",
        "episode_history": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the microwave that is installed above the stove in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 333,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            0.41072535514831543,
            0.11203360557556152,
            -5.710039138793945
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.008665046865371706,
            0.0,
            0.9999624577767011
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy_363_dog_bed_58470",
        "episode_history": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the dog bed next to the refrigerator in the kitchen empty?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 363,
        "class": "dog bed",
        "position": [
            0.2869027554988861,
            0.11203360557556152,
            -7.135987758636475
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9470457308004311,
            0.0,
            0.3210987134397721
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy_377_dining_table_162333",
        "episode_history": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there a centerpiece on the dining table in the dining room?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 377,
        "class": "dining table",
        "position": [
            2.1574602127075195,
            0.11203360557556152,
            -7.820774078369141
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.33406067403377937,
            0.0,
            0.9425515720978332
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy_475_window_shade_790639",
        "episode_history": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the window shade that is above the bed with a floral-patterned bedspread?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 475,
        "class": "window shade",
        "position": [
            0.8810186386108398,
            3.1120338439941406,
            -6.654722213745117
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.835000701910439,
            0.0,
            0.5502488780625312
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy_516_shower_curtain_747831",
        "episode_history": "00582-TYDavTf8oyy",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the shower curtain that is in the bathroom next to the hallway?",
        "answer": "The pattern is a subtle, repeating geometric design.",
        "object_id": 516,
        "class": "shower curtain",
        "position": [
            1.7284471988677979,
            3.1120338439941406,
            -6.738577842712402
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8301406656509734,
            0.0,
            0.557554011045171
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00591-JptJPosx1Z6_147_dishwasher_496026",
        "episode_history": "00591-JptJPosx1Z6",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash the dirty dishes quickly?",
        "answer": "The dishwasher under the counter.",
        "object_id": 147,
        "class": "dishwasher",
        "position": [
            -9.796878814697266,
            0.16929110884666443,
            -5.458637237548828
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9991488869828945,
            0.0,
            0.041249262306735465
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00591-JptJPosx1Z6_176_ventilation_hood_407297",
        "episode_history": "00591-JptJPosx1Z6",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the ventilation hood located?",
        "answer": "The ventilation hood is in the kitchen, above the stove and between the wooden cabinets.",
        "object_id": 176,
        "class": "ventilation hood",
        "position": [
            -8.63252067565918,
            0.16929110884666443,
            -3.2181010246276855
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.610662172514599,
            0.0,
            0.7918912242598413
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00591-JptJPosx1Z6_237_laptop_926509",
        "episode_history": "00591-JptJPosx1Z6",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the laptop on the wooden desk?",
        "answer": "A lamp.",
        "object_id": 237,
        "class": "laptop",
        "position": [
            -14.845460891723633,
            0.16929110884666443,
            -3.332611083984375
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5345143008812088,
            0.0,
            0.8451594300210301
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00591-JptJPosx1Z6_309_fireplace_951098",
        "episode_history": "00591-JptJPosx1Z6",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located in the living room, beneath the large painting and between the two armchairs?",
        "answer": "A fireplace.",
        "object_id": 309,
        "class": "fireplace",
        "position": [
            -3.761838674545288,
            0.16929110884666443,
            -7.735236167907715
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.1932873070969074,
            0.0,
            0.981142200150022
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00591-JptJPosx1Z6_352_rope_770636",
        "episode_history": "00591-JptJPosx1Z6",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the decorative rope with tassels located?",
        "answer": "The decorative rope with tassels is hanging on the wall near the curtains and a framed picture in the corner of the room.",
        "object_id": 352,
        "class": "rope",
        "position": [
            4.884998321533203,
            0.16929110884666443,
            -12.546841621398926
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.04022962252760658,
            0.0,
            0.9991904610589947
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00591-JptJPosx1Z6_407_bottle_600302",
        "episode_history": "00591-JptJPosx1Z6",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the bottle next to the ornate cabinet in the hallway standing upright?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 407,
        "class": "bottle",
        "position": [
            6.4065842628479,
            0.16929110884666443,
            -13.698210716247559
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9681780046326569,
            0.0,
            0.250262564810493
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00591-JptJPosx1Z6_427_sink_377167",
        "episode_history": "00591-JptJPosx1Z6",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the faucet of the pedestal sink in the bathroom turned off?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 427,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            3.494274139404297,
            0.16929110884666443,
            -5.461982727050781
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6371660684683449,
            0.0,
            0.7707265411237584
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00591-JptJPosx1Z6_988_storage_bin_594186",
        "episode_history": "00591-JptJPosx1Z6",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the storage bin with a leopard print blanket on top in the closet empty?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 988,
        "class": "storage bin",
        "position": [
            23.227861404418945,
            0.16929110884666443,
            -18.058732986450195
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7791574284848976,
            0.0,
            0.6268282872021667
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK_1_tv_483362",
        "episode_history": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the TV mounted on the wall above the wooden dresser in the bedroom turned on?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 1,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            7.534077167510986,
            3.226367235183716,
            4.17606258392334
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8429829950945908,
            0.0,
            0.5379402104150174
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK_4_seat_24642",
        "episode_history": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the seat that is positioned near the large black-framed mirror and the window?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 4,
        "class": "seat",
        "position": [
            4.434701442718506,
            3.226367235183716,
            3.841144323348999
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8656465011304553,
            0.0,
            0.5006557051313815
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK_5_laundry_basket_5153",
        "episode_history": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the laundry basket in the hallway?",
        "answer": "The entrance to the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 5,
        "class": "laundry basket",
        "position": [
            6.087428092956543,
            3.226367235183716,
            4.067788600921631
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5444166586428884,
            0.0,
            0.8388149389419056
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK_6_nightstand_74142",
        "episode_history": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the white nightstand in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "The white nightstand is next to the bed, positioned against the wall near the door to the closet.",
        "object_id": 6,
        "class": "nightstand",
        "position": [
            4.5268964767456055,
            3.226367235183716,
            4.1817216873168945
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.12745568563478535,
            0.0,
            0.9918442661019757
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK_7_nightstand_970663",
        "episode_history": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on top of the nightstand next to the bed?",
        "answer": "A small plant pot.",
        "object_id": 7,
        "class": "nightstand",
        "position": [
            7.541901588439941,
            3.226367235183716,
            3.3249001502990723
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.029321104469577045,
            0.0,
            0.9995700439852547
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK_146_monitor_879168",
        "episode_history": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the monitor on the desk in the study room?",
        "answer": "A globe and a laptop.",
        "object_id": 146,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            1.0150120258331299,
            0.0263671875,
            0.7064098119735718
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4637555746139928,
            0.0,
            0.8859631860379106
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK_147_laptop_610796",
        "episode_history": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the laptop on the desk near the window?",
        "answer": "A globe.",
        "object_id": 147,
        "class": "laptop",
        "position": [
            0.39813071489334106,
            0.0263671875,
            0.7492738366127014
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4641053251332816,
            0.0,
            0.8857800218919655
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK_150_chair_771156",
        "episode_history": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the grey chair with wooden legs?",
        "answer": "The grey chair with wooden legs is in the study room, positioned in front of the desk with a computer monitor, near the window with a view outside.",
        "object_id": 150,
        "class": "chair",
        "position": [
            2.098339080810547,
            0.08848457038402557,
            -0.42929306626319885
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7430659431958094,
            0.0,
            0.6692182036245892
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK_229_box_151882",
        "episode_history": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the purple box on the middle shelf of the white rack in the room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 229,
        "class": "box",
        "position": [
            1.3990737199783325,
            0.0263671875,
            3.9538333415985107
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9994411944102997,
            0.0,
            0.033426021535877336
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK_233_crib_265413",
        "episode_history": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I put the baby to sleep safely?",
        "answer": "The crib by the window.",
        "object_id": 233,
        "class": "crib",
        "position": [
            0.6423994302749634,
            0.0263671875,
            2.273746967315674
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9823346439829624,
            0.0,
            0.18713269952326717
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK_353_basket_of_something_401340",
        "episode_history": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the basket with the red cloth?",
        "answer": "The basket with the red cloth is on the floor next to the large window with plants outside, in the corner of the room near the door.",
        "object_id": 353,
        "class": "basket of something",
        "position": [
            6.787209987640381,
            -2.9736328125,
            3.5376534461975098
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.15832683787430285,
            0.0,
            0.9873867592836781
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK_356_tv_stand_915136",
        "episode_history": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to place my television and store media equipment?",
        "answer": "The TV stand in the living room.",
        "object_id": 356,
        "class": "tv stand",
        "position": [
            4.947303295135498,
            -2.9736328125,
            5.259857177734375
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5026683028819352,
            0.0,
            0.8644793677571462
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK_391_refrigerator_307598",
        "episode_history": "00592-CthA7sQNTPK",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the stainless steel refrigerator?",
        "answer": "The stainless steel refrigerator is in the kitchen, next to the wooden cabinets and near the door leading outside.",
        "object_id": 391,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            2.7188663482666016,
            -2.9736328125,
            1.0311353206634521
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7199061653660234,
            0.0,
            0.6940714034362658
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v_7_flower_148951",
        "episode_history": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is next to the flower on the ledge beside the bathtub?",
        "answer": "A decorative vase.",
        "object_id": 7,
        "class": "flower",
        "position": [
            -5.565807342529297,
            0.17746078968048096,
            -6.0593581199646
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5524611613780052,
            0.0,
            0.8335386404773721
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v_16_bath_659558",
        "episode_history": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bathtub located?",
        "answer": "The bathtub is in the bathroom, positioned at the far end of the room under a painting of a beach scene, next to the toilet and near a white cabinet.",
        "object_id": 16,
        "class": "bath",
        "position": [
            -4.340868949890137,
            0.12628206610679626,
            -5.8501505851745605
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7122290947171436,
            0.0,
            0.7019470896288397
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v_120_laptop_299700",
        "episode_history": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to work on my computer tasks?",
        "answer": "The laptop on the desk.",
        "object_id": 120,
        "class": "laptop",
        "position": [
            -0.07361859083175659,
            2.8644237518310547,
            -5.740602970123291
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7469634180268409,
            0.0,
            0.6648651383022418
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v_137_exercise_ball_976374",
        "episode_history": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to do some core strengthening exercises?",
        "answer": "The exercise ball in the corner of the room.",
        "object_id": 137,
        "class": "exercise ball",
        "position": [
            -0.2970965802669525,
            2.8644237518310547,
            -5.205410957336426
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9605651464461425,
            0.0,
            0.27805502950477395
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v_175_shower_bench_60798",
        "episode_history": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "Is there enough space on the shower bench to place a bottle of shampoo?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 175,
        "class": "shower bench",
        "position": [
            0.7440010905265808,
            2.904987335205078,
            -1.9672256708145142
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9577278627287743,
            0.0,
            0.2876757566305753
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v_718_dresser_793345",
        "episode_history": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the top drawer of the wooden dresser in the bedroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 718,
        "class": "dresser",
        "position": [
            -0.3395571708679199,
            0.06442362070083618,
            -5.728263854980469
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7981259868709656,
            0.0,
            0.6024905883756585
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v_270_washing_machine_658045",
        "episode_history": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the washing machine located?",
        "answer": "The washing machine is in the laundry area next to the dryer, near the door leading to another room. It is positioned beside a water heater and below a shelf with various items.",
        "object_id": 270,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            3.1982288360595703,
            -0.13557636737823486,
            3.408679962158203
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.25323368913650807,
            0.0,
            0.967405136789295
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v_407_bucket_612152",
        "episode_history": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the white bucket with a green label?",
        "answer": "The white bucket with a green label is in the garage, placed on the floor next to a green storage bin and in front of a shelf filled with various containers and tools.",
        "object_id": 407,
        "class": "bucket",
        "position": [
            3.904395341873169,
            -0.13557636737823486,
            3.352356433868408
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8610856686381737,
            0.0,
            0.5084599013353457
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v_612_coffee_machine_59201",
        "episode_history": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the coffee machine located?",
        "answer": "The coffee machine is on the kitchen counter, between the stove and the sink, under the wooden cabinets.",
        "object_id": 612,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            -0.54720139503479,
            0.06442362070083618,
            0.07530852407217026
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8955803647876415,
            0.0,
            0.444899775462783
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v_619_dishwasher_543563",
        "episode_history": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the dishwasher that is located between the sink and the oven in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Stainless steel.",
        "object_id": 619,
        "class": "dishwasher",
        "position": [
            -2.2496981620788574,
            0.06442362070083618,
            -1.3643853664398193
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8836383810641372,
            0.0,
            0.4681700668671063
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v_682_printer_528044",
        "episode_history": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to print my documents?",
        "answer": "The printer on the wooden desk.",
        "object_id": 682,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            -0.9714072942733765,
            0.06442362070083618,
            -5.376382827758789
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.24558622707384467,
            0.0,
            0.9693747495533572
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v_720_flower_vase_595607",
        "episode_history": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on top of the wooden dresser under the slanted ceiling in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A flower vase.",
        "object_id": 720,
        "class": "flower vase",
        "position": [
            -0.873676061630249,
            0.06442362070083618,
            -5.4064226150512695
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8197619354878094,
            0.0,
            0.572704434350984
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v_773_coffee_table_700360",
        "episode_history": "00606-W16Bm4ysK8v",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the coffee table in the living room cluttered with items?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 773,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            -7.910858154296875,
            -0.3355763852596283,
            0.3841314911842346
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9208063125534389,
            0.0,
            0.3900201722497677
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00626-XiJhRLvpKpX_68_piano_315750",
        "episode_history": "00626-XiJhRLvpKpX",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to play some music for the guests?",
        "answer": "The piano near the window.",
        "object_id": 68,
        "class": "piano",
        "position": [
            -11.27541732788086,
            0.03955364227294922,
            9.04041862487793
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.25799691779119494,
            0.0,
            0.9661457397361143
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00626-XiJhRLvpKpX_69_piano_bench_543546",
        "episode_history": "00626-XiJhRLvpKpX",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "Is there enough space for someone to sit on the piano bench without moving the dining chairs?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 69,
        "class": "piano bench",
        "position": [
            -10.611472129821777,
            0.03955364227294922,
            7.4437127113342285
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5737017361647249,
            0.0,
            0.8190642941317736
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00626-XiJhRLvpKpX_76_monitor_224641",
        "episode_history": "00626-XiJhRLvpKpX",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the desk in front of the black office chair in the study area?",
        "answer": "A monitor.",
        "object_id": 76,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            -11.008251190185547,
            0.03955364227294922,
            5.84066915512085
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7174945607636675,
            0.0,
            0.6965641070817186
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00626-XiJhRLvpKpX_313_monitor_129457",
        "episode_history": "00626-XiJhRLvpKpX",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the monitor on the wooden cabinet in the corner of the room turned off?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 313,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            -1.0990897417068481,
            0.23955368995666504,
            6.3368072509765625
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7131492792973305,
            0.0,
            0.701012200633982
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00626-XiJhRLvpKpX_303_fireplace_tool_set_140441",
        "episode_history": "00626-XiJhRLvpKpX",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to tend to the fire in the fireplace?",
        "answer": "The fireplace tool set next to the green-tiled fireplace.",
        "object_id": 303,
        "class": "fireplace tool set",
        "position": [
            -2.6673619747161865,
            0.03955364227294922,
            2.2013986110687256
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5347555661352825,
            0.0,
            0.8450067955273102
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00626-XiJhRLvpKpX_615_screen_354566",
        "episode_history": "00626-XiJhRLvpKpX",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the screen that is placed on the wooden shelf near the dining area with red chairs?",
        "answer": "The screen is rectangular.",
        "object_id": 615,
        "class": "screen",
        "position": [
            5.573325157165527,
            0.03955364227294922,
            16.16311264038086
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9659456622721543,
            0.0,
            0.25874500485537627
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00626-XiJhRLvpKpX_691_bench_484236",
        "episode_history": "00626-XiJhRLvpKpX",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the bench that is placed in front of the windows with flower boxes?",
        "answer": "Wood.",
        "object_id": 691,
        "class": "bench",
        "position": [
            6.501009464263916,
            0.23955368995666504,
            -0.17552565038204193
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9895143911569926,
            0.0,
            0.14443430926620435
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00626-XiJhRLvpKpX_933_exercise_ball_671885",
        "episode_history": "00626-XiJhRLvpKpX",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is the object directly behind the exercise ball in the home gym?",
        "answer": "A large mirror.",
        "object_id": 933,
        "class": "exercise ball",
        "position": [
            -6.675243854522705,
            -2.760446548461914,
            0.40937870740890503
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5894183542698223,
            0.0,
            0.8078279542389297
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00626-XiJhRLvpKpX_1239_sauna_heat_rocks_878702",
        "episode_history": "00626-XiJhRLvpKpX",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the sauna heat rocks that are placed in the corner between the two wooden benches?",
        "answer": "The sauna heat rocks are irregularly shaped.",
        "object_id": 1239,
        "class": "sauna heat rocks",
        "position": [
            12.342826843261719,
            -2.760446548461914,
            0.4428635537624359
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.37553534535594907,
            0.0,
            0.9268080731135159
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00626-XiJhRLvpKpX_1261_statue_130947",
        "episode_history": "00626-XiJhRLvpKpX",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the lighting that illuminates the statue near the stone wall and wooden lounge chair?",
        "answer": "Blue.",
        "object_id": 1261,
        "class": "statue",
        "position": [
            15.968517303466797,
            -2.5604465007781982,
            -0.05192353576421738
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9298675367859995,
            0.0,
            0.3678945012249272
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00643-ggNAcMh8JPT_56_dining_table_612116",
        "episode_history": "00643-ggNAcMh8JPT",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the round wooden object near the chairs in the dining area of the living room?",
        "answer": "A dining table.",
        "object_id": 56,
        "class": "dining table",
        "position": [
            -5.389593601226807,
            0.1174783706665039,
            0.4153629541397095
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5820044858383285,
            0.0,
            0.813185574431853
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00643-ggNAcMh8JPT_61_refrigerator_476945",
        "episode_history": "00643-ggNAcMh8JPT",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the large white appliance next to the kitchen counter and below the cabinets?",
        "answer": "A refrigerator.",
        "object_id": 61,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -3.3165132999420166,
            0.1174783706665039,
            -2.2709598541259766
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.858722942767649,
            0.0,
            0.5124401502268033
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00643-ggNAcMh8JPT_65_tv_493295",
        "episode_history": "00643-ggNAcMh8JPT",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the TV in the living room turned off?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 65,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -2.423694610595703,
            0.1174783706665039,
            -0.12561814486980438
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5940205848357413,
            0.0,
            0.8044498398230955
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00643-ggNAcMh8JPT_69_speaker_560396",
        "episode_history": "00643-ggNAcMh8JPT",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the speaker next to the TV stand in the living room?",
        "answer": "A TV stand with a television on it.",
        "object_id": 69,
        "class": "speaker",
        "position": [
            -2.320067882537842,
            0.1174783706665039,
            -0.49850165843963623
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7403594383604257,
            0.0,
            0.6722112034402841
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00643-ggNAcMh8JPT_136_laundry_machine_515606",
        "episode_history": "00643-ggNAcMh8JPT",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the laundry machine located?",
        "answer": "The laundry machine is in the kitchen, to the left of the door leading to the pantry area.",
        "object_id": 136,
        "class": "laundry machine",
        "position": [
            -5.323425769805908,
            0.1174783706665039,
            -0.35334131121635437
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.674714593207784,
            0.0,
            0.738078734087668
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5_18_laundry_basket_184615",
        "episode_history": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I put my dirty clothes for washing?",
        "answer": "The laundry basket next to the dresser.",
        "object_id": 18,
        "class": "laundry basket",
        "position": [
            0.773213267326355,
            0.17181682586669922,
            -3.71570086479187
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6637645049083836,
            0.0,
            0.747941630091365
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5_322_toilet_230690",
        "episode_history": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to relieve myself?",
        "answer": "The toilet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 322,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            8.625733375549316,
            0.012814819812774658,
            -4.017930507659912
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.23060692139164599,
            0.0,
            0.9730469915714591
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5_82_sink_cabinet_133975",
        "episode_history": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the wooden object with a sink on top, located next to the door in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A sink cabinet.",
        "object_id": 82,
        "class": "sink cabinet",
        "position": [
            -0.49546340107917786,
            0.012814819812774658,
            -3.058964729309082
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9924837150881607,
            0.0,
            0.12237677592092652
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5_111_pouffe_426426",
        "episode_history": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the orange pouffe located?",
        "answer": "The orange pouffe is in the living room, next to the wooden console table and near the dark brown chest with drawers.",
        "object_id": 111,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            3.5990829467773438,
            0.029422489926218987,
            -3.218374252319336
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.933843497795113,
            0.0,
            0.3576818720955651
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5_121_bouquet_758566",
        "episode_history": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the bouquet on the ornate cabinet in the living room fresh?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 121,
        "class": "bouquet",
        "position": [
            3.736556053161621,
            0.1988314390182495,
            -1.9556190967559814
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.005791172979109297,
            0.0,
            0.9999832310171636
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5_124_cabinet_table_809014",
        "episode_history": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on top of the cabinet table near the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A lamp and a vase with flowers.",
        "object_id": 124,
        "class": "cabinet table",
        "position": [
            2.545886516571045,
            0.12387591600418091,
            -1.0393000841140747
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.014837493212807749,
            0.0,
            0.9998899183385939
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5_137_table_lamp_90691",
        "episode_history": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the table lamp on the wooden console table in the living room?",
        "answer": "A white vase with green leaves.",
        "object_id": 137,
        "class": "table lamp",
        "position": [
            4.184345245361328,
            0.11560787260532379,
            -2.64251708984375
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8518451000007249,
            0.0,
            0.5237937815636562
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5_142_dog_bed_527249",
        "episode_history": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there a toy on the dog bed next to the console table in the living room?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 142,
        "class": "dog bed",
        "position": [
            4.73007869720459,
            0.015136698260903358,
            -3.232468605041504
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9791382884428482,
            0.0,
            0.20319501004013552
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5_179_bin_506434",
        "episode_history": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the metallic object located between the refrigerator and the door in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A bin.",
        "object_id": 179,
        "class": "bin",
        "position": [
            4.179140090942383,
            0.012814819812774658,
            -5.2063517570495605
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6099242754309714,
            0.0,
            0.7924597013350296
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5_181_microwave_347358",
        "episode_history": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The microwave is above the stove, between the cabinets and near the window with the sink.",
        "object_id": 181,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            4.792845726013184,
            0.012814819812774658,
            -4.861175537109375
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2838826025969357,
            0.0,
            0.9588590448771864
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5_202_coffee_machine_782437",
        "episode_history": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to make a cup of coffee in the morning?",
        "answer": "The coffee machine on the countertop.",
        "object_id": 202,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            5.301325798034668,
            0.05341462790966034,
            -5.096539497375488
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.26700855532094375,
            0.0,
            0.9636941586340672
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5_240_bowl_676614",
        "episode_history": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the pet food bowl?",
        "answer": "The pet food bowl is on the floor in the corner of the dining nook, near the white round table and the cushioned bench seating.",
        "object_id": 240,
        "class": "bowl",
        "position": [
            4.995291233062744,
            0.012814819812774658,
            -5.005002498626709
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6238525175622646,
            0.0,
            0.7815420886498848
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5_241_table_643532",
        "episode_history": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I place the dishes for our meal?",
        "answer": "The table in the dining nook.",
        "object_id": 241,
        "class": "table",
        "position": [
            4.089191436767578,
            0.012814819812774658,
            -5.3904571533203125
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7183790950945599,
            0.0,
            0.6956518351381827
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5_494_tv_252254",
        "episode_history": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object mounted above the white brick fireplace in the living room?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 494,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            3.2084739208221436,
            0.09218842536211014,
            1.350879192352295
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6952311582498241,
            0.0,
            0.7187862245470541
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5_335_bathtub_999930",
        "episode_history": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object next to the toilet and behind the shower curtain in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A bathtub.",
        "object_id": 335,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            8.736125946044922,
            0.012814819812774658,
            -4.186384677886963
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3897666352843098,
            0.0,
            0.9209136604585404
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5_388_desk_lamp_277874",
        "episode_history": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the desk lamp that is placed on the wooden desk near the window with white curtains?",
        "answer": "The desk lamp is beige.",
        "object_id": 388,
        "class": "desk lamp",
        "position": [
            0.7561773061752319,
            0.2128148078918457,
            1.548911690711975
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8805923658485748,
            0.0,
            0.4738745458549232
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5_389_desk_439780",
        "episode_history": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lamp on the desk in the study room turned on?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 389,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            0.6008745431900024,
            0.012814819812774658,
            -0.40870213508605957
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9919676136164634,
            0.0,
            0.12649210859204438
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5_466_oven_649417",
        "episode_history": "00680-YmWinf3mhb5",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the oven in the living room?",
        "answer": "A large TV mounted on the wall.",
        "object_id": 466,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            3.050569534301758,
            0.05008059740066528,
            1.166252613067627
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7302739305880034,
            0.0,
            0.6831544381057243
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p_16_blinds_278834",
        "episode_history": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the blinds in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A radiator.",
        "object_id": 16,
        "class": "blinds",
        "position": [
            -1.5262210369110107,
            0.07948863506317139,
            -1.7196934223175049
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5783831045501538,
            0.0,
            0.8157652752911991
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p_17_heater_659298",
        "episode_history": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the heater in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A window with a closed blind.",
        "object_id": 17,
        "class": "heater",
        "position": [
            -2.128662109375,
            0.07948863506317139,
            -1.6332285404205322
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6040571047245964,
            0.0,
            0.7969410356053565
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p_18_jacket_81633",
        "episode_history": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the jacket hanging in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "The jacket is hanging on a stand next to the window and radiator in the bedroom.",
        "object_id": 18,
        "class": "jacket",
        "position": [
            -2.267144203186035,
            0.07948863506317139,
            -2.007603645324707
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7764264265417226,
            0.0,
            0.6302079055102778
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p_22_nightstand_59632",
        "episode_history": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the wooden object next to the bed and below the wall lamp in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A nightstand.",
        "object_id": 22,
        "class": "nightstand",
        "position": [
            -0.0402165986597538,
            0.07948863506317139,
            -1.8019847869873047
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.072358730454128,
            0.0,
            0.9973786713816708
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p_23_nightstand_767003",
        "episode_history": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on top of the nightstand next to the bed?",
        "answer": "A lamp and a remote control.",
        "object_id": 23,
        "class": "nightstand",
        "position": [
            -2.2075657844543457,
            0.07948863506317139,
            -1.2719477415084839
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.027446589665366634,
            0.0,
            0.9996232713956499
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p_72_tv_563319",
        "episode_history": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the TV located?",
        "answer": "The TV is mounted on the wall in the living room, near the doorway and above a small wooden table. It is positioned next to a shelf with various items and across from a sofa and coffee table.",
        "object_id": 72,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -2.405975103378296,
            0.07948863506317139,
            1.610390067100525
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5526102408052231,
            0.0,
            0.8334398129182414
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p_206_tv_897636",
        "episode_history": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the TV located?",
        "answer": "The TV is in the living room, positioned against the wall that separates the kitchen from the living area, near the sliding glass doors that lead to the outside.",
        "object_id": 206,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -6.713273048400879,
            0.07948863506317139,
            -0.8000212907791138
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8701472628032443,
            0.0,
            0.4927917826384908
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p_78_printer_476462",
        "episode_history": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the printer located?",
        "answer": "The printer is on a small black table next to the TV stand and near the window with a radiator underneath it.",
        "object_id": 78,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            -1.433530330657959,
            0.07948863506317139,
            2.0795772075653076
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.41930489999469667,
            0.0,
            0.9078454718951003
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p_140_shower_tub_575168",
        "episode_history": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly to the left of the shower tub in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A towel rack with towels.",
        "object_id": 140,
        "class": "shower tub",
        "position": [
            -4.522395610809326,
            0.07948863506317139,
            0.34797435998916626
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9928740210741952,
            0.0,
            0.11916869671167035
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p_141_toilet_466767",
        "episode_history": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to relieve myself?",
        "answer": "The toilet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 141,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -4.04115104675293,
            0.07948863506317139,
            0.676959753036499
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9994330135092817,
            0.0,
            0.03366974172472761
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p_144_trash_can_899999",
        "episode_history": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the small cylindrical object located between the toilet and the wooden cabinet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A trash can.",
        "object_id": 144,
        "class": "trash can",
        "position": [
            -4.332251071929932,
            0.07948863506317139,
            1.346811294555664
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9639261504975792,
            0.0,
            0.26616982621423946
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p_210_basket_of_something_210072",
        "episode_history": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is inside the small woven basket that is placed near the television stand?",
        "answer": "The basket contains small white objects, likely stones or decorative items.",
        "object_id": 210,
        "class": "basket of something",
        "position": [
            -7.714548587799072,
            0.07948863506317139,
            -0.44755813479423523
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.947706952080248,
            0.0,
            0.31914186967360947
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p_220_armchair_224973",
        "episode_history": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the black armchair?",
        "answer": "The black armchair is in the living room, positioned near the large windows and facing the TV. It is placed on a decorative rug next to another black chair and a white sofa.",
        "object_id": 220,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            -9.509461402893066,
            0.07948863506317139,
            -3.5209364891052246
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.988744402035636,
            0.0,
            0.14961452951900328
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p_239_dining_table_661859",
        "episode_history": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there a lamp on the dining table in the room with the tapestry on the wall?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 239,
        "class": "dining table",
        "position": [
            -6.535738945007324,
            0.07948863506317139,
            -0.4845227599143982
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.24963097159538908,
            0.0,
            0.9683410442712537
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p_281_washing_machine_905167",
        "episode_history": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the washing machine located?",
        "answer": "The washing machine is in the laundry room, to the right of the door, next to the counter and under the cabinets.",
        "object_id": 281,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -8.402421951293945,
            0.07948863506317139,
            1.9080730676651
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8402809454928515,
            0.0,
            0.5421512082820065
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p_283_laundry_basket_956398",
        "episode_history": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the white object located between the dishwasher and the washing machine in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "A laundry basket.",
        "object_id": 283,
        "class": "laundry basket",
        "position": [
            -7.850704193115234,
            0.07948863506317139,
            2.2369959354400635
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6804384770513591,
            0.0,
            0.7328052121457838
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p_332_coffee_machine_213238",
        "episode_history": "00706-YHmAkqgwe2p",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the coffee machine on the kitchen counter next to the sink clean?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 332,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            -8.071419715881348,
            0.07948863506317139,
            1.977959394454956
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9722899266088612,
            0.0,
            0.23377831083087106
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00723-hWDDQnSDMXb_885_laptop_912137",
        "episode_history": "00723-hWDDQnSDMXb",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the laptop that is placed on the wooden desk near the black chair?",
        "answer": "The color is gray.",
        "object_id": 885,
        "class": "laptop",
        "position": [
            -8.123496055603027,
            -2.158547878265381,
            5.758255958557129
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8353642546819816,
            0.0,
            0.5496967909671816
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00723-hWDDQnSDMXb_557_fireplace_621726",
        "episode_history": "00723-hWDDQnSDMXb",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to warm up the living room?",
        "answer": "The fireplace against the stone wall.",
        "object_id": 557,
        "class": "fireplace",
        "position": [
            -3.516059398651123,
            0.04145216941833496,
            7.101663589477539
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9858552127609319,
            0.0,
            0.16759922276698228
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00723-hWDDQnSDMXb_638_microwave_421227",
        "episode_history": "00723-hWDDQnSDMXb",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located above the double oven and next to the refrigerator in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A microwave.",
        "object_id": 638,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -10.273078918457031,
            0.04145216941833496,
            13.410018920898438
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7671679746122182,
            0.0,
            0.6414462555268265
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00723-hWDDQnSDMXb_811_mini_fridge_617819",
        "episode_history": "00723-hWDDQnSDMXb",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the small appliance located near the sliding glass door in the game room?",
        "answer": "A mini fridge.",
        "object_id": 811,
        "class": "mini fridge",
        "position": [
            -1.4673209190368652,
            -1.9936045408248901,
            2.734238386154175
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.03994440820689024,
            0.0,
            0.9992019036476069
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00723-hWDDQnSDMXb_819_foosball_game_table_784900",
        "episode_history": "00723-hWDDQnSDMXb",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object in the center of the room with multiple rods and small figures on it?",
        "answer": "A foosball game table.",
        "object_id": 819,
        "class": "foosball game table",
        "position": [
            1.841770052909851,
            -2.033966064453125,
            3.9615345001220703
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2312800004776867,
            0.0,
            0.9728872295281922
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00723-hWDDQnSDMXb_820_display_cabinet_113852",
        "episode_history": "00723-hWDDQnSDMXb",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located between the door and the dartboard in the room?",
        "answer": "A display cabinet.",
        "object_id": 820,
        "class": "display cabinet",
        "position": [
            0.6304752826690674,
            -2.087165355682373,
            3.7085185050964355
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7972597318284296,
            0.0,
            0.6036364137499167
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00723-hWDDQnSDMXb_879_printer_920417",
        "episode_history": "00723-hWDDQnSDMXb",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the printer that is placed on top of the small white refrigerator next to the filing cabinet?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 879,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            -8.978738784790039,
            -2.158547878265381,
            5.283627033233643
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.622599649471975,
            0.0,
            0.7825405270510747
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn_4_flowerpot_860824",
        "episode_history": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly behind the flowerpot on the wooden coffee table in the living room?",
        "answer": "A sectional sofa.",
        "object_id": 4,
        "class": "flowerpot",
        "position": [
            6.727829456329346,
            -2.847735643386841,
            1.7324587106704712
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.45093371819032135,
            0.0,
            0.8925574389354737
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn_8_led_tv_21587",
        "episode_history": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the LED TV located?",
        "answer": "The LED TV is in the living room, placed on a wooden cabinet between two windows, near a red leather chair.",
        "object_id": 8,
        "class": "led tv",
        "position": [
            6.559633731842041,
            -2.847735643386841,
            1.3088269233703613
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.343727399330936,
            0.0,
            0.9390694729087893
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn_60_bed_table_338871",
        "episode_history": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the small wooden object next to the bed in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A bed table.",
        "object_id": 60,
        "class": "bed table",
        "position": [
            3.230457305908203,
            -2.847735643386841,
            4.652919769287109
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9924470188079636,
            0.0,
            0.1226740186803475
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn_183_bag_485198",
        "episode_history": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the plastic bag hanging on the wall in the utility room filled with items?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 183,
        "class": "bag",
        "position": [
            -3.1200177669525146,
            -2.847735643386841,
            5.693280220031738
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.33190530666967727,
            0.0,
            0.9433127092351229
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn_224_monitor_349079",
        "episode_history": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to view my computer's display?",
        "answer": "The monitor on the desk.",
        "object_id": 224,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            -0.42090120911598206,
            -2.847735643386841,
            -6.129599571228027
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9493395976418733,
            0.0,
            0.3142520140733646
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn_232_monitor_574504",
        "episode_history": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly behind the monitor on the desk in the study room?",
        "answer": "A window with red curtains.",
        "object_id": 232,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            -0.894870400428772,
            -2.847735643386841,
            -3.556879997253418
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.466660110891531,
            0.0,
            0.8844367365180531
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn_234_printer_820928",
        "episode_history": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is the object next to the printer on the wooden chest?",
        "answer": "A box of tissues.",
        "object_id": 234,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            -0.1522039771080017,
            -2.847735643386841,
            -5.594315528869629
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.298323686423906,
            0.0,
            0.9544647600191696
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn_246_bookshelf_520461",
        "episode_history": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the bookshelf that is next to the bed with a red plaid blanket?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 246,
        "class": "bookshelf",
        "position": [
            -0.8507770895957947,
            -2.847735643386841,
            -5.161360740661621
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5721583881298562,
            0.0,
            0.8201431453671029
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn_542_clock_467451",
        "episode_history": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the clock with the wooden frame?",
        "answer": "The clock with the wooden frame is hanging on the dark wooden wall in the hallway, near the glass door leading to the outside deck.",
        "object_id": 542,
        "class": "clock",
        "position": [
            3.165839672088623,
            0.15226435661315918,
            -2.526623249053955
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.905231859845266,
            0.0,
            0.4249179684610676
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn_379_stove_518899",
        "episode_history": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the kettle that is on the stove located beneath the stainless steel range hood?",
        "answer": "Red.",
        "object_id": 379,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            0.43654924631118774,
            0.15226435661315918,
            6.028984069824219
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8640766670432816,
            0.0,
            0.5033602223769515
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn_380_ventilation_hood_865112",
        "episode_history": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to remove smoke and odors while cooking?",
        "answer": "The ventilation hood above the stove.",
        "object_id": 380,
        "class": "ventilation hood",
        "position": [
            0.6134243011474609,
            0.15226435661315918,
            6.581090927124023
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.743397755953585,
            0.0,
            0.6688495917941297
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn_387_oven_34844",
        "episode_history": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the oven located in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The oven is located in the kitchen, built into the cabinets under the countertop, near the corner where the two countertops meet.",
        "object_id": 387,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            -0.15032464265823364,
            0.15226435661315918,
            5.377438545227051
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9537978356499809,
            0.0,
            0.30044914496369013
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn_394_oven_461932",
        "episode_history": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located above the drawer and next to the refrigerator in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "An oven.",
        "object_id": 394,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            0.7128689289093018,
            0.15226435661315918,
            6.573473930358887
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.23602944495247655,
            0.0,
            0.9717459035753255
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn_395_refrigerator_720212",
        "episode_history": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to keep my groceries cold and fresh?",
        "answer": "The refrigerator in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 395,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -2.5074026584625244,
            0.15226435661315918,
            4.789106369018555
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5997886505915563,
            0.0,
            0.8001584684433203
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn_397_stone_bench_899414",
        "episode_history": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the stone bench in the hallway?",
        "answer": "A wooden sign hung on the wall.",
        "object_id": 397,
        "class": "stone bench",
        "position": [
            0.5580926537513733,
            0.15226435661315918,
            4.810420989990234
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7789817790171032,
            0.0,
            0.6270465596423833
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn_409_washing_machine_80860",
        "episode_history": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the washing machine in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "A set of dark-colored cabinets.",
        "object_id": 409,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -2.996697425842285,
            0.15226435661315918,
            5.817295074462891
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9141704973131382,
            0.0,
            0.405329867937523
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn_410_washing_machine_918083",
        "episode_history": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the washing machine next to the dryer in the laundry room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 410,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -3.8499813079833984,
            0.15226435661315918,
            4.87357759475708
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9994557343426683,
            0.0,
            0.032988408411490096
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn_456_tv_104654",
        "episode_history": "00732-Z2DQddYp1fn",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the TV that is placed on top of the tall wooden dresser near the window with dark curtains?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 456,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            0.2804528772830963,
            0.15226435661315918,
            -4.079364776611328
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9238508264772035,
            0.0,
            0.3827527275113633
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00733-GtM3JtRvvvR_131_tv_492447",
        "episode_history": "00733-GtM3JtRvvvR",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the TV located?",
        "answer": "The TV is mounted on the wall in the room with the black and white patterned rug, next to a framed picture.",
        "object_id": 131,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            8.27877140045166,
            0.11806264519691467,
            -2.8199548721313477
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5598619410212733,
            0.0,
            0.8285859080360299
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00733-GtM3JtRvvvR_258_air_conditioner_997053",
        "episode_history": "00733-GtM3JtRvvvR",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "Is the air conditioner blocking the window when it is fully opened?",
        "answer": "No, the air conditioner is positioned to the side of the window and does not block it when fully opened.",
        "object_id": 258,
        "class": "air conditioner",
        "position": [
            16.693458557128906,
            0.11806264519691467,
            1.6786816120147705
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8918063420126126,
            0.0,
            0.4524173386886088
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00733-GtM3JtRvvvR_329_oven_626250",
        "episode_history": "00733-GtM3JtRvvvR",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the built-in oven in the kitchen closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 329,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            5.912436485290527,
            0.11806264519691467,
            2.8082363605499268
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9650542108142596,
            0.0,
            0.2620503199571918
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00733-GtM3JtRvvvR_330_microwave_582979",
        "episode_history": "00733-GtM3JtRvvvR",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "An oven.",
        "object_id": 330,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            3.954653263092041,
            0.11806264519691467,
            3.538769245147705
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9691813881897426,
            0.0,
            0.24634820232062546
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk_36_sheet_882685",
        "episode_history": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bed sheet with brown and beige stripes?",
        "answer": "The bed sheet with brown and beige stripes is on the bed in the bedroom, under the large abstract painting on the wall.",
        "object_id": 36,
        "class": "sheet",
        "position": [
            -2.868823766708374,
            -0.007398039102554321,
            -3.05427885055542
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6142221397575877,
            0.0,
            0.7891331719244924
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk_55_desk_180667",
        "episode_history": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the desk that is next to the tall wooden dresser with multiple drawers?",
        "answer": "The desk is white.",
        "object_id": 55,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            -5.963107109069824,
            -0.007398039102554321,
            -1.587906837463379
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.971505104715184,
            0.0,
            0.237018631150253
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk_56_desk_chair_193060",
        "episode_history": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the desk chair with the white upholstery?",
        "answer": "The desk chair with the white upholstery is in the corner room, positioned in front of the desk and next to a tall wooden dresser, near the large window.",
        "object_id": 56,
        "class": "desk chair",
        "position": [
            -5.9559783935546875,
            -0.007398039102554321,
            -1.3453361988067627
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9595669606317584,
            0.0,
            0.281480457694543
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk_86_toy_806765",
        "episode_history": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the primary color of the roof of the toy that is placed on top of a red storage box near the white shelf?",
        "answer": "Yellow.",
        "object_id": 86,
        "class": "toy",
        "position": [
            -7.016140937805176,
            -0.007398039102554321,
            -0.3050748109817505
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.008027256892260219,
            0.0,
            0.9999677810543626
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk_90_couch_102285",
        "episode_history": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the red couch with pillows?",
        "answer": "The red couch with pillows is in the living room, positioned against the wall with a large framed artwork above it, near the sliding glass doors that lead to the balcony.",
        "object_id": 90,
        "class": "couch",
        "position": [
            -3.0196661949157715,
            -0.007398039102554321,
            3.4669909477233887
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3895657798419509,
            0.0,
            0.9209986445028747
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk_115_tv_336196",
        "episode_history": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to watch my favorite shows and movies?",
        "answer": "The TV on the wooden stand.",
        "object_id": 115,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -6.737660884857178,
            0.015309195965528488,
            2.633985996246338
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9049917267794294,
            0.0,
            0.4254291650331305
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk_184_bathtub_847489",
        "episode_history": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to take a bath?",
        "answer": "The bathtub in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 184,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            -1.852771520614624,
            -0.007398039102554321,
            -2.3463540077209473
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.32989705403876657,
            0.0,
            0.9440169139038469
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk_186_bathroom_cabinet_882837",
        "episode_history": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the bathroom cabinet that is located below the mirror and next to the bathtub?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 186,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            -1.713171124458313,
            -0.007398039102554321,
            -2.9148330688476562
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5975760771598403,
            0.0,
            0.8018122174214213
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk_191_bathroom_cabinet_305630",
        "episode_history": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located to the left of the bathroom cabinet?",
        "answer": "A bathtub with shelves above it.",
        "object_id": 191,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            -1.9112095832824707,
            -0.007398039102554321,
            -2.764885902404785
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5960481796636617,
            0.0,
            0.8029486705385565
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk_275_toilet_133406",
        "episode_history": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to relieve myself?",
        "answer": "The toilet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 275,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -0.48477983474731445,
            2.9926021099090576,
            -0.2758972644805908
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2649209554120143,
            0.0,
            0.9642701319565931
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk_371_oven_156445",
        "episode_history": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the oven on the kitchen counter?",
        "answer": "A coffee machine.",
        "object_id": 371,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            -0.8262603878974915,
            2.9926021099090576,
            -2.98649263381958
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.053612585880394505,
            0.0,
            0.9985618111239871
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk_397_stove_679730",
        "episode_history": "00006-HkseAnWCgqk",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the stove in the kitchen clean?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 397,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            -0.9152246117591858,
            2.9926021099090576,
            -3.4319045543670654
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6463720863794791,
            0.0,
            0.7630223626797836
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00020-XYyR54sxe6b_74_couch_61133",
        "episode_history": "00020-XYyR54sxe6b",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object in the living room that is placed against the wall and has two cushions on it?",
        "answer": "A couch.",
        "object_id": 74,
        "class": "couch",
        "position": [
            -3.4251232147216797,
            0.1170770525932312,
            1.0055263042449951
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.036887672215063796,
            0.0,
            0.9993194182234998
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00020-XYyR54sxe6b_332_toilet_397385",
        "episode_history": "00020-XYyR54sxe6b",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the toilet with the wooden seat?",
        "answer": "The toilet with the wooden seat is in the bathroom, positioned between the sink cabinet and the window ledge.",
        "object_id": 332,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            0.09418010711669922,
            2.91707706451416,
            -4.431240081787109
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8052044594757916,
            0.0,
            0.5929972836702528
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00020-XYyR54sxe6b_142_furnace_701571",
        "episode_history": "00020-XYyR54sxe6b",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to heat up the room during the winter?",
        "answer": "The furnace in the dining room.",
        "object_id": 142,
        "class": "furnace",
        "position": [
            -2.9445040225982666,
            0.1170770525932312,
            -3.5269155502319336
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5668454739289752,
            0.0,
            0.8238241369893428
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00020-XYyR54sxe6b_179_microwave_426731",
        "episode_history": "00020-XYyR54sxe6b",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to quickly heat up my food?",
        "answer": "The microwave on the countertop.",
        "object_id": 179,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            2.3113677501678467,
            0.1170770525932312,
            -4.8852033615112305
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6121642462704089,
            0.0,
            0.7907306340266463
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00020-XYyR54sxe6b_196_washing_machine_362589",
        "episode_history": "00020-XYyR54sxe6b",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash my clothes?",
        "answer": "The washing machine next to the door.",
        "object_id": 196,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            1.7655742168426514,
            0.1170770525932312,
            -4.7942609786987305
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.466146713331728,
            0.0,
            0.8847074327991303
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00020-XYyR54sxe6b_237_stove_999877",
        "episode_history": "00020-XYyR54sxe6b",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to cook my food?",
        "answer": "The stove in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 237,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            0.08880241215229034,
            0.1170770525932312,
            -5.056641101837158
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8959736377858957,
            0.0,
            0.444107239743633
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR_6_dresser_713681",
        "episode_history": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on top of the white dresser in the hallway?",
        "answer": "A decorative vase with dried flowers and a small basket.",
        "object_id": 6,
        "class": "dresser",
        "position": [
            5.674562931060791,
            0.12750515341758728,
            1.4634860754013062
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7861871911185431,
            0.0,
            0.6179884307340513
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR_60_toilet_123394",
        "episode_history": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located between the shower and the sink in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A toilet.",
        "object_id": 60,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            5.827756881713867,
            0.12750515341758728,
            1.2153081893920898
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.285760718313477,
            0.0,
            0.9583010027485965
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR_93_toilet_553720",
        "episode_history": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the tiles on the floor surrounding the toilet that is next to the white shelving unit in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The tiles are a mix of red and white.",
        "object_id": 93,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            6.750455379486084,
            0.12750515341758728,
            4.852691173553467
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.25235258037062547,
            0.0,
            0.967635352382439
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR_480_sofa_chair_162435",
        "episode_history": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the small sofa chair with a pillow?",
        "answer": "The small sofa chair with a pillow is in the living room, positioned between the large window with curtains and the TV stand.",
        "object_id": 480,
        "class": "sofa chair",
        "position": [
            -1.847656488418579,
            0.12750515341758728,
            3.477001667022705
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.49473163532148196,
            0.0,
            0.8690458037480718
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR_233_microwave_712831",
        "episode_history": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the microwave on the shelf above the kitchen counter closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 233,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            1.3899133205413818,
            0.12750515341758728,
            -0.005067110061645508
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.31212763110070046,
            0.0,
            0.950040179099529
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR_236_recycle_bin_106322",
        "episode_history": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to dispose of recyclable materials?",
        "answer": "The recycle bin next to the refrigerator.",
        "object_id": 236,
        "class": "recycle bin",
        "position": [
            0.24713513255119324,
            0.12750515341758728,
            0.04713353514671326
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7772576721712106,
            0.0,
            0.6291824147661718
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR_237_refrigerator_774470",
        "episode_history": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to store my groceries and keep them fresh?",
        "answer": "The refrigerator in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 237,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -0.6100504994392395,
            0.12750515341758728,
            0.31380629539489746
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8059208721249069,
            0.0,
            0.5920232663277935
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR_251_oven_and_stove_555291",
        "episode_history": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the oven and stove that is located below the range hood and near the window in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 251,
        "class": "oven and stove",
        "position": [
            1.0960109233856201,
            0.12750515341758728,
            1.8504359722137451
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.06373683959989153,
            0.0,
            0.9979667405669478
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR_477_cabinet_494352",
        "episode_history": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are the wicker baskets in the cabinet under the TV in the living room properly placed inside their compartments?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 477,
        "class": "cabinet",
        "position": [
            -2.9356675148010254,
            0.12750515341758728,
            4.043710708618164
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.09489280226176615,
            0.0,
            0.9954874966964222
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR_376_bowl_455531",
        "episode_history": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to serve the fruits for the guests?",
        "answer": "The bowl on the wooden table.",
        "object_id": 376,
        "class": "bowl",
        "position": [
            1.3628439903259277,
            0.12750515341758728,
            1.6254050731658936
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8571374812149962,
            0.0,
            0.5150876996166888
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR_409_ventilation_hood_727361",
        "episode_history": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the large white ventilation hood located?",
        "answer": "The large white ventilation hood is in the living room, above the fireplace, near the window with white curtains and next to a chair with a red cushion.",
        "object_id": 409,
        "class": "ventilation hood",
        "position": [
            2.9626286029815674,
            0.12750515341758728,
            2.7361257076263428
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.920675316042765,
            0.0,
            0.39032929998855403
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR_447_blanket_415167",
        "episode_history": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to keep myself warm while sitting in the living room?",
        "answer": "The blanket on the shelf.",
        "object_id": 447,
        "class": "blanket",
        "position": [
            -0.07996242493391037,
            0.12750515341758728,
            4.917330265045166
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8265430225098411,
            0.0,
            0.5628735488014126
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR_471_tv_947152",
        "episode_history": "00023-zepmXAdrpjR",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the TV in the living room?",
        "answer": "A floor lamp.",
        "object_id": 471,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -3.527599811553955,
            0.12750515341758728,
            3.9908928871154785
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.009909862076364708,
            0.0,
            0.9999508961112178
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00033-oPj9qMxrDEa_57_oven_30530",
        "episode_history": "00033-oPj9qMxrDEa",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located directly above the oven in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A clock.",
        "object_id": 57,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            -0.9327190518379211,
            0.13368353247642517,
            0.4862770438194275
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.16083486789278464,
            0.0,
            0.9869813297473821
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00033-oPj9qMxrDEa_82_stove_240397",
        "episode_history": "00033-oPj9qMxrDEa",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What items are placed to the left of the stove on the kitchen counter?",
        "answer": "A set of knives and two bottles.",
        "object_id": 82,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            0.23719878494739532,
            0.13368353247642517,
            -0.938364565372467
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.33604392239200037,
            0.0,
            0.9418463156074877
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00033-oPj9qMxrDEa_137_tv_288048",
        "episode_history": "00033-oPj9qMxrDEa",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the TV located?",
        "answer": "The TV is mounted on the wall in the living room, above a wooden TV stand that has various decorative items on it. It is near a small table by the glass door.",
        "object_id": 137,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            2.1369943618774414,
            0.13368353247642517,
            5.777348041534424
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9762903413165607,
            0.0,
            0.2164651691427355
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00033-oPj9qMxrDEa_174_fireplace_350549",
        "episode_history": "00033-oPj9qMxrDEa",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the wall that the fireplace, which is flanked by two black wall-mounted lamps, is set into?",
        "answer": "Light blue.",
        "object_id": 174,
        "class": "fireplace",
        "position": [
            0.5481216907501221,
            0.13368353247642517,
            1.2912873029708862
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8055701459330241,
            0.0,
            0.5925004134863083
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00033-oPj9qMxrDEa_258_toilet_942981",
        "episode_history": "00033-oPj9qMxrDEa",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the toilet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The toilet is in the bathroom, positioned against the brown-tiled wall, next to a small wooden stool and near the white cabinet with stacked towels.",
        "object_id": 258,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -4.620061874389648,
            0.13368353247642517,
            5.3596696853637695
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9968956372314023,
            0.0,
            0.07873429029967063
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00033-oPj9qMxrDEa_295_monitor_877965",
        "episode_history": "00033-oPj9qMxrDEa",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the monitor on the desk in the study room turned off?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 295,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            -8.042520523071289,
            0.13368353247642517,
            5.921521186828613
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9567043495754916,
            0.0,
            0.29106148406021687
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00033-oPj9qMxrDEa_300_office_chair_963605",
        "episode_history": "00033-oPj9qMxrDEa",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the office chair in front of the desk in the study room pushed in?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 300,
        "class": "office chair",
        "position": [
            -9.668967247009277,
            0.13368353247642517,
            6.015719413757324
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.815782639570917,
            0.0,
            0.5783586127781858
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00033-oPj9qMxrDEa_479_washing_machine_788831",
        "episode_history": "00033-oPj9qMxrDEa",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the washing machine next to the dryer in the laundry room open?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 479,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -5.339298725128174,
            0.13368353247642517,
            3.780808925628662
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6903246156300663,
            0.0,
            0.7234997754354877
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00033-oPj9qMxrDEa_480_washing_machine_459042",
        "episode_history": "00033-oPj9qMxrDEa",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object to the right of the dryer in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "A washing machine.",
        "object_id": 480,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -5.01547384262085,
            0.13368353247642517,
            1.8981866836547852
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8359469698123166,
            0.0,
            0.5488102255439539
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00059-kJxT5qssH4H_64_bathtub_872528",
        "episode_history": "00059-kJxT5qssH4H",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the white bathtub next to the sliding glass door in the bedroom empty?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 64,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            4.6321892738342285,
            3.2607569694519043,
            -2.7559280395507812
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.04984287227810639,
            0.0,
            0.998757071606038
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00059-kJxT5qssH4H_107_book_781751",
        "episode_history": "00059-kJxT5qssH4H",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to read and relax?",
        "answer": "The book on the glass coffee table.",
        "object_id": 107,
        "class": "book",
        "position": [
            3.544703483581543,
            3.2607569694519043,
            -0.036747269332408905
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5852329849962788,
            0.0,
            0.8108651880999365
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00059-kJxT5qssH4H_166_wall_cubby_252055",
        "episode_history": "00059-kJxT5qssH4H",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the wall cubby that is located under the staircase?",
        "answer": "Glass.",
        "object_id": 166,
        "class": "wall cubby",
        "position": [
            0.8428189158439636,
            0.06075684726238251,
            -2.479727029800415
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.647727562380221,
            0.0,
            0.7618720397369737
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00059-kJxT5qssH4H_167_wall_cubby_547952",
        "episode_history": "00059-kJxT5qssH4H",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the wall cubby under the staircase closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 167,
        "class": "wall cubby",
        "position": [
            0.2805505394935608,
            0.06075684726238251,
            -6.167411804199219
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9502738311287956,
            0.0,
            0.31141555175007113
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00059-kJxT5qssH4H_182_desk_chair_648041",
        "episode_history": "00059-kJxT5qssH4H",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object in front of the desk and below the large wall-mounted TV in the study room?",
        "answer": "A desk chair.",
        "object_id": 182,
        "class": "desk chair",
        "position": [
            0.0805153101682663,
            0.06075684726238251,
            -7.264226913452148
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9949671976187047,
            0.0,
            0.10020117595511946
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00064-gQgtJ9Stk5s_1265_fan_451727",
        "episode_history": "00064-gQgtJ9Stk5s",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the fan next to the windows in the bedroom standing upright?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 1265,
        "class": "fan",
        "position": [
            -9.96174144744873,
            3.151498794555664,
            4.2783403396606445
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.536428815838271,
            0.0,
            0.8439455702462987
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00064-gQgtJ9Stk5s_602_basket_728440",
        "episode_history": "00064-gQgtJ9Stk5s",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the basket in the hallway?",
        "answer": "A framed picture hung on the wall.",
        "object_id": 602,
        "class": "basket",
        "position": [
            -8.193241119384766,
            0.18341350555419922,
            3.9137532711029053
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7083774996930382,
            0.0,
            0.7058337749985045
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00064-gQgtJ9Stk5s_715_mannequin_93153",
        "episode_history": "00064-gQgtJ9Stk5s",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the mannequin in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "A small wooden shelf with framed pictures.",
        "object_id": 715,
        "class": "mannequin",
        "position": [
            -11.303755760192871,
            0.18341350555419922,
            5.940558433532715
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4042839069352221,
            0.0,
            0.9146335455214797
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00064-gQgtJ9Stk5s_722_shelf_with_clutter_367891",
        "episode_history": "00064-gQgtJ9Stk5s",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the shelf with clutter next to the wooden dresser in the bedroom filled with books and magazines?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 722,
        "class": "shelf with clutter",
        "position": [
            -11.638144493103027,
            0.18341350555419922,
            6.168018341064453
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8340649637182644,
            0.0,
            0.5516662363219723
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00064-gQgtJ9Stk5s_1215_whiteboard_718705",
        "episode_history": "00064-gQgtJ9Stk5s",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the whiteboard that is placed in front of the cardboard boxes and near the green exercise ball?",
        "answer": "Rectangular.",
        "object_id": 1215,
        "class": "whiteboard",
        "position": [
            -0.9964840412139893,
            2.9834132194519043,
            2.8812828063964844
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9988742207825652,
            0.0,
            0.047437232803164725
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00064-gQgtJ9Stk5s_1201_rocking_horse_692415",
        "episode_history": "00064-gQgtJ9Stk5s",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the primary color of the rocking horse that is near the window with curtains and a small trampoline?",
        "answer": "Brown.",
        "object_id": 1201,
        "class": "rocking horse",
        "position": [
            -0.2901725769042969,
            2.9834132194519043,
            2.770815372467041
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9347021440758966,
            0.0,
            0.355431993298186
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00064-gQgtJ9Stk5s_1223_exercise_ball_460133",
        "episode_history": "00064-gQgtJ9Stk5s",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the exercise ball that is placed near the whiteboard and below the dartboard?",
        "answer": "Light blue.",
        "object_id": 1223,
        "class": "exercise ball",
        "position": [
            -1.457750916481018,
            2.9834132194519043,
            3.8777904510498047
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9965030699880696,
            0.0,
            0.08355615778836471
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00064-gQgtJ9Stk5s_1226_bean_bag_chair_36578",
        "episode_history": "00064-gQgtJ9Stk5s",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What are the colors of the bean bag chair that is placed under the wooden table near the window with curtains?",
        "answer": "Red, green, yellow, and white.",
        "object_id": 1226,
        "class": "bean bag chair",
        "position": [
            0.05633425712585449,
            2.9834132194519043,
            3.7467732429504395
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9820085434224348,
            0.0,
            0.18883649182652168
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00064-gQgtJ9Stk5s_1343_closet_shelf_478434",
        "episode_history": "00064-gQgtJ9Stk5s",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on the top shelf of the closet shelf next to the door in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A potted plant.",
        "object_id": 1343,
        "class": "closet shelf",
        "position": [
            -10.820781707763672,
            3.1398770809173584,
            4.224272727966309
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4637119360766003,
            0.0,
            0.8859860271697805
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00064-gQgtJ9Stk5s_1344_closet_shelf_633439",
        "episode_history": "00064-gQgtJ9Stk5s",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are the closet shelves in the bedroom filled with clothes?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 1344,
        "class": "closet shelf",
        "position": [
            -11.106546401977539,
            3.064551591873169,
            5.480802059173584
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5218761973393754,
            0.0,
            0.8530212392728527
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf_13_rug_638518",
        "episode_history": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the rug in the small room?",
        "answer": "A wooden chair.",
        "object_id": 13,
        "class": "rug",
        "position": [
            -2.9905436038970947,
            0.02108585834503174,
            -2.676556348800659
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.016761526899471607,
            0.0,
            0.9998595157400856
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf_21_clothes_763046",
        "episode_history": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are the clothes hanging on the rack next to the wooden wardrobe in the bedroom neatly arranged?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 21,
        "class": "clothes",
        "position": [
            -2.300800085067749,
            0.02108585834503174,
            -6.662999629974365
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8464089208220997,
            0.0,
            0.5325335095116255
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf_25_wall_tv_553185",
        "episode_history": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object mounted on the wall above the wooden dresser in the room with the wooden ceiling?",
        "answer": "A wall tv.",
        "object_id": 25,
        "class": "wall tv",
        "position": [
            -5.372808933258057,
            0.02108585834503174,
            -6.795253753662109
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9161005637936509,
            0.0,
            0.40094857153624397
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf_118_trash_can_976349",
        "episode_history": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to dispose of waste in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The trash can next to the toilet.",
        "object_id": 118,
        "class": "trash can",
        "position": [
            -3.2293038368225098,
            0.02108585834503174,
            -2.7250962257385254
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9999986232968459,
            0.0,
            0.0016593420481581798
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf_121_bidet_924760",
        "episode_history": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located to the right of the bidet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A small trash can and a toilet brush holder.",
        "object_id": 121,
        "class": "bidet",
        "position": [
            -3.2458431720733643,
            0.02108585834503174,
            -3.389397144317627
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9972386324258784,
            0.0,
            0.07426378658112233
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf_156_stove_196217",
        "episode_history": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located on the countertop between the toaster and the bottles in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A stove.",
        "object_id": 156,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            0.8500459790229797,
            0.02108585834503174,
            -5.283573150634766
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3109757251699256,
            0.0,
            0.950417854606614
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf_204_stove_916102",
        "episode_history": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the stove in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The stove is in the kitchen, located on the right side of the room, embedded in the wooden cabinetry under the range hood and next to the countertop with various kitchen items.",
        "object_id": 204,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            2.6182785034179688,
            0.02108585834503174,
            -6.01542854309082
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.82381264221542,
            0.0,
            0.5668621794810872
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf_164_refrigerator_273457",
        "episode_history": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are there any magnets on the door of the refrigerator in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 164,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            2.5946192741394043,
            0.02108585834503174,
            -6.276062965393066
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8975714143486584,
            0.0,
            0.4408690918449023
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf_168_tv_158554",
        "episode_history": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the TV on top of the wooden cabinet in the room turned off?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 168,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            2.152411460876465,
            0.02108585834503174,
            -6.276381015777588
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9827704038902061,
            0.0,
            0.1848305527705882
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf_292_tv_771494",
        "episode_history": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the white stand in front of the armchair in the living room?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 292,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            6.262012958526611,
            0.02108585834503174,
            -2.5884947776794434
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5549301701135432,
            0.0,
            0.8318969324969013
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf_197_dishwasher_291947",
        "episode_history": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the white appliance located between the wooden cabinets under the kitchen window?",
        "answer": "A dishwasher.",
        "object_id": 197,
        "class": "dishwasher",
        "position": [
            0.6719956398010254,
            0.02108585834503174,
            -4.859272480010986
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.12713874389950952,
            0.0,
            0.9918849428233372
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf_442_sink_567080",
        "episode_history": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the sink in the utility room?",
        "answer": "The sink is located in the utility room, between the washing machine and a tall white cabinet, directly under a mirror.",
        "object_id": 442,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            0.6325262188911438,
            0.02108585834503174,
            2.8802642822265625
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.03000921552064193,
            0.0,
            0.9995496220717788
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf_253_bouquet_319315",
        "episode_history": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the floor against the wall in the hallway, near the entrance to the rooms?",
        "answer": "A bouquet.",
        "object_id": 253,
        "class": "bouquet",
        "position": [
            -0.9305973649024963,
            0.02108585834503174,
            -2.917351722717285
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.36818568238371485,
            0.0,
            0.9297522806036231
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf_284_pouffe_778851",
        "episode_history": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly in front of the pouffe in the living room?",
        "answer": "A wooden coffee table with a glass top.",
        "object_id": 284,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            6.109586715698242,
            0.02108585834503174,
            -2.5694522857666016
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6242946634430542,
            0.0,
            0.7811889484603093
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf_285_coffee_table_868419",
        "episode_history": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the coffee table in the living room?",
        "answer": "A glass surface.",
        "object_id": 285,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            5.0028076171875,
            0.02108585834503174,
            -2.041510820388794
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5499967804060059,
            0.0,
            0.8351667746881624
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf_347_dining_table_683077",
        "episode_history": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to have a family meal together?",
        "answer": "The dining table in the dining room.",
        "object_id": 347,
        "class": "dining table",
        "position": [
            2.1347744464874268,
            0.02108585834503174,
            -2.3502769470214844
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.517733892321096,
            0.0,
            0.8555417095279737
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf_511_table_709411",
        "episode_history": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the small table with tools and supplies?",
        "answer": "The small table with tools and supplies is in the workshop, positioned in front of the blue workbench and under the window. It is surrounded by various items, including red containers and a lawnmower.",
        "object_id": 511,
        "class": "table",
        "position": [
            5.2865118980407715,
            0.02108585834503174,
            2.9977376461029053
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.95969759027861,
            0.0,
            0.28103475801656497
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf_396_washing_machine_and_dryer_332722",
        "episode_history": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located between the wooden cabinet and the sink in the utility room?",
        "answer": "A washing machine and dryer.",
        "object_id": 396,
        "class": "washing machine and dryer",
        "position": [
            2.000760316848755,
            0.02108585834503174,
            4.131844520568848
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3564612654887866,
            0.0,
            0.934310101736106
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf_402_ladder_851128",
        "episode_history": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the metal ladder in the garage?",
        "answer": "The metal ladder is in the garage, leaning against the wall next to the open door and near the washing machine.",
        "object_id": 402,
        "class": "ladder",
        "position": [
            4.764730453491211,
            0.02108585834503174,
            1.2568597793579102
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6513190650500689,
            0.0,
            0.7588039769942592
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf_446_trash_bag_795783",
        "episode_history": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the purple trash bag in the garage?",
        "answer": "The purple trash bag is on the floor of the garage, near the red and orange fuel containers, and next to the blue workbench.",
        "object_id": 446,
        "class": "trash bag",
        "position": [
            1.5978741645812988,
            0.02108585834503174,
            3.2514257431030273
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9180274108824314,
            0.0,
            0.3965169263329112
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf_512_trash_bag_464906",
        "episode_history": "00087-YY8rqV6L6rf",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to dispose of the garbage in the workshop?",
        "answer": "The trash bag next to the wooden cabinet.",
        "object_id": 512,
        "class": "trash bag",
        "position": [
            5.072184085845947,
            0.02108585834503174,
            3.732074737548828
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9929754737111393,
            0.0,
            0.11832036430021854
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_257_lamp_506945",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on top of the ornate wooden cabinet next to the door in the living room?",
        "answer": "A lamp.",
        "object_id": 257,
        "class": "lamp",
        "position": [
            -0.7715491056442261,
            0.19285917282104492,
            -0.8428569436073303
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9832488918962288,
            0.0,
            0.18226798014143494
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_185_basket_of_something_494706",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the basket next to the door filled with items?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 185,
        "class": "basket of something",
        "position": [
            0.7281949520111084,
            0.19285917282104492,
            -5.4902262687683105
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4878838023651183,
            0.0,
            0.8729085836384897
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_190_refrigerator_190505",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the surface finish of the refrigerator that is next to the blue cabinets and near the door leading outside?",
        "answer": "Stainless steel.",
        "object_id": 190,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -0.8251848220825195,
            0.19285917282104492,
            -3.2097103595733643
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.1623741319590718,
            0.0,
            0.9867292644239036
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_194_bar_chair_387134",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bar chair with the wooden backrest?",
        "answer": "The bar chair with the wooden backrest is at the kitchen island, facing the kitchen counter, next to another similar bar chair.",
        "object_id": 194,
        "class": "bar chair",
        "position": [
            -0.9818381667137146,
            0.19285917282104492,
            -0.8525248765945435
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.277971861984953,
            0.0,
            0.9605892170665973
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_195_bar_chair_600843",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly in front of the bar chair at the kitchen island?",
        "answer": "The kitchen island counter.",
        "object_id": 195,
        "class": "bar chair",
        "position": [
            -1.1893458366394043,
            0.19285917282104492,
            -0.6725572347640991
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.12123530445659621,
            0.0,
            0.9926237962860434
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_214_kitchen_counter_698558",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located to the right of the kitchen counter next to the stove?",
        "answer": "A bread box.",
        "object_id": 214,
        "class": "kitchen counter",
        "position": [
            -2.479606866836548,
            0.19285917282104492,
            -5.044375896453857
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8257737267507231,
            0.0,
            0.5640015533739442
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_217_dishrag_545357",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object hanging on the handle of the dishwasher next to the sink in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A dishrag.",
        "object_id": 217,
        "class": "dishrag",
        "position": [
            -3.6150550842285156,
            0.19285917282104492,
            -4.861614227294922
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.43677673079288953,
            0.0,
            0.8995699458284918
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_218_coffee_machine_212807",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the coffee machine on the kitchen counter next to the refrigerator clean?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 218,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            -3.377373218536377,
            0.19285917282104492,
            -5.2630720138549805
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.400742878013042,
            0.0,
            0.9161905619039219
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_220_microwave_685456",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located above the stove in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A microwave.",
        "object_id": 220,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -1.961077094078064,
            0.19285917282104492,
            -5.254621982574463
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7265696173742622,
            0.0,
            0.6870928547937449
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_232_tv_904344",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the TV that is placed in the corner cabinet near the window with a wooden frame?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 232,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -3.8697879314422607,
            0.19285917282104492,
            -0.9305959939956665
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.981455092120045,
            0.0,
            0.19169220680985974
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_322_tv_70915",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on top of the wooden cabinet between the two windows in the living room?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 322,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            2.963984727859497,
            -1.2071408033370972,
            -1.1202033758163452
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9130822871287224,
            0.0,
            0.4077753510596019
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_259_coffee_table_935627",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the coffee table in the living room?",
        "answer": "A window with multiple panes.",
        "object_id": 259,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            -0.13466806709766388,
            0.19285917282104492,
            -1.1735436916351318
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8145484662423099,
            0.0,
            0.5800955060524952
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_261_lounge_chair_905513",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the turquoise blanket on the lounge chair in the living room neatly folded?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 261,
        "class": "lounge chair",
        "position": [
            -1.2341854572296143,
            0.19285917282104492,
            -0.028612256050109863
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4537047735708517,
            0.0,
            0.8911520512454776
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_262_blanket_85721",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the green object draped over the back of the chair in the living room near the large window?",
        "answer": "A blanket.",
        "object_id": 262,
        "class": "blanket",
        "position": [
            -4.011076927185059,
            0.19285917282104492,
            -3.4127180576324463
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9816785605608571,
            0.0,
            0.19054449279673208
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_449_shower_cabin_48312",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the shower cabin in the bathroom open?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 449,
        "class": "shower cabin",
        "position": [
            4.2968034744262695,
            -1.2071408033370972,
            -5.356200218200684
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9145895573826335,
            0.0,
            0.40438340906451464
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_463_washing_machine_223394",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash my clothes?",
        "answer": "The washing machine next to the dryer.",
        "object_id": 463,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            3.31925368309021,
            -1.2071408033370972,
            -2.8479340076446533
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.08419978873857314,
            0.0,
            0.9964488926063291
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_470_clothes_hamper_492173",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the white object located between the curtain and the bathroom counter?",
        "answer": "A clothes hamper.",
        "object_id": 470,
        "class": "clothes hamper",
        "position": [
            2.737191677093506,
            -1.2071408033370972,
            -4.514793395996094
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6750902523177257,
            0.0,
            0.7377351497831653
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_511_ladder_872771",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object with steps located near the wooden cabinets in the basement?",
        "answer": "A ladder.",
        "object_id": 511,
        "class": "ladder",
        "position": [
            -3.1801273822784424,
            -2.6071407794952393,
            -3.220277786254883
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.017028886067167077,
            0.0,
            0.9998549980068667
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_527_ladder_593228",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the ladder that is positioned next to the wooden cabinets and a mirror in the basement?",
        "answer": "Blue.",
        "object_id": 527,
        "class": "ladder",
        "position": [
            -3.387726306915283,
            -2.6071407794952393,
            -4.00009298324585
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.16463203562816286,
            0.0,
            0.9863550541488229
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_519_air_conditioner_770131",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the air conditioner that is placed on the floor near the water heater and the blue tank?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 519,
        "class": "air conditioner",
        "position": [
            -1.7093088626861572,
            -2.6071407794952393,
            -4.150198936462402
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6040206608875496,
            0.0,
            0.7969686576151962
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_528_cart_752940",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the blue cart in the basement?",
        "answer": "The blue cart is in the basement, positioned near the wooden cabinets and next to the window. It is placed against the wall, close to some buckets and other storage items.",
        "object_id": 528,
        "class": "cart",
        "position": [
            -0.4292527139186859,
            -2.6071407794952393,
            -3.9433348178863525
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3920460244229665,
            0.0,
            0.9199456042256775
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_552_chair_5723",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the cushion of the chair that is next to the wooden cabinet and under the blue storage boxes?",
        "answer": "The pattern on the cushion is a checkered design.",
        "object_id": 552,
        "class": "chair",
        "position": [
            -2.3766095638275146,
            -2.6071407794952393,
            -2.079284906387329
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9271803495243368,
            0.0,
            0.37461526858355465
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb_594_luggage_88883",
        "episode_history": "00096-6HRFAUDqpTb",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to pack my clothes and belongings for a trip?",
        "answer": "The luggage on the shelf in the basement.",
        "object_id": 594,
        "class": "luggage",
        "position": [
            -2.1757445335388184,
            -2.6071407794952393,
            -4.287562370300293
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.870112786724383,
            0.0,
            0.4928526538213306
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_13_tv_stand_249345",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the white TV stand with the television on it?",
        "answer": "The white TV stand with the television on it is against the wall, next to the blue sofa and on the wooden floor, partially on the edge of a carpet.",
        "object_id": 13,
        "class": "tv stand",
        "position": [
            -1.472100853919983,
            0.039113134145736694,
            5.750222206115723
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.1264954168382774,
            0.0,
            0.9919671917553072
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_47_chest_of_drawers_473432",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I store my clothes neatly?",
        "answer": "The chest of drawers in the corner of the room.",
        "object_id": 47,
        "class": "chest of drawers",
        "position": [
            1.5734254121780396,
            0.039113134145736694,
            4.473620414733887
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9981579273987528,
            0.0,
            0.06066920117341181
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_144_chest_of_drawers_734768",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object against the wall near the window in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A chest of drawers.",
        "object_id": 144,
        "class": "chest of drawers",
        "position": [
            -2.051196575164795,
            0.039113134145736694,
            -0.25504612922668457
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8225883576564706,
            0.0,
            0.5686373130986306
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_52_laptop_691537",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly behind the laptop on the table?",
        "answer": "A chair.",
        "object_id": 52,
        "class": "laptop",
        "position": [
            2.806138515472412,
            0.039113134145736694,
            6.05573034286499
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.005528402874280484,
            0.0,
            0.9999847182640641
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_213_mirror_610645",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the mirror on the wall in the hallway clean?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 213,
        "class": "mirror",
        "position": [
            5.958473205566406,
            0.039113134145736694,
            -1.4194190502166748
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7401107010815241,
            0.0,
            0.672485055703556
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_68_bouquet_296910",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the flowers in the bouquet that is placed in the corner near the sink in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The flowers are pink and green.",
        "object_id": 68,
        "class": "bouquet",
        "position": [
            -3.065706968307495,
            0.039113134145736694,
            1.587594747543335
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9716722972811555,
            0.0,
            0.2363322802673442
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_71_bathroom_towel_387251",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the brown bathroom towel?",
        "answer": "The brown bathroom towel is hanging on the wall next to the sink and above the bathroom scale, near the shower area.",
        "object_id": 71,
        "class": "bathroom towel",
        "position": [
            -3.2588770389556885,
            0.039113134145736694,
            1.6921024322509766
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9621144499481958,
            0.0,
            0.2726458970915939
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_402_bathroom_towel_458371",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the bathroom towel hanging on the wall?",
        "answer": "A large mirror with a light fixture above it.",
        "object_id": 402,
        "class": "bathroom towel",
        "position": [
            4.534876346588135,
            0.039113134145736694,
            -1.906754493713379
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.42922844636909063,
            0.0,
            0.9031959592622061
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_403_sink_cabinet_748991",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the red object below the mirror in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A sink cabinet.",
        "object_id": 403,
        "class": "sink cabinet",
        "position": [
            4.430514812469482,
            0.039113134145736694,
            -1.3891801834106445
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.21029038260391852,
            0.0,
            0.9776389696530604
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_76_toilet_929398",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the toilet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The toilet is in the bathroom, next to the bidet and near the entrance to the bedroom.",
        "object_id": 76,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -2.1528139114379883,
            0.039113134145736694,
            2.1349565982818604
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.561101125030144,
            0.0,
            0.8277472606357008
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_411_toilet_20975",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to flush away waste?",
        "answer": "The toilet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 411,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            3.856771230697632,
            0.039113134145736694,
            -3.7589669227600098
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8588241272263477,
            0.0,
            0.5122705520463791
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_131_closet_shelving_461294",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object at the end of the hallway with multiple shelves holding folded clothes?",
        "answer": "A closet shelving.",
        "object_id": 131,
        "class": "closet shelving",
        "position": [
            -2.9440622329711914,
            0.039113134145736694,
            2.1330361366271973
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7086331640581202,
            0.0,
            0.7055770962814605
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_310_tv_438580",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object mounted on the wall above the white cabinet in the living room?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 310,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            9.100372314453125,
            0.039113134145736694,
            -3.9610815048217773
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9973862182813329,
            0.0,
            0.07225463018001844
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_169_nightstand_12788",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the nightstand that is next to the bed with white pillows and a white bedspread?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 169,
        "class": "nightstand",
        "position": [
            -2.655219316482544,
            0.039113134145736694,
            -0.04067113250494003
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.09344400520565602,
            0.0,
            0.9956245366056048
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_178_nightstand_170396",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the nightstand that is next to the bed with white and gray pillows?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 178,
        "class": "nightstand",
        "position": [
            -5.265406131744385,
            0.039113134145736694,
            -0.17999817430973053
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.1720478320713829,
            0.0,
            0.9850885967665737
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_199_cabinet_779835",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the black piece of furniture against the wall in the hallway?",
        "answer": "A cabinet.",
        "object_id": 199,
        "class": "cabinet",
        "position": [
            4.0489630699157715,
            0.039113134145736694,
            0.5860525369644165
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6026576807133709,
            0.0,
            0.7979998244844297
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_340_cabinet_919022",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the white cabinet with the TV on top?",
        "answer": "The white cabinet with the TV on top is in the living room, against the wall opposite the windows and near the entrance door.",
        "object_id": 340,
        "class": "cabinet",
        "position": [
            7.6944146156311035,
            0.039113134145736694,
            -3.9363317489624023
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9822596300335777,
            0.0,
            0.18752604940726997
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_234_bed_table_328758",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the bed table next to the bed in the green-walled bedroom empty?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 234,
        "class": "bed table",
        "position": [
            4.782454013824463,
            0.039113134145736694,
            2.013719081878662
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9750021830364262,
            0.0,
            0.22219528139500042
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_247_clutter_310445",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is the object to the left of the clutter near the desk in the room?",
        "answer": "A desk with drawers.",
        "object_id": 247,
        "class": "clutter",
        "position": [
            5.176583766937256,
            0.039113134145736694,
            2.2958717346191406
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4789194790177004,
            0.0,
            0.8778588341056974
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_248_desk_889342",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object with drawers and a blue chair in front of it, located against the green wall in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A desk.",
        "object_id": 248,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            5.675328731536865,
            0.039113134145736694,
            2.842113733291626
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5756907381002766,
            0.0,
            0.8176675204907914
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_288_desk_168563",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the pink chair at the desk in the bedroom pushed in?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 288,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            6.711944580078125,
            0.039113134145736694,
            0.18370133638381958
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7783201981025359,
            0.0,
            0.6278675570736468
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_416_decorative_plant_801866",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the wooden shelf below the window in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A decorative plant.",
        "object_id": 416,
        "class": "decorative plant",
        "position": [
            3.9252052307128906,
            0.039113134145736694,
            -3.753688097000122
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.0430127538962452,
            0.0,
            0.9990745232475208
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_351_kitchen_appliance_788112",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the kitchen appliance that is placed on the countertop near the wooden door?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 351,
        "class": "kitchen appliance",
        "position": [
            9.484952926635742,
            0.039113134145736694,
            -6.354510307312012
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.07788584747970506,
            0.0,
            0.9969622835204791
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_364_kitchen_appliance_879852",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the kitchen counter to the right of the sink?",
        "answer": "A kitchen appliance.",
        "object_id": 364,
        "class": "kitchen appliance",
        "position": [
            8.840968132019043,
            0.039113134145736694,
            -4.995749473571777
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.044472458258176674,
            0.0,
            0.9990106107827257
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_355_cooker_18772",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the cooker on the purple countertop in the kitchen clean?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 355,
        "class": "cooker",
        "position": [
            9.145458221435547,
            0.039113134145736694,
            -6.060197353363037
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6315848031298232,
            0.0,
            0.7753068015021294
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_362_microwave_500352",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the microwave above the refrigerator in the kitchen open?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 362,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            9.754518508911133,
            0.039113134145736694,
            -6.060906887054443
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8178814112288878,
            0.0,
            0.5753868239421571
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id_363_kitchen_extractor_912522",
        "episode_history": "00108-oStKKWkQ1id",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the kitchen extractor in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A stovetop.",
        "object_id": 363,
        "class": "kitchen extractor",
        "position": [
            9.841556549072266,
            0.039113134145736694,
            -6.794971466064453
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.791815869489474,
            0.0,
            0.6107598782047068
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00143-5Kw4nGdqYtS_91_washing_machine_607188",
        "episode_history": "00143-5Kw4nGdqYtS",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the washing machine located?",
        "answer": "The washing machine is in the laundry room, positioned between the dryer and the wooden cabinets, under the countertop.",
        "object_id": 91,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -0.9667859077453613,
            -2.3581573963165283,
            0.982724666595459
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7170856151945428,
            0.0,
            0.6969850934425097
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00143-5Kw4nGdqYtS_92_washing_machine_947889",
        "episode_history": "00143-5Kw4nGdqYtS",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the washing machine located?",
        "answer": "The washing machine is in the kitchen, next to the dryer and under the wooden cabinets, near the tiled backsplash.",
        "object_id": 92,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -1.1049985885620117,
            -2.3581573963165283,
            0.8651893138885498
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6532562215078498,
            0.0,
            0.7571369156640608
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00143-5Kw4nGdqYtS_273_basket_of_something_680726",
        "episode_history": "00143-5Kw4nGdqYtS",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is hanging on the wall above the basket near the kitchen entrance?",
        "answer": "Several towels are hanging on the wall above the basket.",
        "object_id": 273,
        "class": "basket of something",
        "position": [
            -1.0140947103500366,
            0.04184269905090332,
            1.776425838470459
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7531521142107724,
            0.0,
            0.6578464052192149
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00143-5Kw4nGdqYtS_282_cutting_board_195983",
        "episode_history": "00143-5Kw4nGdqYtS",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the cutting board that is placed on the kitchen counter near the window?",
        "answer": "Rectangular.",
        "object_id": 282,
        "class": "cutting board",
        "position": [
            -0.5547090172767639,
            0.04184269905090332,
            1.1531572341918945
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5012644081915306,
            0.0,
            0.8652941656340892
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00143-5Kw4nGdqYtS_379_coffee_table_577246",
        "episode_history": "00143-5Kw4nGdqYtS",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object between the red armchair and the lamp in the living room?",
        "answer": "A coffee table.",
        "object_id": 379,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            -3.216809034347534,
            0.04184269905090332,
            5.808135509490967
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8085622919500597,
            0.0,
            0.5884105879710751
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00143-5Kw4nGdqYtS_396_small_table_stand_606491",
        "episode_history": "00143-5Kw4nGdqYtS",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the small table/stand that is located below two framed pictures on the wooden wall?",
        "answer": "Wood.",
        "object_id": 396,
        "class": "small table/stand",
        "position": [
            -1.2808268070220947,
            0.04184269905090332,
            1.8404872417449951
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.23668585146573873,
            0.0,
            0.9715862327739819
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00143-5Kw4nGdqYtS_497_small_table_stand_520653",
        "episode_history": "00143-5Kw4nGdqYtS",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed between the bunk bed and the door in the wooden room?",
        "answer": "A small table/stand.",
        "object_id": 497,
        "class": "small table/stand",
        "position": [
            -0.5187129378318787,
            2.641842842102051,
            4.408841133117676
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9996581152180679,
            0.0,
            0.026146752734408585
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00143-5Kw4nGdqYtS_505_bath_towel_888404",
        "episode_history": "00143-5Kw4nGdqYtS",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to dry myself after a shower?",
        "answer": "The bath towel hanging on the rack.",
        "object_id": 505,
        "class": "bath towel",
        "position": [
            1.5462515354156494,
            2.641842842102051,
            0.40144503116607666
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9942947684670717,
            0.0,
            0.10666730238931187
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00143-5Kw4nGdqYtS_519_bathroom_cabinet_423152",
        "episode_history": "00143-5Kw4nGdqYtS",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wooden bathroom cabinet with toiletries?",
        "answer": "The wooden bathroom cabinet with toiletries is in the bathroom, next to the bathtub and under the towel rack.",
        "object_id": 519,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            0.23265302181243896,
            2.641842842102051,
            1.7893484830856323
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6935101242062144,
            0.0,
            0.7204468805009021
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00143-5Kw4nGdqYtS_520_bathtub_677367",
        "episode_history": "00143-5Kw4nGdqYtS",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wooden bathtub?",
        "answer": "The wooden bathtub is in the bathroom, positioned against the wall under the window, next to the toilet.",
        "object_id": 520,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            0.21717435121536255,
            2.641842842102051,
            1.8526095151901245
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.43818031459115286,
            0.0,
            0.8988870963056474
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN_279_washing_machine_794947",
        "episode_history": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the washing machine in the laundry room open?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 279,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            0.5380448698997498,
            3.2586965560913086,
            -7.37189245223999
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8957931423670041,
            0.0,
            0.44447119826626363
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN_280_washing_machine_776215",
        "episode_history": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash my clothes?",
        "answer": "The washing machine in the laundry room.",
        "object_id": 280,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            1.0160526037216187,
            3.2586965560913086,
            -7.321842193603516
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8722312281341299,
            0.0,
            0.4890937381194197
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN_284_vacuum_cleaner_454547",
        "episode_history": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the black and yellow object standing against the wall next to the step ladder in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "A vacuum cleaner.",
        "object_id": 284,
        "class": "vacuum cleaner",
        "position": [
            3.685713768005371,
            3.2586965560913086,
            -6.591679096221924
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5456987462852043,
            0.0,
            0.8379814307624939
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN_424_shower_bench_120114",
        "episode_history": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object inside the shower area that is attached to the wall and can be used for sitting?",
        "answer": "A shower bench.",
        "object_id": 424,
        "class": "shower bench",
        "position": [
            -4.897974967956543,
            3.2586965560913086,
            -12.141737937927246
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9997505875469147,
            0.0,
            0.02233299576060663
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN_451_desk_750128",
        "episode_history": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the desk in the closet area?",
        "answer": "A window with red floral curtains.",
        "object_id": 451,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            9.248154640197754,
            3.2586965560913086,
            -8.499225616455078
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7977117075812248,
            0.0,
            0.6030389967388897
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN_465_bag_50037",
        "episode_history": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the black and white object with a floral pattern on the bottom shelf of the closet next to the hanging clothes?",
        "answer": "A bag.",
        "object_id": 465,
        "class": "bag",
        "position": [
            7.146313667297363,
            3.2586965560913086,
            -7.366890907287598
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9439846407865673,
            0.0,
            0.32998939067651173
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN_837_microwave_549641",
        "episode_history": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A decorative item (possibly a statue or figurine).",
        "object_id": 837,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            3.570694923400879,
            0.05869650840759277,
            -10.903938293457031
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7507460307139078,
            0.0,
            0.660590945568672
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN_848_kitchen_table_387063",
        "episode_history": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the kitchen table located?",
        "answer": "The kitchen table is near the sliding glass door that leads to the patio, adjacent to the small desk area with cabinets.",
        "object_id": 848,
        "class": "kitchen table",
        "position": [
            0.9241011142730713,
            0.05869650840759277,
            -10.119275093078613
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.05657085527037952,
            0.0,
            0.9983985869050385
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN_1001_sitting_bench_841271",
        "episode_history": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the floral sitting bench?",
        "answer": "The floral sitting bench is in the room with the wooden cabinet and mirror, next to a stack of boxes and a plant.",
        "object_id": 1001,
        "class": "sitting bench",
        "position": [
            1.7298682928085327,
            -2.9413034915924072,
            -10.202959060668945
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9344952775795816,
            0.0,
            0.35597552750359185
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN_945_bowl_with_sweets_724961",
        "episode_history": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly behind the bowl with sweets on the coffee table in the living room?",
        "answer": "A floral-patterned sofa with red pillows.",
        "object_id": 945,
        "class": "bowl with sweets",
        "position": [
            -4.040170192718506,
            0.05869650840759277,
            -11.286422729492188
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9018209897292868,
            0.0,
            0.4321098268770214
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN_1064_decorative_vase_31335",
        "episode_history": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the decorative vase next to the door in the corner of the room empty?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 1064,
        "class": "decorative vase",
        "position": [
            -4.02499532699585,
            -2.9413034915924072,
            -8.544318199157715
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9070721771974687,
            0.0,
            0.4209751362660792
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN_1027_pot_997301",
        "episode_history": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the bottom shelf inside the wooden cabinet next to the armchair in the living room?",
        "answer": "A pot.",
        "object_id": 1027,
        "class": "pot",
        "position": [
            3.783766269683838,
            -2.9413034915924072,
            -9.663675308227539
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7736351217011856,
            0.0,
            0.6336313584967144
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN_1044_folded_chair_457280",
        "episode_history": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object leaning against the wooden cabinet in the room?",
        "answer": "A folded chair.",
        "object_id": 1044,
        "class": "folded chair",
        "position": [
            0.9978853464126587,
            -2.9413034915924072,
            -10.891739845275879
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.04550654639998242,
            0.0,
            0.998964040511342
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN_1045_fan_339258",
        "episode_history": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the fan that is positioned next to the wooden cabinet in the living room?",
        "answer": "Blue.",
        "object_id": 1045,
        "class": "fan",
        "position": [
            2.1759355068206787,
            -2.9413034915924072,
            -10.367873191833496
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2656934194147293,
            0.0,
            0.9640575744631171
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN_1153_screen_361922",
        "episode_history": "00149-UuwwmrTsfBN",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to watch a movie in this room?",
        "answer": "The screen at the front of the room.",
        "object_id": 1153,
        "class": "screen",
        "position": [
            -3.7751200199127197,
            -2.9413034915924072,
            -2.5576229095458984
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9988208080363904,
            0.0,
            0.048548876748455635
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00155-iLDo95ZbDJq_141_oven_943005",
        "episode_history": "00155-iLDo95ZbDJq",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the double oven located?",
        "answer": "The double oven is in the kitchen, built into the cabinetry to the right of the stove and range hood, near the countertop with the coffee maker.",
        "object_id": 141,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            -4.996062755584717,
            0.11437656730413437,
            4.993079662322998
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7564222839781742,
            0.0,
            0.6540835789876109
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00155-iLDo95ZbDJq_426_box_928228",
        "episode_history": "00155-iLDo95ZbDJq",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the blue decorative box on the wicker nightstand next to the bed in the bedroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 426,
        "class": "box",
        "position": [
            3.751765489578247,
            0.11437656730413437,
            1.7206363677978516
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6581748989901945,
            0.0,
            0.7528650625040634
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00155-iLDo95ZbDJq_335_washing_machine_209304",
        "episode_history": "00155-iLDo95ZbDJq",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the washing machine that is next to the window with a white blind and below the decorative \"love\" sign?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 335,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -8.144952774047852,
            0.11437656730413437,
            0.9759376049041748
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.42506137830127244,
            0.0,
            0.9051645290645356
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00155-iLDo95ZbDJq_336_washing_machine_270020",
        "episode_history": "00155-iLDo95ZbDJq",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the washing machine located?",
        "answer": "The washing machine is in the laundry room, next to the window and below the \"Love\" sign on the counter.",
        "object_id": 336,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -8.075029373168945,
            0.11437656730413437,
            1.5662070512771606
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4207465965980419,
            0.0,
            0.9071782082100323
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb_17_wall_clock_63308",
        "episode_history": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the wall clock that is mounted above the framed certificate and next to the wooden cabinet?",
        "answer": "It is in circular shape.",
        "object_id": 17,
        "class": "wall clock",
        "position": [
            -3.5687146186828613,
            0.11970052123069763,
            0.7244597673416138
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.07691545497201337,
            0.0,
            0.9970376185412706
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb_24_book_736999",
        "episode_history": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the book on top of the small wooden cabinet next to the sofa in the living room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 24,
        "class": "book",
        "position": [
            -3.168102741241455,
            0.11970052123069763,
            0.7314521670341492
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2562748508102661,
            0.0,
            0.966603952424247
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb_26_sofa_chair_812197",
        "episode_history": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the brown sofa chair in the living room?",
        "answer": "The brown sofa chair is in the living room, positioned near the wooden door and next to a floor lamp with a green base. It is also adjacent to a small wooden cabinet and below a wall clock.",
        "object_id": 26,
        "class": "sofa chair",
        "position": [
            -1.6369431018829346,
            0.11970052123069763,
            2.6006107330322266
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.1873018690112021,
            0.0,
            0.9823024024529873
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb_30_sofa_chair_90219",
        "episode_history": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the sofa chair near the window?",
        "answer": "A wooden side table with a lamp on it.",
        "object_id": 30,
        "class": "sofa chair",
        "position": [
            -2.5953805446624756,
            0.11970052123069763,
            3.4887425899505615
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.31544305840168363,
            0.0,
            0.9489445067580042
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb_29_stuffed_animal_600203",
        "episode_history": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the stuffed animal on the backrest of the brown sofa in the living room facing towards the window shutters?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 29,
        "class": "stuffed animal",
        "position": [
            -2.026914358139038,
            0.11970052123069763,
            0.7043322920799255
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2409835826610211,
            0.0,
            0.9705291921873648
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb_39_tv_217558",
        "episode_history": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to watch my favorite shows and movies?",
        "answer": "The TV on the wooden stand.",
        "object_id": 39,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -3.2694320678710938,
            0.11970052123069763,
            4.127305030822754
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5097030118157827,
            0.0,
            0.8603504168336993
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb_237_tv_597048",
        "episode_history": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to watch my favorite shows?",
        "answer": "The TV on the round table.",
        "object_id": 237,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -6.812170028686523,
            2.719700574874878,
            2.019075393676758
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8530015075926148,
            0.0,
            0.5219084479530163
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb_204_speaker_58199",
        "episode_history": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the speaker on the small table next to the window in the corner of the room turned on?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 204,
        "class": "speaker",
        "position": [
            -2.3650429248809814,
            2.719700574874878,
            2.7647335529327393
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8166102260321095,
            0.0,
            0.5771895171776659
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb_49_fireplace_280214",
        "episode_history": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there a cushion on the ledge in front of the fireplace in the living room?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 49,
        "class": "fireplace",
        "position": [
            -1.5244754552841187,
            0.11970052123069763,
            1.3427960872650146
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9970776368941003,
            0.0,
            0.0763949344242243
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb_61_fireplace_tool_set_527437",
        "episode_history": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are all the tools in the fireplace tool set next to the brick fireplace in the living room properly hung on the stand?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 61,
        "class": "fireplace tool set",
        "position": [
            -1.8848366737365723,
            0.11970052123069763,
            3.4531197547912598
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9999253471154961,
            0.0,
            0.012218845946379689
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb_62_basket_855362",
        "episode_history": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wicker basket in the living room?",
        "answer": "The wicker basket is on the lower shelf of the wooden TV stand, next to the fireplace with a brick surround.",
        "object_id": 62,
        "class": "basket",
        "position": [
            -2.6118011474609375,
            0.11970052123069763,
            3.487011671066284
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.704408656587085,
            0.0,
            0.7097946495467391
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb_77_trashcan_924533",
        "episode_history": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the trashcan in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A wall-mounted mail holder and several framed items.",
        "object_id": 77,
        "class": "trashcan",
        "position": [
            -7.487770080566406,
            0.11970052123069763,
            1.6080641746520996
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6990458974106929,
            0.0,
            0.7150768023878826
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb_78_refrigerator_42057",
        "episode_history": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to store my groceries and keep them fresh?",
        "answer": "The refrigerator in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 78,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -5.305443286895752,
            0.11970052123069763,
            0.18310463428497314
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9962946265134169,
            0.0,
            0.08600591363672047
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb_337_kitchen_lower_cabinet_610277",
        "episode_history": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the kitchen lower cabinet next to the stove?",
        "answer": "A granite countertop and a sink.",
        "object_id": 337,
        "class": "kitchen lower cabinet",
        "position": [
            -6.683591842651367,
            0.11970052123069763,
            2.176476240158081
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8396028374481319,
            0.0,
            0.5432007689142623
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb_88_microwave_837795",
        "episode_history": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the microwave that is placed on the granite countertop near the refrigerator?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 88,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -7.546651363372803,
            0.11970052123069763,
            2.102177381515503
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9174873859838271,
            0.0,
            0.3977648759764544
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb_100_microwave_403318",
        "episode_history": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the white electronic device placed on the small wooden cabinet next to the fire extinguisher in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A microwave.",
        "object_id": 100,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -6.443692684173584,
            0.11970052123069763,
            0.6800546050071716
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2169005848243864,
            0.0,
            0.9761936981474727
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb_124_dining_table_118847",
        "episode_history": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the dining table that is surrounded by wooden chairs in the kitchen area?",
        "answer": "Rectangular.",
        "object_id": 124,
        "class": "dining table",
        "position": [
            -9.639885902404785,
            -0.0802994966506958,
            1.3134583234786987
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5718150081550226,
            0.0,
            0.820382591507567
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb_157_toilet_222465",
        "episode_history": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located directly above the toilet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A wooden shelf with a basket on it.",
        "object_id": 157,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -6.0598554611206055,
            0.11970052123069763,
            4.672852039337158
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5004049603155591,
            0.0,
            0.8657914735613788
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb_268_toilet_27316",
        "episode_history": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to relieve myself?",
        "answer": "The toilet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 268,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -7.393233776092529,
            2.719700574874878,
            2.032212257385254
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9997660720993342,
            0.0,
            0.021628709601008034
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb_190_drawer_138031",
        "episode_history": "00164-XfUxBGTFQQb",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the top drawer of the wooden dresser next to the bed in the bedroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 190,
        "class": "drawer",
        "position": [
            -3.568298816680908,
            2.719700574874878,
            0.6199910044670105
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5942884837622662,
            0.0,
            0.8042519493713066
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00168-bHKTDQFJxTw_464_arcade_game_144912",
        "episode_history": "00168-bHKTDQFJxTw",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the screen of the arcade game machine in the corner of the room turned on?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 464,
        "class": "arcade game",
        "position": [
            19.75632095336914,
            0.062085628509521484,
            -5.320215225219727
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.992747795157339,
            0.0,
            0.12021570284385491
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z_307_desk_918598",
        "episode_history": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the drawer of the white desk next to the window in the bedroom open?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 307,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            -7.2405171394348145,
            0.11005091667175293,
            9.325398445129395
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6024892975355464,
            0.0,
            0.7981269613007218
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z_220_towel_930500",
        "episode_history": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to dry my hands after washing them?",
        "answer": "The towel hanging on the rack.",
        "object_id": 220,
        "class": "towel",
        "position": [
            1.4012404680252075,
            0.13634291291236877,
            10.12150764465332
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9677410680201165,
            0.0,
            0.2519468699295239
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z_230_bathroom_counter_793922",
        "episode_history": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to place my toiletries while getting ready in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The bathroom counter next to the shower.",
        "object_id": 230,
        "class": "bathroom counter",
        "position": [
            -0.6727823615074158,
            0.2656691074371338,
            10.36795711517334
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3216632593282991,
            0.0,
            0.9468541321651901
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z_260_stool_287410",
        "episode_history": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the small wooden object with a cushioned top next to the green armchair in the closet?",
        "answer": "A stool.",
        "object_id": 260,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            -3.382810115814209,
            0.11005091667175293,
            10.699029922485352
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7733089464714031,
            0.0,
            0.6340293946713265
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z_303_tv_504945",
        "episode_history": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the TV in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A small cabinet with a fish tank design.",
        "object_id": 303,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -9.53845500946045,
            0.11005091667175293,
            9.359610557556152
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9851295336320737,
            0.0,
            0.1718132764539898
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z_521_tv_383454",
        "episode_history": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the TV in the living room?",
        "answer": "A fireplace.",
        "object_id": 521,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            5.169161796569824,
            -3.2899491786956787,
            3.272840976715088
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5750175318108875,
            0.0,
            0.8181410869221243
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z_330_mat_857778",
        "episode_history": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the black and white patterned mat next to the bed in the bedroom properly aligned with the floor?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 330,
        "class": "mat",
        "position": [
            -10.142768859863281,
            0.11005091667175293,
            9.38011360168457
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9681432334340843,
            0.0,
            0.25039704382399663
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z_436_chandelier_163566",
        "episode_history": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the ornate object hanging from the ceiling above the dining table in the dining room?",
        "answer": "A chandelier.",
        "object_id": 436,
        "class": "chandelier",
        "position": [
            -4.124080657958984,
            -3.2899491786956787,
            10.575074195861816
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6023421364245554,
            0.0,
            0.7982380288407102
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z_504_microwave_140972",
        "episode_history": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The microwave is mounted above the counter, next to the double oven and adjacent to the refrigerator in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 504,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            1.9520474672317505,
            -3.2899491786956787,
            10.039615631103516
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9903706068292814,
            0.0,
            0.13844154408486267
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z_505_refrigerator_223987",
        "episode_history": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the stainless steel refrigerator?",
        "answer": "The stainless steel refrigerator is in the kitchen, positioned between the microwave and the granite countertop.",
        "object_id": 505,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            2.252849817276001,
            -3.2899491786956787,
            8.796773910522461
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9907798666944448,
            0.0,
            0.1354815697906519
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z_509_stove_228318",
        "episode_history": "00172-bB6nKqfsb1z",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to cook my meals?",
        "answer": "The stove on the kitchen counter.",
        "object_id": 509,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            2.182323455810547,
            -3.2899491786956787,
            10.357056617736816
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.32684617267582927,
            0.0,
            0.9450775520597037
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y_112_storage_cabinet_850070",
        "episode_history": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the top drawer of the white storage cabinet in the room with the red walls closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 112,
        "class": "storage cabinet",
        "position": [
            -1.1347692012786865,
            0.1653902530670166,
            0.5683412551879883
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9797620435321512,
            0.0,
            0.20016577642969774
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y_118_armchair_289667",
        "episode_history": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there a cushion on the patterned armchair in the room with red walls and wooden floor?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 118,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            -2.0927352905273438,
            0.1653902530670166,
            1.4540934562683105
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4211257605405755,
            0.0,
            0.9070022567828163
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y_237_coffee_table_803012",
        "episode_history": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly in front of the coffee table in the living room?",
        "answer": "A brown leather sofa.",
        "object_id": 237,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            -7.467493534088135,
            0.1653902530670166,
            3.094672679901123
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2847221790293713,
            0.0,
            0.9586100775439234
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y_245_vase_182589",
        "episode_history": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the vase that is placed on the wooden cabinet near the television?",
        "answer": "The vase is white.",
        "object_id": 245,
        "class": "vase",
        "position": [
            -5.693474292755127,
            0.1653902530670166,
            1.817406177520752
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.31802313519035036,
            0.0,
            0.948082952849433
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y_498_couch_556338",
        "episode_history": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the beige couch located?",
        "answer": "The beige couch is in the basement, against the wall near the entrance to the bathroom, with a coffee table in front of it and a dog bed to its right.",
        "object_id": 498,
        "class": "couch",
        "position": [
            -5.551052093505859,
            -2.234609842300415,
            4.375973701477051
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.27104266764668306,
            0.0,
            0.962567333912267
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y_247_box_with_toys_521787",
        "episode_history": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object inside the wooden crate next to the brown leather sofa in the living room?",
        "answer": "A box with toys.",
        "object_id": 247,
        "class": "box with toys",
        "position": [
            -5.382091045379639,
            0.19483187794685364,
            2.703282356262207
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5428005067018253,
            0.0,
            0.8398616611825078
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y_469_bathroom_cabinet_915998",
        "episode_history": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the bathroom cabinet under the mirror in the bathroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 469,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            -5.747254371643066,
            -2.234609842300415,
            1.282780647277832
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.33212808913634806,
            0.0,
            0.9432342934852602
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y_520_laundry_machine_901737",
        "episode_history": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the laundry machine in the basement?",
        "answer": "A sink with a red towel hanging on it.",
        "object_id": 520,
        "class": "laundry machine",
        "position": [
            -4.641973972320557,
            -2.234609842300415,
            5.5251569747924805
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6915687247531748,
            0.0,
            0.7223106665024874
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y_521_laundry_machine_963406",
        "episode_history": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the laundry machine located?",
        "answer": "The laundry machine is in the basement, next to the utility sink and near the ironing board, with a wooden cabinet and countertop on the left side.",
        "object_id": 521,
        "class": "laundry machine",
        "position": [
            -6.747563362121582,
            -2.234609842300415,
            3.9218826293945312
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9797188621189465,
            0.0,
            0.20037702265568383
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y_569_pet_bowl_607848",
        "episode_history": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the pet bowl next to the mat with the text \"Wipe Your Paws\" in the corner of the room filled with food?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 569,
        "class": "pet bowl",
        "position": [
            -5.769455432891846,
            -2.234609842300415,
            1.9990134239196777
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.23439224109978968,
            0.0,
            0.9721421075708109
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y_609_ladder_989257",
        "episode_history": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the yellow object with steps near the red basket and green bag in the basement?",
        "answer": "A ladder.",
        "object_id": 609,
        "class": "ladder",
        "position": [
            -0.1741466224193573,
            -2.234609842300415,
            0.9854907393455505
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4126897855880996,
            0.0,
            0.9108716379771896
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y_618_bicycle_95278",
        "episode_history": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the primary color of the bicycle that is parked near the furnace and the storage shelves in the basement?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 618,
        "class": "bicycle",
        "position": [
            -0.1992495059967041,
            -2.234609842300415,
            -0.2728203535079956
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.869701420384584,
            0.0,
            0.49357819986405127
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y_619_bicycle_635651",
        "episode_history": "00173-qZ4B7U6XE5Y",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to go for a ride around the neighborhood?",
        "answer": "The bicycle in the basement.",
        "object_id": 619,
        "class": "bicycle",
        "position": [
            -0.6145372986793518,
            -2.234609842300415,
            0.723017692565918
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8178874290113863,
            0.0,
            0.5753782698930717
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw_31_bath_tub_555092",
        "episode_history": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to take a bath?",
        "answer": "The bathtub in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 31,
        "class": "bath tub",
        "position": [
            3.2684030532836914,
            0.17856313288211823,
            -2.6701548099517822
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.035879867949142615,
            0.0,
            0.9993561102409652
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw_65_bath_tub_454155",
        "episode_history": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to take a bath?",
        "answer": "The bathtub in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 65,
        "class": "bath tub",
        "position": [
            7.32051420211792,
            0.028199851512908936,
            -4.152742385864258
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4957352358179913,
            0.0,
            0.8684737048227082
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw_109_carpet_421753",
        "episode_history": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the floor between the two blue armchairs in the living room?",
        "answer": "A carpet.",
        "object_id": 109,
        "class": "carpet",
        "position": [
            8.258764266967773,
            0.028199851512908936,
            -3.4974985122680664
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.43665531791750806,
            0.0,
            0.8996288864494959
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw_139_desk_38821",
        "episode_history": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the desk that is positioned below the large clock on the wall?",
        "answer": "Brown.",
        "object_id": 139,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            8.403846740722656,
            0.028199851512908936,
            -4.350174427032471
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.778720948456149,
            0.0,
            0.6273704523131096
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw_194_dinner_table_489514",
        "episode_history": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the dinner table with the beige chairs?",
        "answer": "The dinner table with the beige chairs is in the dining area, next to a large potted plant and under a modern chandelier, adjacent to the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 194,
        "class": "dinner table",
        "position": [
            12.028677940368652,
            0.028199851512908936,
            3.6799938678741455
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.47293052300077265,
            0.0,
            0.8810997221734982
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw_247_washing_machine_195888",
        "episode_history": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object stacked in the narrow hallway next to the black door?",
        "answer": "A washing machine.",
        "object_id": 247,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            5.509421348571777,
            0.028199851512908936,
            0.15612781047821045
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.10781146042016117,
            0.0,
            0.9941713579670619
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw_395_sink_351790",
        "episode_history": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the kitchen sink?",
        "answer": "The kitchen sink is located on the island counter near the door, with a view of the living room and the dining area.",
        "object_id": 395,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            10.604312896728516,
            0.028199851512908936,
            -2.549238920211792
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9226582977192597,
            0.0,
            0.38561854941094065
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw_330_bedside_cabinet_13637",
        "episode_history": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on top of the bedside cabinet next to the bed?",
        "answer": "A lamp.",
        "object_id": 330,
        "class": "bedside cabinet",
        "position": [
            1.7356339693069458,
            0.028199851512908936,
            2.765442371368408
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7035516434357245,
            0.0,
            0.7106441338805881
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw_349_chest_of_drawers_992147",
        "episode_history": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I store my clothes in this room?",
        "answer": "The chest of drawers next to the bed.",
        "object_id": 349,
        "class": "chest of drawers",
        "position": [
            2.958909511566162,
            0.028199851512908936,
            0.12859663367271423
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.915409726905827,
            0.0,
            0.4025233308594662
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw_374_stool_408493",
        "episode_history": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object with a round base located at the kitchen counter?",
        "answer": "A stool.",
        "object_id": 374,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            13.848323822021484,
            0.028199851512908936,
            -0.8395239114761353
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7006498576335146,
            0.0,
            0.7135052746813688
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw_375_stool_833865",
        "episode_history": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the white stool at the kitchen island pulled out?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 375,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            9.587881088256836,
            0.028199851512908936,
            -0.01856844872236252
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5204846526021467,
            0.0,
            0.853871024456049
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw_399_fridge_178801",
        "episode_history": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the fridge in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A countertop with a decorative object.",
        "object_id": 399,
        "class": "fridge",
        "position": [
            12.23747730255127,
            0.028199851512908936,
            -2.043201446533203
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7088578769134263,
            0.0,
            0.7053513382264117
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw_400_range_hood_665084",
        "episode_history": "00177-VSxVP19Cdyw",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the metallic object located above the stove in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A range hood.",
        "object_id": 400,
        "class": "range hood",
        "position": [
            10.27462100982666,
            0.028199851512908936,
            -2.003178119659424
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3285541644328192,
            0.0,
            0.9444851301285013
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00188-dQrLTxHvLXU_43_bathrobe_729801",
        "episode_history": "00188-dQrLTxHvLXU",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to dry myself off after a shower?",
        "answer": "The bathrobe hanging on the wall.",
        "object_id": 43,
        "class": "bathrobe",
        "position": [
            -1.100762128829956,
            2.8822133541107178,
            -2.387655019760132
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9999619206509928,
            0.0,
            0.008726811973156366
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00210-j2EJhFEQGCL_78_microwave_371933",
        "episode_history": "00210-j2EJhFEQGCL",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the built-in microwave in the kitchen closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 78,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -8.68602180480957,
            0.12694469094276428,
            -4.678424835205078
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.20706434256616624,
            0.0,
            0.9783273266333928
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00210-j2EJhFEQGCL_84_bread_bin_537683",
        "episode_history": "00210-j2EJhFEQGCL",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to store my bread to keep it fresh?",
        "answer": "The bread bin on the kitchen counter.",
        "object_id": 84,
        "class": "bread bin",
        "position": [
            -8.513484954833984,
            0.12694469094276428,
            -5.033051013946533
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.1284329150532532,
            0.0,
            0.9917181990519907
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00210-j2EJhFEQGCL_167_guitar_180179",
        "episode_history": "00210-j2EJhFEQGCL",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object standing on a stand next to the console table in the hallway?",
        "answer": "A guitar.",
        "object_id": 167,
        "class": "guitar",
        "position": [
            -10.555819511413574,
            0.12694469094276428,
            -0.7214801907539368
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.31521835552287925,
            0.0,
            0.9490191717459936
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00210-j2EJhFEQGCL_173_tv_939243",
        "episode_history": "00210-j2EJhFEQGCL",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to watch my favorite shows and movies?",
        "answer": "The TV mounted on the wall.",
        "object_id": 173,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -10.34382438659668,
            0.12694469094276428,
            -0.48673775792121887
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9665229930291647,
            0.0,
            0.2565800147048571
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00210-j2EJhFEQGCL_429_footrest_469669",
        "episode_history": "00210-j2EJhFEQGCL",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the footrest that matches the wooden chair with the blanket draped over it?",
        "answer": "The footrest is in the room with large glass sliding doors, positioned directly in front of the wooden chair with the blanket draped over it, near the deck outside.",
        "object_id": 429,
        "class": "footrest",
        "position": [
            0.4095747470855713,
            0.12694469094276428,
            6.244913578033447
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4628596344192778,
            0.0,
            0.8864315872221908
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00210-j2EJhFEQGCL_457_pouffe_566388",
        "episode_history": "00210-j2EJhFEQGCL",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the pouffe located?",
        "answer": "The pouffe is in the bathroom, right next to the bathtub and near the entrance to the toilet area.",
        "object_id": 457,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            2.4902451038360596,
            0.12694469094276428,
            -1.0002191066741943
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9354062463317897,
            0.0,
            0.3535748213935361
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9_11_barrel_113445",
        "episode_history": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wooden barrel located?",
        "answer": "The wooden barrel is on the porch, positioned between two wooden chairs and near the stone wall.",
        "object_id": 11,
        "class": "barrel",
        "position": [
            10.861381530761719,
            0.0803389772772789,
            18.569976806640625
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.47218778354207064,
            0.0,
            0.8814979847246542
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9_42_refrigerator_98315",
        "episode_history": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the refrigerator that is next to the wooden cabinets and near the stove in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Silver.",
        "object_id": 42,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            7.453020095825195,
            0.13381248712539673,
            14.111532211303711
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.40119355149483277,
            0.0,
            0.9159933046911222
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9_48_microwave_515161",
        "episode_history": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the microwave that is installed above the stove and next to the wooden cabinets?",
        "answer": "Stainless steel.",
        "object_id": 48,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            5.432918548583984,
            0.13381248712539673,
            13.268400192260742
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3992061793733612,
            0.0,
            0.9168611816137292
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9_50_sink_587805",
        "episode_history": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the sink that is located between the two wooden cabinets in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The sink is rectangular.",
        "object_id": 50,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            5.917231559753418,
            0.13381248712539673,
            12.922443389892578
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7682751663289344,
            0.0,
            0.6401197300523146
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9_56_coffee_machine_523895",
        "episode_history": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the coffee machine on the kitchen counter?",
        "answer": "A paper towel holder.",
        "object_id": 56,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            7.293085098266602,
            0.13381248712539673,
            12.864452362060547
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4422828446442254,
            0.0,
            0.8968756242274689
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9_67_tv_431661",
        "episode_history": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the TV mounted on the wall in the living room turned off?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 67,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            7.709596633911133,
            0.13381248712539673,
            16.17986297607422
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9888925577852732,
            0.0,
            0.1486321269339151
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9_86_dresser_431164",
        "episode_history": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the small dresser with the intricate pattern?",
        "answer": "The small dresser with the intricate pattern is in the room next to the wooden door, under the window, and beside a small round stool.",
        "object_id": 86,
        "class": "dresser",
        "position": [
            4.349980354309082,
            0.13381248712539673,
            16.16425323486328
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9999455322456443,
            0.0,
            0.01043707536995747
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9_97_kitchen_island_95914",
        "episode_history": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the large wooden object with stools around it in the center of the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A kitchen island.",
        "object_id": 97,
        "class": "kitchen island",
        "position": [
            5.001631259918213,
            0.13381248712539673,
            16.87003517150879
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2080057045430655,
            0.0,
            0.9781276127773629
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9_132_bathroom_cabinet_125548",
        "episode_history": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is hanging to the right of the bathroom cabinet?",
        "answer": "Two white towels.",
        "object_id": 132,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            0.7676575779914856,
            0.13381248712539673,
            17.716960906982422
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4652271345446222,
            0.0,
            0.8851913427521758
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9_134_bathroom_counter_523564",
        "episode_history": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object with a granite top and a sink in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A bathroom counter.",
        "object_id": 134,
        "class": "bathroom counter",
        "position": [
            3.1784090995788574,
            0.13381248712539673,
            17.675893783569336
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.15985192501814965,
            0.0,
            0.9871410041468199
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9_165_blanket_302578",
        "episode_history": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the blanket that is on the middle shelf of the white shelving unit in the closet?",
        "answer": "Brown.",
        "object_id": 165,
        "class": "blanket",
        "position": [
            1.219557762145996,
            0.13381248712539673,
            17.335010528564453
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7240167109967031,
            0.0,
            0.689782431058893
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9_205_bedside_lamp_369470",
        "episode_history": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the lampshade on the bedside lamp that is placed on the wooden nightstand next to the bed with a brown leather headboard?",
        "answer": "Beige.",
        "object_id": 205,
        "class": "bedside lamp",
        "position": [
            3.0004963874816895,
            0.13381248712539673,
            13.389701843261719
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.007154313677672675,
            0.0,
            0.9999744075704144
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9_208_bedside_lamp_611192",
        "episode_history": "00245-741Fdj7NLF9",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the wooden nightstand next to the bed in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A bedside lamp.",
        "object_id": 208,
        "class": "bedside lamp",
        "position": [
            0.2778024673461914,
            0.13381248712539673,
            13.347623825073242
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.006250103889588343,
            0.0,
            0.9999804679099333
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00256-92vYG1q49FY_951_sink_cabinet_933886",
        "episode_history": "00256-92vYG1q49FY",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the wooden object directly below the sink in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A sink cabinet.",
        "object_id": 951,
        "class": "sink cabinet",
        "position": [
            -1.756077527999878,
            -2.636651039123535,
            3.0590689182281494
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9976450383194948,
            0.0,
            0.06858846489391994
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00256-92vYG1q49FY_316_coffee_table_719810",
        "episode_history": "00256-92vYG1q49FY",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the white coffee table with the green book on it?",
        "answer": "The white coffee table with the green book on it is in the living room, placed between the sofa with green pillows and a black shelving unit with a globe on top.",
        "object_id": 316,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            0.17234957218170166,
            0.36334896087646484,
            -4.601221084594727
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8510943581407174,
            0.0,
            0.525012755598414
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00256-92vYG1q49FY_788_coffee_table_796019",
        "episode_history": "00256-92vYG1q49FY",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the coffee table with the glass top?",
        "answer": "The coffee table with the glass top is in the living room, positioned between the two striped sofas and in front of the white shelving unit with various decorations and books.",
        "object_id": 788,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            -3.0932984352111816,
            -2.636651039123535,
            -0.27350494265556335
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9302617197779223,
            0.0,
            0.36689662401802314
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00256-92vYG1q49FY_415_toaster_920220",
        "episode_history": "00256-92vYG1q49FY",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the toaster on the wooden cart in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A coffee maker on the countertop.",
        "object_id": 415,
        "class": "toaster",
        "position": [
            2.8743906021118164,
            0.36334896087646484,
            3.448026180267334
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3644392077037165,
            0.0,
            0.9312271816738853
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00256-92vYG1q49FY_1080_coffee_maker_70302",
        "episode_history": "00256-92vYG1q49FY",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to make a cup of coffee?",
        "answer": "The coffee maker on the kitchen counter.",
        "object_id": 1080,
        "class": "coffee maker",
        "position": [
            2.3270139694213867,
            -2.636651039123535,
            6.523163795471191
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9919899303826814,
            0.0,
            0.12631697439127113
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00256-92vYG1q49FY_435_ventilation_hood_214963",
        "episode_history": "00256-92vYG1q49FY",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the ventilation hood that is above the stove and near the white cabinets in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "It is in a conical shape.",
        "object_id": 435,
        "class": "ventilation hood",
        "position": [
            4.106438159942627,
            0.36334896087646484,
            2.721757650375366
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9971318661006442,
            0.0,
            0.07568382658566289
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00256-92vYG1q49FY_1051_ventilation_hood_402183",
        "episode_history": "00256-92vYG1q49FY",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to remove smoke and odors while cooking?",
        "answer": "The ventilation hood above the stove.",
        "object_id": 1051,
        "class": "ventilation hood",
        "position": [
            2.099034309387207,
            -2.636651039123535,
            6.967645168304443
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6944022533603575,
            0.0,
            0.7195870416621312
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00256-92vYG1q49FY_1068_stovetop_761396",
        "episode_history": "00256-92vYG1q49FY",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the stovetop located?",
        "answer": "The stovetop is in the kitchen, built into the countertop between the microwave and the paper towel holder, above the oven.",
        "object_id": 1068,
        "class": "stovetop",
        "position": [
            3.3110218048095703,
            -2.636651039123535,
            6.550815105438232
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7712599896473789,
            0.0,
            0.6365202497714624
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00256-92vYG1q49FY_443_washing_machine_661824",
        "episode_history": "00256-92vYG1q49FY",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the washing machine located?",
        "answer": "The washing machine is in the kitchen, under the countertop next to the stove and near the entrance to the adjacent room with bookshelves.",
        "object_id": 443,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            4.145387172698975,
            0.36334896087646484,
            3.0871665477752686
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9272783688741247,
            0.0,
            0.3743725772784947
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00256-92vYG1q49FY_447_microwave_91705",
        "episode_history": "00256-92vYG1q49FY",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the microwave on the kitchen counter next to the blender closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 447,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            3.5788373947143555,
            0.36334896087646484,
            3.6006734371185303
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8733792225685291,
            0.0,
            0.48704079252727034
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00256-92vYG1q49FY_549_trolley_916737",
        "episode_history": "00256-92vYG1q49FY",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the old white trolley with some items on it?",
        "answer": "The old white trolley is on the porch, next to a plant and near the entrance door with a decorative metal grill.",
        "object_id": 549,
        "class": "trolley",
        "position": [
            -0.09365272521972656,
            -2.836651086807251,
            -5.034612655639648
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9550653102683327,
            0.0,
            0.2963954337064808
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00256-92vYG1q49FY_719_trolley_953412",
        "episode_history": "00256-92vYG1q49FY",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to serve food and drinks to my guests in the dining room?",
        "answer": "The trolley in the dining room.",
        "object_id": 719,
        "class": "trolley",
        "position": [
            -1.887934923171997,
            -2.636651039123535,
            3.018472194671631
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5909302654065588,
            0.0,
            0.806722642192801
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00256-92vYG1q49FY_593_recessed_shelving_265707",
        "episode_history": "00256-92vYG1q49FY",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object built into the wall on either side of the bed in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "Recessed shelving.",
        "object_id": 593,
        "class": "recessed shelving",
        "position": [
            2.1703407764434814,
            -2.636651039123535,
            -2.3289554119110107
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5414471382087194,
            0.0,
            0.8407347955958454
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00256-92vYG1q49FY_594_recessed_shelving_384128",
        "episode_history": "00256-92vYG1q49FY",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What items are stored on the recessed shelving to the right of the bed?",
        "answer": "Books and decorative plates.",
        "object_id": 594,
        "class": "recessed shelving",
        "position": [
            2.122694969177246,
            -2.636651039123535,
            -1.4806907176971436
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7692203516992198,
            0.0,
            0.6389836074045474
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00256-92vYG1q49FY_731_display_table_137688",
        "episode_history": "00256-92vYG1q49FY",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the display table in the hallway?",
        "answer": "A large framed painting.",
        "object_id": 731,
        "class": "display table",
        "position": [
            -0.2929166555404663,
            -2.636651039123535,
            1.2724721431732178
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9991241287135152,
            0.0,
            0.04184465823046228
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00256-92vYG1q49FY_960_bathtub_895664",
        "episode_history": "00256-92vYG1q49FY",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the bathtub in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A wooden vanity with a sink and a mirror above it.",
        "object_id": 960,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            -3.345306873321533,
            -2.636651039123535,
            4.897733688354492
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7501634708603424,
            0.0,
            0.6612524230479342
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21_70_bathtub_668997",
        "episode_history": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the shower curtain in the bathroom pulled closed over the bathtub?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 70,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            2.6812596321105957,
            3.367673635482788,
            -3.3435473442077637
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6446722022661171,
            0.0,
            0.764459123580427
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21_242_basket_972638",
        "episode_history": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is the artwork behind the basket on the black cabinet?",
        "answer": "A large abstract painting with circular patterns.",
        "object_id": 242,
        "class": "basket",
        "position": [
            2.483680248260498,
            3.367673635482788,
            5.9045090675354
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9350772601873418,
            0.0,
            0.3544439553448951
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21_256_nightstand_417765",
        "episode_history": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the small wooden table with crossed legs next to the bed in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A nightstand.",
        "object_id": 256,
        "class": "nightstand",
        "position": [
            3.0301389694213867,
            3.367673635482788,
            8.670684814453125
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.669490867379927,
            0.0,
            0.7428202868089111
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21_260_nightstand_761739",
        "episode_history": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the nightstand with books and a lamp?",
        "answer": "The nightstand is in the bedroom, next to the bed and under the window on the right side as you enter the room.",
        "object_id": 260,
        "class": "nightstand",
        "position": [
            0.8008604645729065,
            3.367673635482788,
            3.5761542320251465
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9983333511162364,
            0.0,
            0.05771065801942289
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21_415_ball_pouffe_957121",
        "episode_history": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the round, brown object with white stripes on the floor in front of the coffee table in the living room?",
        "answer": "A ball pouffe.",
        "object_id": 415,
        "class": "ball pouffe",
        "position": [
            6.780778408050537,
            3.367673635482788,
            4.682276725769043
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.23150809709620712,
            0.0,
            0.9728329769178742
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21_416_ball_pouffe_422547",
        "episode_history": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the round, brown and white object on the floor near the sofa in the room with the large stadium mural?",
        "answer": "A ball pouffe.",
        "object_id": 416,
        "class": "ball pouffe",
        "position": [
            8.201891899108887,
            3.367673635482788,
            1.6596120595932007
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9959486972875308,
            0.0,
            0.08992325823317629
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21_565_dishes_664097",
        "episode_history": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where are the stacks of dishes located?",
        "answer": "The stacks of dishes are on the kitchen counter, next to the stove and under the dark-colored cabinets.",
        "object_id": 565,
        "class": "dishes",
        "position": [
            8.210591316223145,
            0.17012907564640045,
            -2.9469192028045654
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.035084514447304954,
            0.0,
            0.999384348909866
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21_566_dishes_672024",
        "episode_history": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "Are the dishes on the kitchen counter located near any electrical outlets?",
        "answer": "Yes, there is an electrical outlet on the wall behind the dishes.",
        "object_id": 566,
        "class": "dishes",
        "position": [
            7.850698471069336,
            0.28835150599479675,
            -3.1681156158447266
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.216343075817247,
            0.0,
            0.9763174040986532
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21_568_range_hood_443960",
        "episode_history": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the metallic object located above the stove in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A range hood.",
        "object_id": 568,
        "class": "range hood",
        "position": [
            8.172369003295898,
            0.27044978737831116,
            -3.1346211433410645
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.38016504649635663,
            0.0,
            0.9249186653011296
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21_578_refrigerator_693037",
        "episode_history": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the large stainless steel object located between the black cabinets in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A refrigerator.",
        "object_id": 578,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            6.885138988494873,
            -0.03232640027999878,
            -0.15928779542446136
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.34208961863233195,
            0.0,
            0.9396673309336585
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21_899_washing_machine_899696",
        "episode_history": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the washing machine that is next to the black cabinet and under the wall shelves?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 899,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            1.134973168373108,
            0.16767361760139465,
            4.3503618240356445
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8982533517344556,
            0.0,
            0.4394780041114872
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21_934_desk_369254",
        "episode_history": "00258-2Pc8W48bu21",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly behind the desk in the study room?",
        "answer": "A large black bookshelf filled with various items such as books, decorative objects, and storage boxes.",
        "object_id": 934,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            0.7967420816421509,
            0.16767360270023346,
            1.1593048572540283
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9256848635596774,
            0.0,
            0.378295563516811
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00261-fK2vEV32Lag_57_tv_345062",
        "episode_history": "00261-fK2vEV32Lag",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the TV that is placed on a stand next to the fireplace with a large mirror above it?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 57,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -1.9636720418930054,
            -0.024750128388404846,
            -2.002762794494629
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3560793143192419,
            0.0,
            0.9344557356632461
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00261-fK2vEV32Lag_46_beanbag_353801",
        "episode_history": "00261-fK2vEV32Lag",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the beanbag located?",
        "answer": "The beanbag is in the living room, placed on the floor next to the sofa and under the tall floor lamp.",
        "object_id": 46,
        "class": "beanbag",
        "position": [
            -0.45330122113227844,
            -0.024750128388404846,
            -3.4128944873809814
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9880827553368156,
            0.0,
            0.15392358040926254
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00261-fK2vEV32Lag_305_board_546806",
        "episode_history": "00261-fK2vEV32Lag",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I leave a note for someone to see when they enter the house?",
        "answer": "The board next to the front door.",
        "object_id": 305,
        "class": "board",
        "position": [
            -0.7983263731002808,
            -0.003377007320523262,
            0.6588088274002075
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3218745086367241,
            0.0,
            0.9467823407150492
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00261-fK2vEV32Lag_206_desk_901000",
        "episode_history": "00261-fK2vEV32Lag",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wooden desk with the metal chair?",
        "answer": "The wooden desk with the metal chair is in the dining room, near the fireplace and the bookshelf filled with books and bottles.",
        "object_id": 206,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            -3.766954183578491,
            -0.024750128388404846,
            0.5773045420646667
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.018657426858379376,
            0.0,
            0.9998259350622108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00261-fK2vEV32Lag_213_rack_730149",
        "episode_history": "00261-fK2vEV32Lag",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What items are stored on the middle shelf of the rack next to the fireplace?",
        "answer": "Glassware and bottles.",
        "object_id": 213,
        "class": "rack",
        "position": [
            -4.360722064971924,
            -0.024750128388404846,
            -1.475656270980835
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.08846669618301069,
            0.0,
            0.9960791352430102
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00261-fK2vEV32Lag_248_trashcan_251936",
        "episode_history": "00261-fK2vEV32Lag",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What are the two identical objects placed against the wall next to the kitchen counter?",
        "answer": "Two trashcans.",
        "object_id": 248,
        "class": "trashcan",
        "position": [
            -9.199423789978027,
            -0.024750128388404846,
            0.18883977830410004
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9243955346640228,
            0.0,
            0.3814353097095442
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00261-fK2vEV32Lag_249_trashcan_202892",
        "episode_history": "00261-fK2vEV32Lag",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where are the two stainless steel trashcans in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The two stainless steel trashcans are located in the kitchen, against the tiled wall, near the blue cabinets and the countertop with the coffee maker.",
        "object_id": 249,
        "class": "trashcan",
        "position": [
            -9.364399909973145,
            -0.024750128388404846,
            0.09026842564344406
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8874565842521935,
            0.0,
            0.4608913224041317
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00261-fK2vEV32Lag_297_basket_636187",
        "episode_history": "00261-fK2vEV32Lag",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located under the bench in the hallway with the patterned floor tiles?",
        "answer": "A basket.",
        "object_id": 297,
        "class": "basket",
        "position": [
            -3.0142502784729004,
            -0.024750128388404846,
            -0.17194747924804688
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9543159106611961,
            0.0,
            0.29879950244083664
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00261-fK2vEV32Lag_345_towel_350139",
        "episode_history": "00261-fK2vEV32Lag",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the towel that is hanging over the bathtub near the toilet?",
        "answer": "Orange.",
        "object_id": 345,
        "class": "towel",
        "position": [
            -5.355818271636963,
            2.975250005722046,
            -0.1400119960308075
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8546203764093049,
            0.0,
            0.5192533218247314
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz_37_bag_947717",
        "episode_history": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on top of the black and silver box next to the couch in the living room?",
        "answer": "A bag.",
        "object_id": 37,
        "class": "bag",
        "position": [
            -7.742212295532227,
            2.5107767581939697,
            -0.37262916564941406
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8036528546626954,
            0.0,
            0.5950983861450985
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz_66_speaker_715037",
        "episode_history": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is the object to the left of the speaker on the piano?",
        "answer": "A window with blinds.",
        "object_id": 66,
        "class": "speaker",
        "position": [
            -7.376582145690918,
            2.5107767581939697,
            -0.5201832056045532
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.22577134901793142,
            0.0,
            0.9741803210713217
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz_67_speaker_332422",
        "episode_history": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the right side of the piano, under the window in the music room?",
        "answer": "A speaker.",
        "object_id": 67,
        "class": "speaker",
        "position": [
            -7.924756050109863,
            2.5107767581939697,
            -0.35003066062927246
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.036817976646068125,
            0.0,
            0.9993219884480125
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz_88_window_curtain_654999",
        "episode_history": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the window curtain in the bedroom drawn closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 88,
        "class": "window curtain",
        "position": [
            -3.3144636154174805,
            2.5107767581939697,
            1.3975591659545898
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9758180369732696,
            0.0,
            0.21858444299088509
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz_351_toilet_557837",
        "episode_history": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to flush away waste?",
        "answer": "The toilet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 351,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -0.658324122428894,
            0.11077675223350525,
            1.7125192880630493
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9952269515450939,
            0.0,
            0.09758747316261546
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz_126_bathtub_213514",
        "episode_history": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located to the right of the bathtub in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A vanity with a sink and countertop.",
        "object_id": 126,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            -0.8712539672851562,
            2.5107767581939697,
            1.24766206741333
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9861208150136932,
            0.0,
            0.16602932932686698
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz_194_refrigerator_91318",
        "episode_history": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the stainless steel refrigerator in the kitchen closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 194,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -1.4797691106796265,
            2.5107767581939697,
            -0.6090698838233948
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8090310237656165,
            0.0,
            0.5877659420081759
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz_224_microwave_349262",
        "episode_history": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the microwave on the countertop in the hallway next to the kitchen door closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 224,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -3.672055721282959,
            2.5107767581939697,
            -0.5748220086097717
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.47185683957894897,
            0.0,
            0.8816751799515318
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz_266_curtain_956754",
        "episode_history": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the curtain that is hanging in the doorway near the large mirror with a wooden frame?",
        "answer": "Gray.",
        "object_id": 266,
        "class": "curtain",
        "position": [
            -8.770517349243164,
            0.11077675223350525,
            1.7401139736175537
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2990420615906607,
            0.0,
            0.9542399307300065
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz_362_wall_panel_461062",
        "episode_history": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the small access panel on the wall in the bathroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 362,
        "class": "wall panel",
        "position": [
            -1.2951717376708984,
            0.11077675223350525,
            3.6438002586364746
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6846798779845437,
            0.0,
            0.7288439234040923
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz_393_picture_270931",
        "episode_history": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the picture frame that is hanging above the washing machine and dryer?",
        "answer": "It is in rectangular shape.",
        "object_id": 393,
        "class": "picture",
        "position": [
            -1.3134918212890625,
            0.11077675223350525,
            0.13442426919937134
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7743462905799077,
            0.0,
            0.6327620581744273
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz_394_picture_614541",
        "episode_history": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the subject of the picture that is hung on the wall above the table with laundry supplies and a green basket?",
        "answer": "The subject of the picture is a landscape scene.",
        "object_id": 394,
        "class": "picture",
        "position": [
            -1.0770421028137207,
            0.11077675223350525,
            0.14849241077899933
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.09047350177375761,
            0.0,
            0.9958988630763638
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz_396_washing_machine_144038",
        "episode_history": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the washing machine that is next to the dryer and beneath the framed picture of a cat?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 396,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -1.1641865968704224,
            0.11077675223350525,
            -0.47583597898483276
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.94209598204624,
            0.0,
            0.335343347350638
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz_397_washing_machine_543786",
        "episode_history": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object next to the dryer in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "A washing machine.",
        "object_id": 397,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -1.2451367378234863,
            0.11077675223350525,
            2.586426258087158
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2482112365117653,
            0.0,
            0.968705931678598
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz_407_ladder_60492",
        "episode_history": "00262-1xGrZPxG1Hz",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the blue ladder leaning against the wall in the laundry room folded?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 407,
        "class": "ladder",
        "position": [
            -0.6299879550933838,
            0.11077675223350525,
            1.4108028411865234
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.10343226717508809,
            0.0,
            0.9946364994846213
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr_43_dresser_846716",
        "episode_history": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to store and organize my clothes?",
        "answer": "The dresser against the wall.",
        "object_id": 43,
        "class": "dresser",
        "position": [
            -3.28141713142395,
            0.18276762962341309,
            0.19235961139202118
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.99156033674152,
            0.0,
            0.12964605123582068
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr_28_throw_blanket_542843",
        "episode_history": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to keep myself warm while resting on the bed?",
        "answer": "The throw blanket on the bed.",
        "object_id": 28,
        "class": "throw blanket",
        "position": [
            -1.4365060329437256,
            0.18276762962341309,
            2.9593605995178223
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9482843296632902,
            0.0,
            0.3174221638686311
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr_168_keyboard_363370",
        "episode_history": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the keyboard on the desk?",
        "answer": "A monitor.",
        "object_id": 168,
        "class": "keyboard",
        "position": [
            1.4953601360321045,
            0.18276762962341309,
            5.269456386566162
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8987657206098423,
            0.0,
            0.43842921829717396
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr_220_printer_539720",
        "episode_history": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the table to the right of the wooden shelf in the office room?",
        "answer": "A printer.",
        "object_id": 220,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            1.8550870418548584,
            0.18276762962341309,
            3.2302238941192627
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8480601935653965,
            0.0,
            0.5298999038401707
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr_331_calendar_667134",
        "episode_history": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the calendar in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A sign that says \"LOVE + HOME = best life ever.\"",
        "object_id": 331,
        "class": "calendar",
        "position": [
            9.529519081115723,
            0.18276762962341309,
            -0.2955252230167389
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9892177138046347,
            0.0,
            0.14645243150979728
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr_358_microwave_461918",
        "episode_history": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the microwave above the stove in the kitchen closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 358,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            6.809205532073975,
            0.18276762962341309,
            -1.4484455585479736
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9909571116632572,
            0.0,
            0.1341789955395861
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr_655_fireplace_wall_516132",
        "episode_history": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the tiles on the fireplace wall that is below a framed painting?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 655,
        "class": "fireplace wall",
        "position": [
            9.508010864257812,
            0.18276762962341309,
            6.054039478302002
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3447955657923446,
            0.0,
            0.9386778029813728
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr_701_tv_stand_345102",
        "episode_history": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What material is the TV stand that is positioned near the large windows made of?",
        "answer": "Wood.",
        "object_id": 701,
        "class": "tv stand",
        "position": [
            11.153035163879395,
            0.18276762962341309,
            3.573184013366699
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9990152551732856,
            0.0,
            0.04436800571413376
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr_702_led_tv_505361",
        "episode_history": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to watch my favorite TV shows and movies?",
        "answer": "The LED TV in the corner of the living room.",
        "object_id": 702,
        "class": "led tv",
        "position": [
            10.617815017700195,
            0.18276762962341309,
            3.197385549545288
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9975887919330457,
            0.0,
            0.06940174500373758
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr_853_tv_464086",
        "episode_history": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the TV located?",
        "answer": "The TV is on top of a wooden cabinet in the corner of the room, next to a framed picture on the wall and a patterned rug on the floor.",
        "object_id": 853,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            9.883869171142578,
            -2.617232322692871,
            0.36766719818115234
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.178480097549249,
            0.0,
            0.9839435221489141
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr_877_stand_821449",
        "episode_history": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the small stand with the decorative tree on top?",
        "answer": "The small stand with the decorative tree on top is in the hallway, next to the wall with a framed picture of a horse, near the entrance to the storage room.",
        "object_id": 877,
        "class": "stand",
        "position": [
            5.358738899230957,
            -2.617232322692871,
            -1.5721323490142822
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6129256231823604,
            0.0,
            0.7901406080227209
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr_893_wine_cabinet_444252",
        "episode_history": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the tall object with multiple compartments next to the bar counter and near the staircase?",
        "answer": "A wine cabinet.",
        "object_id": 893,
        "class": "wine cabinet",
        "position": [
            8.522904396057129,
            -2.617232322692871,
            4.431047439575195
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7419975969729128,
            0.0,
            0.6704025403341063
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr_958_washing_machine_952000",
        "episode_history": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the washing machine next to the dryer in the laundry room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 958,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -2.2865657806396484,
            -2.617232322692871,
            3.9397425651550293
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9170390419204957,
            0.0,
            0.3987974367940934
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr_997_stacked_chair_765696",
        "episode_history": "00272-kA2nG18hCAr",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where are the stacked chairs in the basement?",
        "answer": "The stacked chairs are located in the basement, directly under the central ductwork, next to a white appliance and near the treadmill.",
        "object_id": 997,
        "class": "stacked chair",
        "position": [
            0.7634216547012329,
            -2.617232322692871,
            -1.0281667709350586
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9997691965794895,
            0.0,
            0.021483797866436057
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW_35_printer_747596",
        "episode_history": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on top of the black cabinet next to the window in the office room?",
        "answer": "A printer.",
        "object_id": 35,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            6.019667625427246,
            0.18035441637039185,
            -9.587692260742188
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9643047313409169,
            0.0,
            0.26479498694937975
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW_36_desk_80751",
        "episode_history": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the desk with dual monitors?",
        "answer": "The desk with dual monitors is in the room with wooden flooring, positioned against the wall near a window with white curtains. It is adjacent to a black filing cabinet and a swivel chair.",
        "object_id": 36,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            5.7554931640625,
            0.13057184219360352,
            -9.89689826965332
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9972386489845148,
            0.0,
            0.0742635642259171
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW_273_desk_153591",
        "episode_history": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the small desk with the computer?",
        "answer": "The small desk with the computer is in the bedroom, positioned against the wall under the window with curtains, next to the bunk bed and near the black shelving unit.",
        "object_id": 273,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            3.899510145187378,
            0.19179342687129974,
            2.6136703491210938
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7938557306534202,
            0.0,
            0.608106141153602
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW_38_screen_39638",
        "episode_history": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is displayed on the left screen of the dual-monitor setup on the desk in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "An image of a beach with water and sand.",
        "object_id": 38,
        "class": "screen",
        "position": [
            5.3026227951049805,
            0.0056416988372802734,
            -8.369712829589844
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9579402935814764,
            0.0,
            0.2869675834184675
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW_39_screen_122936",
        "episode_history": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the left screen on the desk in the study room turned on?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 39,
        "class": "screen",
        "position": [
            5.308757781982422,
            0.029994498938322067,
            -8.623759269714355
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.990610478089778,
            0.0,
            0.13671459577799608
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW_91_dining_table_500280",
        "episode_history": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are there any items placed on the round dining table with black chairs in the dining area?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 91,
        "class": "dining table",
        "position": [
            3.8979153633117676,
            -0.008206576108932495,
            -3.3845295906066895
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.41133967217736106,
            0.0,
            0.9114821304298956
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW_136_display_table_365377",
        "episode_history": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the display table next to the pillar in the kitchen area filled with items?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 136,
        "class": "display table",
        "position": [
            4.442689418792725,
            -0.008206576108932495,
            -0.5965214967727661
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.621692189598037,
            0.0,
            0.7832616557656824
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW_158_refrigerator_295166",
        "episode_history": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the refrigerator in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A small wooden shelf unit with various items stored on it.",
        "object_id": 158,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            2.6132917404174805,
            -0.008206576108932495,
            -3.1270253658294678
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8292010959953916,
            0.0,
            0.5589503935055788
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW_160_microwave_190015",
        "episode_history": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The microwave is mounted above the stove, integrated into the cabinetry in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 160,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            1.981564998626709,
            -0.008206576108932495,
            -2.9713149070739746
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5949425428713455,
            0.0,
            0.8037682319436227
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW_182_sink_360935",
        "episode_history": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the sink in the kitchen filled with dishes?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 182,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            1.2592799663543701,
            0.015151560306549072,
            -5.464860916137695
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8162509149908412,
            0.0,
            0.5776975365852051
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW_272_chair_468990",
        "episode_history": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the small chair that is placed in front of the window with curtains and next to the bunk bed?",
        "answer": "Blue.",
        "object_id": 272,
        "class": "chair",
        "position": [
            5.062681198120117,
            0.19179342687129974,
            2.5185515880584717
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6406307181829701,
            0.0,
            0.7678491277069812
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW_315_mat_313373",
        "episode_history": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to step on after taking a shower to avoid slipping?",
        "answer": "The mat in front of the shower.",
        "object_id": 315,
        "class": "mat",
        "position": [
            2.882122039794922,
            0.19179342687129974,
            2.433621883392334
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7897055781468895,
            0.0,
            0.6134860225332662
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW_389_mat_862073",
        "episode_history": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to prevent slipping when I step out of the shower?",
        "answer": "The mat in front of the shower.",
        "object_id": 389,
        "class": "mat",
        "position": [
            2.4084763526916504,
            0.19179342687129974,
            3.7959728240966797
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8909696518164408,
            0.0,
            0.45406285858027456
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW_330_toilet_315375",
        "episode_history": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the toilet that is next to the sink with a mirror above it in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 330,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            2.200183391571045,
            0.19179342687129974,
            1.7676281929016113
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9808525697570541,
            0.0,
            0.19475173016172018
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW_396_toilet_679343",
        "episode_history": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located next to the sink in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A toilet.",
        "object_id": 396,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            2.9596073627471924,
            0.19179342687129974,
            6.277868747711182
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3294121912189644,
            0.0,
            0.9441862148306976
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW_333_bathtub_529333",
        "episode_history": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the bathtub that is next to the shower with glass doors in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The bathtub is made of white ceramic or porcelain.",
        "object_id": 333,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            2.6814684867858887,
            0.19179342687129974,
            2.7981138229370117
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7098464036954597,
            0.0,
            0.7043565028880066
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW_334_bathroom_cabinet_566607",
        "episode_history": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I store my toiletries in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The bathroom cabinet under the sink.",
        "object_id": 334,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            2.3829104900360107,
            0.19179342687129974,
            1.9443731307983398
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9189556402650428,
            0.0,
            0.3943609149308099
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW_394_bathroom_cabinet_669526",
        "episode_history": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the bathroom cabinet that is located between the sink and the toilet?",
        "answer": "Dark brown.",
        "object_id": 394,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            2.60927152633667,
            0.19179342687129974,
            5.564640998840332
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4686051409555861,
            0.0,
            0.883407732516529
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW_404_shower_floor_60144",
        "episode_history": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly in front of the shower floor in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A beige bath mat.",
        "object_id": 404,
        "class": "shower floor",
        "position": [
            2.4441797733306885,
            0.19179342687129974,
            5.0811991691589355
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6921989927904892,
            0.0,
            0.7217066955348497
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW_500_ladder_7803",
        "episode_history": "00299-bdp1XNEdvmW",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the ladder stored?",
        "answer": "The ladder is stored in the walk-in closet, leaning against the right wall near the entrance.",
        "object_id": 500,
        "class": "ladder",
        "position": [
            3.642756700515747,
            0.19179342687129974,
            6.512531280517578
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6293251480518092,
            0.0,
            0.7771421092886219
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5_35_pouffe_347334",
        "episode_history": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the floral pouffe located?",
        "answer": "The floral pouffe is in the living room, next to the matching floral armchair and near the front door.",
        "object_id": 35,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            2.0385799407958984,
            0.14680051803588867,
            -0.1481497883796692
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.47406356806933136,
            0.0,
            0.8804906208639445
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5_510_pouffe_166262",
        "episode_history": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the black pouffe in the room?",
        "answer": "The black pouffe is next to the bed, near the corner of the room with the green wall.",
        "object_id": 510,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            6.00888204574585,
            0.14680051803588867,
            3.0600645542144775
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9481918939739381,
            0.0,
            0.3176981778388353
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5_36_armchair_513381",
        "episode_history": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the floral-patterned armchair near the windows?",
        "answer": "A small wooden side table with a lamp on it.",
        "object_id": 36,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            1.5462180376052856,
            0.14680051803588867,
            -0.07083895802497864
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3274163105948791,
            0.0,
            0.9448801826456292
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5_49_couch_289736",
        "episode_history": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the pink couch in the living room?",
        "answer": "The pink couch is in the living room, positioned near the window and adjacent to another matching couch. It is facing a wooden coffee table and is situated on a large, light-colored rug.",
        "object_id": 49,
        "class": "couch",
        "position": [
            0.40794485807418823,
            0.14680051803588867,
            0.054016828536987305
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.46335401928893505,
            0.0,
            0.8861732634247036
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5_115_oven_595506",
        "episode_history": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the oven in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A microwave.",
        "object_id": 115,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            7.222870826721191,
            0.14680051803588867,
            -0.711600661277771
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9903678494118222,
            0.0,
            0.1384612684161206
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5_116_oven_887595",
        "episode_history": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the oven in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A microwave.",
        "object_id": 116,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            7.60987663269043,
            0.14680051803588867,
            -0.9789620041847229
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9787386068946613,
            0.0,
            0.20511152911013475
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5_392_toilet_503005",
        "episode_history": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to flush away waste?",
        "answer": "The toilet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 392,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            3.1539666652679443,
            0.14680051803588867,
            4.224295139312744
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.953397856722487,
            0.0,
            0.3017159704042338
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5_564_toilet_80172",
        "episode_history": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the toilet that is next to the shower area with a wooden mat?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 564,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            7.782071590423584,
            0.14680051803588867,
            2.3748152256011963
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7029003843633994,
            0.0,
            0.7112883027730635
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5_395_bathtub_398105",
        "episode_history": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bathtub in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The bathtub is located at the far end of the bathroom, beneath the window, next to the toilet and opposite the sink.",
        "object_id": 395,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            3.2610878944396973,
            0.14680051803588867,
            3.6446938514709473
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9946012881804741,
            0.0,
            0.10377031150448343
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5_423_shelf_437696",
        "episode_history": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are there any shoes on the top shelf of the wooden shoe rack in the hallway?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 423,
        "class": "shelf",
        "position": [
            3.090831995010376,
            0.14680051803588867,
            2.0252795219421387
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9717086316713498,
            0.0,
            0.23618284259317515
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5_446_wall_board_822214",
        "episode_history": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object mounted on the wall above the dresser and next to the wooden door in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A wall board.",
        "object_id": 446,
        "class": "wall board",
        "position": [
            5.192995548248291,
            0.14680051803588867,
            4.9218058586120605
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9336269681864674,
            0.0,
            0.3582466807591452
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5_595_curtain_606678",
        "episode_history": "00304-X6Pct1msZv5",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is the object hanging from the ceiling above the bed near the curtain?",
        "answer": "A light fixture with a decorative cover.",
        "object_id": 595,
        "class": "curtain",
        "position": [
            7.489407539367676,
            0.14680051803588867,
            4.368247985839844
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9839025421822171,
            0.0,
            0.17870586864278057
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_17_chest_drawer_742729",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the chest drawer near the staircase?",
        "answer": "The staircase.",
        "object_id": 17,
        "class": "chest drawer",
        "position": [
            1.2884137630462646,
            0.09852778911590576,
            2.847547769546509
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5011014310048536,
            0.0,
            0.8653885577270409
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_31_row_of_theater_chairs_68691",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the upholstery on the row of theater chairs that is placed below the painting of three people?",
        "answer": "Red.",
        "object_id": 31,
        "class": "row of theater chairs",
        "position": [
            -1.4557499885559082,
            0.09852778911590576,
            0.1890524923801422
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8453468550222962,
            0.0,
            0.5342178345056565
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_66_microwave_437760",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to quickly heat up my food?",
        "answer": "The microwave on the countertop.",
        "object_id": 66,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -2.9167356491088867,
            0.09852778911590576,
            1.2783420085906982
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9908872816480201,
            0.0,
            0.1346937083467408
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_143_dog_bed_414249",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I find a place for my dog to rest?",
        "answer": "The dog bed near the window.",
        "object_id": 143,
        "class": "dog bed",
        "position": [
            -0.9135801792144775,
            0.09852778911590576,
            0.18404638767242432
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7008459371728335,
            0.0,
            0.7133126750229052
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_384_dog_bed_728398",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there a blanket on the black dog bed next to the armchair in the living room?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 384,
        "class": "dog bed",
        "position": [
            -0.444179892539978,
            0.09852778911590576,
            5.366397857666016
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9015173006836343,
            0.0,
            0.4327430606816169
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_709_toilet_134818",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the toilet paper roll next to the toilet in the bathroom almost empty?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 709,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -3.950767755508423,
            2.8985278606414795,
            0.6245266795158386
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9923617947495366,
            0.0,
            0.12336153501589674
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_240_oven_852672",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to bake a cake?",
        "answer": "The oven in the kitchen with orange cabinets.",
        "object_id": 240,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            2.4042792320251465,
            0.09852778911590576,
            4.03633975982666
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.007105769523987658,
            0.0,
            0.9999747537010482
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_254_sink_821618",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the kitchen sink?",
        "answer": "The kitchen sink is located on the countertop between the stove and the window, with various kitchen appliances and utensils around it.",
        "object_id": 254,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            2.636463165283203,
            0.09852778911590576,
            2.6390652656555176
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4512406058749507,
            0.0,
            0.8924023283304495
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_302_rice_cooker_717695",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the rice cooker in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The rice cooker is on the kitchen counter, next to the stove and under the wall clock.",
        "object_id": 302,
        "class": "rice cooker",
        "position": [
            3.3526525497436523,
            0.09852778911590576,
            3.083834648132324
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9197036159343578,
            0.0,
            0.3926133706807084
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_307_range_hood_905314",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the range hood located?",
        "answer": "The range hood is in the kitchen, hanging above the central island with orange cabinets.",
        "object_id": 307,
        "class": "range hood",
        "position": [
            1.7555608749389648,
            0.09852778911590576,
            2.442504644393921
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8884776429380384,
            0.0,
            0.4589199036861088
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_367_blanket_basket_309549",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the blanket inside the basket next to the wooden box by the sliding glass door rolled up?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 367,
        "class": "blanket basket",
        "position": [
            0.4411191940307617,
            0.09852778911590576,
            6.292086601257324
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9990928547868018,
            0.0,
            0.04258482727395344
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_383_wall_tv_635041",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object mounted on the wall above the white cabinet and next to the armchair in the living room?",
        "answer": "A wall TV.",
        "object_id": 383,
        "class": "wall tv",
        "position": [
            -1.95412278175354,
            0.10229656845331192,
            6.348601341247559
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7551268758877016,
            0.0,
            0.6555786766758661
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_389_media_console_604148",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are there magazines stacked on the media console next to the sofa in the living room?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 389,
        "class": "media console",
        "position": [
            -3.324019432067871,
            0.12402395904064178,
            5.598682403564453
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8456033308596745,
            0.0,
            0.5338117709820792
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_429_projector_637317",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the projector located?",
        "answer": "The projector is on top of a white cabinet next to the gray sofa in the living room, under a shelf with decorative items.",
        "object_id": 429,
        "class": "projector",
        "position": [
            -2.9689269065856934,
            0.16745837032794952,
            5.868905067443848
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5450093148306286,
            0.0,
            0.8384299891749154
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_441_table_14959",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the table in front of the sofa in the living room clear of any items?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 441,
        "class": "table",
        "position": [
            -0.28792643547058105,
            0.09852778911590576,
            4.4222493171691895
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7522165674724259,
            0.0,
            0.6589159548986512
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_460_dresser_920784",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is hanging on the wall above the dresser in the hallway?",
        "answer": "A large piece of artwork with various designs.",
        "object_id": 460,
        "class": "dresser",
        "position": [
            0.06805998086929321,
            2.8985278606414795,
            2.3871302604675293
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.14031735907728152,
            0.0,
            0.9901065794860557
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_525_side_table_415481",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the basket on the side table next to the stacked storage boxes filled with items?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 525,
        "class": "side table",
        "position": [
            1.3541417121887207,
            3.0371925830841064,
            2.0366902351379395
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9846389672574445,
            0.0,
            0.17460270375396053
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_590_sewing_machine_379776",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the desk with a green cutting mat in the room with shelves full of fabric?",
        "answer": "A sewing machine.",
        "object_id": 590,
        "class": "sewing machine",
        "position": [
            3.736205577850342,
            2.9596097469329834,
            5.374007701873779
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9829029244282451,
            0.0,
            0.18412452620551278
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_654_computer_chair_633591",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the computer chair that is positioned in front of the desk with multiple monitors and surrounded by stacks of books and papers?",
        "answer": "The color of the computer chair is black.",
        "object_id": 654,
        "class": "computer chair",
        "position": [
            2.4941153526306152,
            2.8985278606414795,
            6.444210529327393
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.32000916283311964,
            0.0,
            0.947414447695857
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_661_papers_156518",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where are the stacks of papers located?",
        "answer": "The stacks of papers are on the wooden desk in the study room, next to the bookshelf filled with binders and folders.",
        "object_id": 661,
        "class": "papers",
        "position": [
            4.016148567199707,
            3.0005602836608887,
            5.7678728103637695
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4361110988067487,
            0.0,
            0.899892832229244
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_671_exercise_machine_31600",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the exercise machine next to the brown swivel chair in the room folded?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 671,
        "class": "exercise machine",
        "position": [
            1.5751121044158936,
            2.8985278606414795,
            4.886699199676514
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9762706848910021,
            0.0,
            0.21655380352802173
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_714_bathtub_995865",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the bathtub in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A towel rack with a fish painting hanging above it.",
        "object_id": 714,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            -4.003058910369873,
            2.8985278606414795,
            0.30082419514656067
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9493504845505019,
            0.0,
            0.31421912335777213
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_720_radiator_387419",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the radiator with the fish painting above it?",
        "answer": "The radiator is in the bathroom, mounted on the wall next to the bathtub and below a fish painting.",
        "object_id": 720,
        "class": "radiator",
        "position": [
            -4.1648454666137695,
            2.8985278606414795,
            1.3159830570220947
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8388504949559004,
            0.0,
            0.5443618714717636
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj_725_washbasin_622735",
        "episode_history": "00313-PE6kVEtrxtj",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the towel hanging next to the washbasin in the bathroom clean?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 725,
        "class": "washbasin",
        "position": [
            -3.2050533294677734,
            2.8985278606414795,
            1.5470919609069824
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6542659496600212,
            0.0,
            0.7562645483661592
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5_71_bathtub_4607",
        "episode_history": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located next to the toilet and under the decorative mirror in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A bathtub.",
        "object_id": 71,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            -2.4441986083984375,
            2.7934396266937256,
            -3.8518388271331787
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.23516751581264808,
            0.0,
            0.9719548546648182
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5_194_desk_321728",
        "episode_history": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located below the wooden cabinets and next to the pink bin in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A desk.",
        "object_id": 194,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            -5.162799835205078,
            2.7934396266937256,
            -0.14596380293369293
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.34173486654080715,
            0.0,
            0.9397964040101114
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5_195_blanket_837627",
        "episode_history": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the pink blanket folded neatly on the worktop next to the wooden drawers in the room?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 195,
        "class": "blanket",
        "position": [
            -7.040682792663574,
            2.7934396266937256,
            -1.1908140182495117
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.1752478765248026,
            0.0,
            0.9845243429055208
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5_362_blanket_893238",
        "episode_history": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the blanket draped over the back of the black office chair near the window with a garden view?",
        "answer": "The pattern is a geometric design consisting of interlocking shapes.",
        "object_id": 362,
        "class": "blanket",
        "position": [
            -3.433093309402466,
            0.19343972206115723,
            2.7560129165649414
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.47023845470603487,
            0.0,
            0.8825394017921695
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5_201_pouffe_278746",
        "episode_history": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the pouffe that is placed near the wall with butterfly decorations and next to the bunk bed?",
        "answer": "Beige.",
        "object_id": 201,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            -5.582846164703369,
            2.7934396266937256,
            -1.7550493478775024
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9949090785852486,
            0.0,
            0.10077661111913706
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5_413_pouffe_64898",
        "episode_history": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the pouffe that is placed near the cat tree and the large mirror in the living room?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 413,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            1.6574654579162598,
            -0.006560325622558594,
            -5.23124885559082
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9936464958441098,
            0.0,
            0.11254617406522861
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5_212_carpet_183874",
        "episode_history": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the pink carpet in the bedroom clean?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 212,
        "class": "carpet",
        "position": [
            -4.218969345092773,
            2.7934396266937256,
            0.12870332598686218
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5411984111317697,
            0.0,
            0.8408949279121904
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5_338_stovetop_958623",
        "episode_history": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to cook my meals?",
        "answer": "The stovetop on the kitchen counter.",
        "object_id": 338,
        "class": "stovetop",
        "position": [
            -3.5532689094543457,
            0.19343972206115723,
            2.5281951427459717
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8030035091321993,
            0.0,
            0.5959742983731545
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5_395_furniture_872911",
        "episode_history": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the wooden piece of furniture with a round mirror above it, located against the wall in the dining area?",
        "answer": "A wooden cabinet.",
        "object_id": 395,
        "class": "furniture",
        "position": [
            -3.9412522315979004,
            -0.006560325622558594,
            -3.8067593574523926
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.07407896846578997,
            0.0,
            0.9972523785035784
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5_410_fireplace_132540",
        "episode_history": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the fireplace that is located between the dining area and the living room with the fluffy rugs?",
        "answer": "The fireplace is green.",
        "object_id": 410,
        "class": "fireplace",
        "position": [
            0.4684255123138428,
            0.07769382745027542,
            -4.077381610870361
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8707938824667634,
            0.0,
            0.491648262743255
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5_415_tv_stand_873903",
        "episode_history": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the TV stand in the living room?",
        "answer": "A cat tree.",
        "object_id": 415,
        "class": "tv stand",
        "position": [
            -0.8574178218841553,
            0.19343972206115723,
            -5.306969165802002
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7950085809424539,
            0.0,
            0.6065981835019504
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5_423_bench_675285",
        "episode_history": "00330-WhNyDTnd9g5",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the bench that is placed next to the wooden dining table and beneath the large painting of palm trees?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 423,
        "class": "bench",
        "position": [
            -1.0088939666748047,
            0.1661645919084549,
            -2.7110135555267334
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.34008673544967777,
            0.0,
            0.9403940729136806
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00378-DqJKU7YU7dA_249_tool_box_108296",
        "episode_history": "00378-DqJKU7YU7dA",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located to the left of the tool box on the porch?",
        "answer": "A grill and some outdoor furniture.",
        "object_id": 249,
        "class": "tool box",
        "position": [
            -3.197072982788086,
            0.079173743724823,
            9.487786293029785
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3986500055506693,
            0.0,
            0.9171031420044592
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00378-DqJKU7YU7dA_305_fireplace_447425",
        "episode_history": "00378-DqJKU7YU7dA",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the outdoor fireplace?",
        "answer": "The outdoor fireplace is located on the patio, built into the wall between the glass doors and behind the wooden dining table and chairs.",
        "object_id": 305,
        "class": "fireplace",
        "position": [
            -7.89528751373291,
            -0.12082625925540924,
            11.792099952697754
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6449202201742248,
            0.0,
            0.764249899974105
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00378-DqJKU7YU7dA_375_refrigerator_60413",
        "episode_history": "00378-DqJKU7YU7dA",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to store my groceries and keep them fresh?",
        "answer": "The refrigerator in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 375,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -4.761074542999268,
            0.079173743724823,
            16.44790267944336
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.959221848545692,
            0.0,
            0.2826542857849231
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00378-DqJKU7YU7dA_578_printer_684233",
        "episode_history": "00378-DqJKU7YU7dA",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the printer that is on the wooden stand next to the door with two black knobs?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 578,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            -3.0793802738189697,
            0.079173743724823,
            20.939735412597656
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9698639187755498,
            0.0,
            0.2436472430735333
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00378-DqJKU7YU7dA_585_office_chair_71935",
        "episode_history": "00378-DqJKU7YU7dA",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the office chair that is placed in front of the window with blinds in the study room?",
        "answer": "Black and gray.",
        "object_id": 585,
        "class": "office chair",
        "position": [
            -3.5351333618164062,
            0.079173743724823,
            22.10028839111328
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7161026561126743,
            0.0,
            0.69799497556098
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00378-DqJKU7YU7dA_784_file_cabinet_516550",
        "episode_history": "00378-DqJKU7YU7dA",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the tall black file cabinet?",
        "answer": "The tall black file cabinet is in the living room, positioned in the corner between the beige sofa and the window with white curtains.",
        "object_id": 784,
        "class": "file cabinet",
        "position": [
            -9.402543067932129,
            0.079173743724823,
            26.299394607543945
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9815306471019412,
            0.0,
            0.19130496282021942
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00378-DqJKU7YU7dA_785_file_cabinet_608212",
        "episode_history": "00378-DqJKU7YU7dA",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I store important documents securely?",
        "answer": "The file cabinet next to the sofa.",
        "object_id": 785,
        "class": "file cabinet",
        "position": [
            -9.753724098205566,
            0.079173743724823,
            26.3131160736084
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9984672652083075,
            0.0,
            0.05534546329597836
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq_29_coffee_table_415322",
        "episode_history": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly behind the coffee table in the sunroom?",
        "answer": "A blue sectional sofa.",
        "object_id": 29,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            -0.7743314504623413,
            -0.03508578985929489,
            -0.12051144242286682
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9745616598999259,
            0.0,
            0.22411954634324263
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq_67_tv_899151",
        "episode_history": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the small wooden table next to the blue sectional sofa in the sunroom?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 67,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            0.4972018599510193,
            -0.1355365663766861,
            0.3506629467010498
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9434258433889754,
            0.0,
            0.33158359130964343
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq_129_tv_840226",
        "episode_history": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the TV located?",
        "answer": "The TV is in the living room, placed on a wooden TV stand against the wall, near the entrance to the hallway.",
        "object_id": 129,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -4.041123390197754,
            0.06446343660354614,
            1.5372207164764404
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2301161362044135,
            0.0,
            0.9731631743229662
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq_118_piano_682975",
        "episode_history": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located to the right of the piano near the staircase?",
        "answer": "A small wooden bench.",
        "object_id": 118,
        "class": "piano",
        "position": [
            -4.624359130859375,
            0.06446343660354614,
            -0.03347606956958771
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9869458936110224,
            0.0,
            0.1610521750376003
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq_124_piano_stool_983382",
        "episode_history": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the piano stool in front of the piano in the hallway properly aligned with the piano?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 124,
        "class": "piano stool",
        "position": [
            -3.8428993225097656,
            0.06446343660354614,
            0.09825317561626434
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9989900088994084,
            0.0,
            0.044932862352597774
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq_127_pouffe_874360",
        "episode_history": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to rest my feet while sitting on the couch?",
        "answer": "The pouffe in the living room.",
        "object_id": 127,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            -4.321028232574463,
            0.06446343660354614,
            0.10361082851886749
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2887708222264505,
            0.0,
            0.9573982516333835
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq_216_table_428184",
        "episode_history": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the table that is surrounded by intricately carved chairs in the dining room with blue curtains?",
        "answer": "Rectangular.",
        "object_id": 216,
        "class": "table",
        "position": [
            -4.651546001434326,
            0.06446343660354614,
            -2.316359519958496
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7566699524461509,
            0.0,
            0.6537970503643618
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq_260_fridge_601281",
        "episode_history": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the large metallic object in the kitchen, visible through the doorway from the hallway?",
        "answer": "A fridge.",
        "object_id": 260,
        "class": "fridge",
        "position": [
            -4.214040756225586,
            0.06446343660354614,
            -0.27579575777053833
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9482706032039536,
            0.0,
            0.31746316809861613
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq_287_fridge_516919",
        "episode_history": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the fridge that is near the window with white curtains and has a stack of canned drinks beside it?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 287,
        "class": "fridge",
        "position": [
            -9.455707550048828,
            0.06446343660354614,
            2.64687180519104
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8241592740852499,
            0.0,
            0.5663580942648158
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq_263_microwave_66630",
        "episode_history": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to quickly heat up my leftovers?",
        "answer": "The microwave above the stove.",
        "object_id": 263,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -7.506491661071777,
            0.06446343660354614,
            1.8329747915267944
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6360805384394286,
            0.0,
            0.7716226724368631
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq_270_microwave_446012",
        "episode_history": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the microwave that is installed above the stove and next to the wooden cabinets?",
        "answer": "Stainless steel.",
        "object_id": 270,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -7.86309814453125,
            0.06446343660354614,
            1.2848153114318848
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8551010628034116,
            0.0,
            0.5184613509148738
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq_265_oven_287399",
        "episode_history": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the oven that is located below the microwave and next to the wooden cabinets in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Stainless steel (silver).",
        "object_id": 265,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            -6.966817855834961,
            0.06446343660354614,
            3.270822763442993
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.41437723180001096,
            0.0,
            0.9101052190630268
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq_342_bathroom_cabinet_636238",
        "episode_history": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located to the left of the bathroom cabinet?",
        "answer": "A toilet.",
        "object_id": 342,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            -11.85722827911377,
            0.06446343660354614,
            2.5461442470550537
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4413578496557367,
            0.0,
            0.8973311810849237
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq_343_bathroom_counter_726264",
        "episode_history": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bathroom counter with the mirror above it?",
        "answer": "The bathroom counter is in the bathroom, next to the toilet and under a wall-mounted mirror.",
        "object_id": 343,
        "class": "bathroom counter",
        "position": [
            -11.288337707519531,
            0.06446343660354614,
            0.3597857356071472
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8811542019215381,
            0.0,
            0.47282900972340636
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq_355_toilet_796990",
        "episode_history": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the toilet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A radiator with a toilet paper roll on top.",
        "object_id": 355,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -11.428955078125,
            0.06446343660354614,
            2.187100648880005
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2827681950985633,
            0.0,
            0.9591882754916788
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq_370_bathtub_404500",
        "episode_history": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the tiles surrounding the bathtub that is next to the window with a floral curtain?",
        "answer": "The tiles are predominantly white with gray veining.",
        "object_id": 370,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            -10.462874412536621,
            0.06446343660354614,
            2.7839784622192383
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.33950675748027087,
            0.0,
            0.9406036155709974
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq_390_bookshelf_846959",
        "episode_history": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the bookshelf next to the windows in the room empty?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 390,
        "class": "bookshelf",
        "position": [
            -6.575129508972168,
            3.0644636154174805,
            -1.3069181442260742
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8067329007574291,
            0.0,
            0.5909162604257088
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq_431_printer_88140",
        "episode_history": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on top of the black cabinet next to the window in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A printer.",
        "object_id": 431,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            -7.637758255004883,
            3.0700342655181885,
            1.2062673568725586
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5351162845940924,
            0.0,
            0.8447784099763762
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq_591_trashcan_36620",
        "episode_history": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the trashcan that is placed next to the radiator and near the wooden nightstand?",
        "answer": "Metal.",
        "object_id": 591,
        "class": "trashcan",
        "position": [
            0.02475394308567047,
            3.177349328994751,
            2.280360698699951
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9174658331820699,
            0.0,
            0.3978145861372236
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq_595_mat_172336",
        "episode_history": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the floor in front of the black chair in the room with the wooden floor?",
        "answer": "A mat.",
        "object_id": 595,
        "class": "mat",
        "position": [
            1.0559337139129639,
            3.087519407272339,
            1.4941060543060303
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7539386333431103,
            0.0,
            0.6569448509218434
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq_598_keyboard_524122",
        "episode_history": "00382-S7uMvxjBVZq",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed in front of the monitor on the wooden desk near the window?",
        "answer": "A keyboard.",
        "object_id": 598,
        "class": "keyboard",
        "position": [
            -0.10069383680820465,
            3.2151925563812256,
            3.1365280151367188
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.71768666095858,
            0.0,
            0.6963661800246507
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00384-ceJTwFNjqCt_11_drinking_fountain_304958",
        "episode_history": "00384-ceJTwFNjqCt",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object attached to the wall in the hallway near the restroom door?",
        "answer": "A drinking fountain.",
        "object_id": 11,
        "class": "drinking fountain",
        "position": [
            9.951333999633789,
            0.061710767447948456,
            -1.68510901927948
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6644406615553998,
            0.0,
            0.747341024748289
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00384-ceJTwFNjqCt_12_drinking_fountain_86663",
        "episode_history": "00384-ceJTwFNjqCt",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly to the right of the drinking fountain in the hallway?",
        "answer": "A restroom door with a sign.",
        "object_id": 12,
        "class": "drinking fountain",
        "position": [
            13.905526161193848,
            0.19653522968292236,
            -0.7522498369216919
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.41351719580144936,
            0.0,
            0.9104963090405725
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00384-ceJTwFNjqCt_30_table_798556",
        "episode_history": "00384-ceJTwFNjqCt",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the small table with the brochure on it?",
        "answer": "The small table with the brochure on it is located in the corner of the room, between two brown chairs, under the posters on the yellow wall.",
        "object_id": 30,
        "class": "table",
        "position": [
            7.499865531921387,
            0.19653522968292236,
            -1.9789328575134277
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9789362372444051,
            0.0,
            0.2041662151526712
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00384-ceJTwFNjqCt_786_monitor_164300",
        "episode_history": "00384-ceJTwFNjqCt",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the monitor on the counter in the music store turned on?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 786,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            -4.457651138305664,
            -0.0034647732973098755,
            -0.6421154737472534
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9816418526478677,
            0.0,
            0.19073351338991706
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00397-ZNanfzgCdm3_3_refrigerator_622596",
        "episode_history": "00397-ZNanfzgCdm3",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the large stainless steel object next to the window in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A refrigerator.",
        "object_id": 3,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -5.604827880859375,
            0.014647245407104492,
            4.472256183624268
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5144354886115369,
            0.0,
            0.8575290829219784
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00397-ZNanfzgCdm3_5_kitchen_table_538077",
        "episode_history": "00397-ZNanfzgCdm3",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What material is the kitchen table that is surrounded by three wooden chairs made of?",
        "answer": "Granite.",
        "object_id": 5,
        "class": "kitchen table",
        "position": [
            -7.414138317108154,
            0.014647245407104492,
            2.9389078617095947
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7452311979142634,
            0.0,
            0.6668061649799527
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00397-ZNanfzgCdm3_25_microwave_52692",
        "episode_history": "00397-ZNanfzgCdm3",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located above the stove in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A microwave.",
        "object_id": 25,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -3.782588481903076,
            0.014647245407104492,
            3.0381486415863037
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9954797549112121,
            0.0,
            0.09497398360559933
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00397-ZNanfzgCdm3_97_bathroom_cabinet_656823",
        "episode_history": "00397-ZNanfzgCdm3",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the small wooden bathroom cabinet?",
        "answer": "The small wooden bathroom cabinet is mounted on the wall above the half-wall divider in the bathroom, near the pictures and the wall-mounted telephone.",
        "object_id": 97,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            -9.799981117248535,
            0.014647245407104492,
            4.643040180206299
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8503946021129377,
            0.0,
            0.5261454368301394
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00397-ZNanfzgCdm3_101_toilet_23456",
        "episode_history": "00397-ZNanfzgCdm3",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the small trash can next to the toilet that is below the wooden cabinet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "Blue.",
        "object_id": 101,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -8.292563438415527,
            0.014647245407104492,
            3.3697094917297363
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9992592555727382,
            0.0,
            0.038482985229800905
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00397-ZNanfzgCdm3_222_tv_777999",
        "episode_history": "00397-ZNanfzgCdm3",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the TV on top of the tall dresser in the bedroom turned on?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 222,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -9.930594444274902,
            -0.18535275757312775,
            -2.331057071685791
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7163938919608316,
            0.0,
            0.6976960595855565
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00397-ZNanfzgCdm3_298_tv_631476",
        "episode_history": "00397-ZNanfzgCdm3",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the TV in the wooden cabinet in the living room turned off?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 298,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -4.630636215209961,
            0.13641706109046936,
            -1.1339831352233887
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7586171346656932,
            0.0,
            0.6515366781629516
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00397-ZNanfzgCdm3_257_laptop_327543",
        "episode_history": "00397-ZNanfzgCdm3",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the laptop located?",
        "answer": "The laptop is on a small wooden table next to the beige sofa, near the window with red curtains in the living room.",
        "object_id": 257,
        "class": "laptop",
        "position": [
            -6.031155586242676,
            0.21667268872261047,
            -0.7439182996749878
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.1958955233576224,
            0.0,
            0.9806247722388228
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00397-ZNanfzgCdm3_391_frame_746348",
        "episode_history": "00397-ZNanfzgCdm3",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the wooden frame that is around the small window near the open door?",
        "answer": "Brown.",
        "object_id": 391,
        "class": "frame",
        "position": [
            -0.6456938982009888,
            2.614647150039673,
            0.09941630065441132
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9274182120043203,
            0.0,
            0.37402601519507966
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00397-ZNanfzgCdm3_418_desk_505009",
        "episode_history": "00397-ZNanfzgCdm3",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located underneath the desk in the corner of the room with pink and blue walls?",
        "answer": "Some books and papers.",
        "object_id": 418,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            -6.29327392578125,
            2.614647150039673,
            -0.101731076836586
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.16978763726885182,
            0.0,
            0.9854806736971866
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00401-H8rQCnvBgo6_21_coffee_table_571882",
        "episode_history": "00401-H8rQCnvBgo6",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lamp on the coffee table between the two sofas in the living room turned on?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 21,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            -3.0594403743743896,
            0.1905980259180069,
            -6.846441268920898
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5771086557207261,
            0.0,
            0.8166673738384658
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00401-H8rQCnvBgo6_27_tv_725465",
        "episode_history": "00401-H8rQCnvBgo6",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the TV in the living room?",
        "answer": "A fireplace.",
        "object_id": 27,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -4.019548416137695,
            0.1905980259180069,
            -4.481156826019287
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6284254239030012,
            0.0,
            0.7778698391069893
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00401-H8rQCnvBgo6_55_fridge_942159",
        "episode_history": "00401-H8rQCnvBgo6",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to store my perishable food items and keep them cold?",
        "answer": "The fridge in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 55,
        "class": "fridge",
        "position": [
            -0.9016990661621094,
            0.1905980259180069,
            -0.6244397759437561
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7485851957748962,
            0.0,
            0.6630386147628661
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00401-H8rQCnvBgo6_64_microwave_634650",
        "episode_history": "00401-H8rQCnvBgo6",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The microwave is above the stove, between the cabinets in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 64,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -2.059352159500122,
            0.052705973386764526,
            0.03359122574329376
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9736067520188499,
            0.0,
            0.2282321020875571
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00401-H8rQCnvBgo6_113_cabinet_650816",
        "episode_history": "00401-H8rQCnvBgo6",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the top drawer of the black cabinet in the bedroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 113,
        "class": "cabinet",
        "position": [
            3.3911666870117188,
            0.1905980259180069,
            -1.823432207107544
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9880531604448277,
            0.0,
            0.15411343917708298
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00401-H8rQCnvBgo6_175_cabinet_698376",
        "episode_history": "00401-H8rQCnvBgo6",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the cabinet that has a mirror on top and is placed against the wall near the hallway entrance?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 175,
        "class": "cabinet",
        "position": [
            0.9393840432167053,
            0.1905980259180069,
            -2.2881667613983154
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4572749812951142,
            0.0,
            0.8893253574938438
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00401-H8rQCnvBgo6_127_bedside_table_72951",
        "episode_history": "00401-H8rQCnvBgo6",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object next to the bed with a lamp on it in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A bedside table.",
        "object_id": 127,
        "class": "bedside table",
        "position": [
            2.709988594055176,
            0.1905980259180069,
            -0.10803957283496857
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5688385913617029,
            0.0,
            0.8224491820031397
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00401-H8rQCnvBgo6_250_bedside_table_279297",
        "episode_history": "00401-H8rQCnvBgo6",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object next to the bed with a lamp and an alarm clock on it in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A bedside table.",
        "object_id": 250,
        "class": "bedside table",
        "position": [
            2.0443732738494873,
            0.1905980259180069,
            -6.005238056182861
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7415541340109442,
            0.0,
            0.6708930364307552
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00401-H8rQCnvBgo6_156_toilet_807950",
        "episode_history": "00401-H8rQCnvBgo6",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the toilet in the house?",
        "answer": "The toilet is in the bathroom, next to the sink and under the towel rack.",
        "object_id": 156,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            3.4648537635803223,
            0.1905980259180069,
            2.067939281463623
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5850396870231768,
            0.0,
            0.8110046637398723
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00401-H8rQCnvBgo6_193_hand_towel_706653",
        "episode_history": "00401-H8rQCnvBgo6",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the hand towel that is hanging on the ring next to the bathroom sink?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 193,
        "class": "hand towel",
        "position": [
            4.653135776519775,
            0.1905980259180069,
            -5.103921413421631
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.08634220648889845,
            0.0,
            0.9962655385882965
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc_333_footrest_208538",
        "episode_history": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object in the middle of the room with four small legs and a cushioned top?",
        "answer": "A footrest.",
        "object_id": 333,
        "class": "footrest",
        "position": [
            7.071571350097656,
            0.07853966951370239,
            -3.395174264907837
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.0575730868607743,
            0.0,
            0.9983412941821658
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc_115_mirror_frame_317610",
        "episode_history": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the mirror frame in the hallway hanging straight on the wall?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 115,
        "class": "mirror frame",
        "position": [
            -0.7888283133506775,
            -0.12146031856536865,
            0.07547172904014587
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9955488580081743,
            0.0,
            0.09424686370709824
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc_440_mirror_frame_443136",
        "episode_history": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the ornate object hanging on the wall above the wooden cabinet in the dining room?",
        "answer": "A mirror frame.",
        "object_id": 440,
        "class": "mirror frame",
        "position": [
            6.929173946380615,
            0.07853966951370239,
            1.4699006080627441
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5687358360132628,
            0.0,
            0.8225202422033727
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc_210_stove_114412",
        "episode_history": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to cook my food?",
        "answer": "The stove on the kitchen counter.",
        "object_id": 210,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            -0.2834319770336151,
            0.07853966951370239,
            -4.341898441314697
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2700510991263432,
            0.0,
            0.9628459917664164
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc_211_oven_192761",
        "episode_history": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object built into the tall white cabinet next to the window in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "An oven.",
        "object_id": 211,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            -3.01446270942688,
            0.07853966951370239,
            -2.6588613986968994
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.05292193803625242,
            0.0,
            0.9985986523496249
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc_291_washing_machine_174423",
        "episode_history": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the washing machine located?",
        "answer": "The washing machine is in the narrow kitchen or laundry area, under the wooden countertop and next to the dishwasher.",
        "object_id": 291,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            4.322283744812012,
            0.07853966951370239,
            -3.6119823455810547
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.18778980236356016,
            0.0,
            0.9822092394842634
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc_292_washing_machine_493495",
        "episode_history": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the washing machine located?",
        "answer": "The washing machine is in the laundry room, under the wooden countertop and next to the dishwasher.",
        "object_id": 292,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            4.350115776062012,
            0.07853966951370239,
            -4.2321038246154785
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.18290082240221553,
            0.0,
            0.9831313692302739
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc_296_microwave_670637",
        "episode_history": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The microwave is on the wooden countertop, next to a small oven, beneath the white cabinets, and near the glass door in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 296,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            3.710259199142456,
            0.07853966951370239,
            -3.270768165588379
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5934595058804958,
            0.0,
            0.8048638486601805
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc_322_clothes_459663",
        "episode_history": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where are the clothes hanging in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "The clothes are hanging on a rod near the window, next to the door in the laundry room.",
        "object_id": 322,
        "class": "clothes",
        "position": [
            4.749977111816406,
            0.07853966951370239,
            -5.093390941619873
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.10067823748544304,
            0.0,
            0.9949190381618118
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc_388_bed_small_276086",
        "episode_history": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to put my baby to sleep safely?",
        "answer": "The small bed in the room.",
        "object_id": 388,
        "class": "bed small",
        "position": [
            8.881509780883789,
            0.07853966951370239,
            -1.754138469696045
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5278183140371969,
            0.0,
            0.8493573025334691
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc_601_bath_wall_366628",
        "episode_history": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bath wall with the window?",
        "answer": "The bath wall with the window is in the bathroom, directly opposite the door, next to the bathtub.",
        "object_id": 601,
        "class": "bath wall",
        "position": [
            15.183588027954102,
            0.07853966951370239,
            -1.084639549255371
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.06619870036103195,
            0.0,
            0.997806460226887
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc_602_step_362691",
        "episode_history": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the step in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The step is next to the bathtub and in front of the toilet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 602,
        "class": "step",
        "position": [
            14.322515487670898,
            0.07853966951370239,
            -3.601776123046875
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6713470661965928,
            0.0,
            0.7411431148632682
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc_604_bathtub_905059",
        "episode_history": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the large rectangular object located beneath the window in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A bathtub.",
        "object_id": 604,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            15.32623291015625,
            0.11079579591751099,
            -1.5292723178863525
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.05327145149424987,
            0.0,
            0.9985800681245824
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc_626_towel_831011",
        "episode_history": "00407-NPHxDe6VeCc",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object hanging on the metal rack next to the door in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A towel.",
        "object_id": 626,
        "class": "towel",
        "position": [
            12.943145751953125,
            0.07853966951370239,
            -3.5316100120544434
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7606666301631316,
            0.0,
            0.6491427252586796
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb_9_bucket_383872",
        "episode_history": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed in the corner near the door in the room?",
        "answer": "A bucket.",
        "object_id": 9,
        "class": "bucket",
        "position": [
            3.6574831008911133,
            0.14677730202674866,
            5.003511428833008
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8993910100163194,
            0.0,
            0.43714506871498016
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb_405_bathroom_cabinet_698755",
        "episode_history": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object directly below the mirror in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A bathroom cabinet.",
        "object_id": 405,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            13.330710411071777,
            0.05261719226837158,
            1.6860313415527344
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8778258534144575,
            0.0,
            0.4789799276349473
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb_86_toilet_792410",
        "episode_history": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to relieve myself?",
        "answer": "The toilet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 86,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            1.4361143112182617,
            0.05261719226837158,
            -8.596437454223633
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8322872814760096,
            0.0,
            0.5543445508826379
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb_108_hanging_clothes_480704",
        "episode_history": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to find something to wear after a shower?",
        "answer": "The hanging clothes in the closet.",
        "object_id": 108,
        "class": "hanging clothes",
        "position": [
            3.3905396461486816,
            0.05261719226837158,
            -5.066646575927734
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9999843752099302,
            0.0,
            0.005590110438532402
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb_109_hanging_clothes_497147",
        "episode_history": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "Are there any empty hangers near the hanging clothes in the closet?",
        "answer": "Yes, there are empty hangers on the left side of the closet.",
        "object_id": 109,
        "class": "hanging clothes",
        "position": [
            2.656216621398926,
            0.05261719226837158,
            -5.099078178405762
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9244066107802033,
            0.0,
            0.3814084660123028
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb_123_desk_910312",
        "episode_history": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to work on my computer or do some writing?",
        "answer": "The desk in the room.",
        "object_id": 123,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            5.969616889953613,
            0.05261719226837158,
            -0.07735539972782135
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9898453432095736,
            0.0,
            0.14214850166752313
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb_157_side_table_141856",
        "episode_history": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the side table that is next to the armchair with a patterned pillow and beneath a large floral painting?",
        "answer": "The side table is cylindrical in shape.",
        "object_id": 157,
        "class": "side table",
        "position": [
            6.807015895843506,
            0.05261719226837158,
            -6.470381736755371
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3391060430228208,
            0.0,
            0.940748155238906
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb_201_tv_230444",
        "episode_history": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to watch my favorite shows and movies?",
        "answer": "The TV on the black stand.",
        "object_id": 201,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            10.993497848510742,
            0.05261719226837158,
            -4.755553245544434
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.40572599577249435,
            0.0,
            0.9139947572904441
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb_287_tv_962500",
        "episode_history": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the TV that is placed on the wooden cabinet with white drawers in the living room?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 287,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            19.92702865600586,
            0.05261719226837158,
            -3.10270357131958
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9944086306959643,
            0.0,
            0.10560054544071901
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb_205_armchair_121415",
        "episode_history": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the armchair with the green cushion?",
        "answer": "The armchair with the green cushion is in the living room, positioned between the TV stand and the coffee table, near the large window.",
        "object_id": 205,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            12.868926048278809,
            0.05261719226837158,
            -4.39249324798584
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6417473025095175,
            0.0,
            0.7669161621205788
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb_207_coffee_table_872035",
        "episode_history": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there a decorative tray on the coffee table in the living room?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 207,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            12.849803924560547,
            0.05261719226837158,
            -3.7248730659484863
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.26815621181083726,
            0.0,
            0.963375443981868
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb_227_range_hood_318174",
        "episode_history": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the range hood in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A gas stove.",
        "object_id": 227,
        "class": "range hood",
        "position": [
            10.060935974121094,
            0.05261719226837158,
            -1.3040874004364014
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9395497001464632,
            0.0,
            0.34241255957498234
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb_233_stovetop_752885",
        "episode_history": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the stovetop in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A range hood.",
        "object_id": 233,
        "class": "stovetop",
        "position": [
            10.38390827178955,
            0.05261719226837158,
            -0.9996734857559204
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9425131496570364,
            0.0,
            0.3341690630856979
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb_234_oven_517837",
        "episode_history": "00417-nGhNxKrgBPb",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the oven under the stove in the kitchen closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 234,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            13.32297134399414,
            0.05261719226837158,
            -1.9993102550506592
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9166513020014401,
            0.0,
            0.3996878663895921
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY_32_wall_tv_719882",
        "episode_history": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to watch my favorite TV shows?",
        "answer": "The wall-mounted TV in the living room.",
        "object_id": 32,
        "class": "wall tv",
        "position": [
            1.5323543548583984,
            0.05638301372528076,
            20.3895320892334
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8297059577315682,
            0.0,
            0.5582007019923398
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY_454_wall_tv_922691",
        "episode_history": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object mounted on the stone wall in the living room?",
        "answer": "A wall tv.",
        "object_id": 454,
        "class": "wall tv",
        "position": [
            15.87960433959961,
            0.05638301372528076,
            26.288196563720703
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.1179574614692008,
            0.0,
            0.9930186490110556
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY_77_copier_machine_899191",
        "episode_history": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly to the left of the copier machine in the office?",
        "answer": "A desk with various items on it.",
        "object_id": 77,
        "class": "copier machine",
        "position": [
            3.0762505531311035,
            0.05638301372528076,
            19.29187774658203
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.17271633147801285,
            0.0,
            0.9849716081394312
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY_80_desk_chair_992087",
        "episode_history": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly in front of the desk chair in the home office?",
        "answer": "A desk with a computer monitor on it.",
        "object_id": 80,
        "class": "desk chair",
        "position": [
            4.922772407531738,
            0.05638301372528076,
            19.340166091918945
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6145437539145117,
            0.0,
            0.7888827381332794
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY_710_desk_chair_629280",
        "episode_history": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the desk chair in front of the window in the bedroom pushed under the desk?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 710,
        "class": "desk chair",
        "position": [
            0.46160659193992615,
            0.05638301372528076,
            5.65415096282959
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7806516781537824,
            0.0,
            0.6249663650114966
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY_297_tv_917681",
        "episode_history": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed in front of the large window with curtains in the living room?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 297,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            6.567523002624512,
            0.05638301372528076,
            22.106693267822266
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8139555036030871,
            0.0,
            0.5809272227691217
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY_421_rack_938799",
        "episode_history": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wooden rack located?",
        "answer": "The wooden rack is in the corner of a room with wooden flooring, next to a white wall and near a window.",
        "object_id": 421,
        "class": "rack",
        "position": [
            15.409132957458496,
            0.05638301372528076,
            19.367599487304688
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.0749779422842189,
            0.0,
            0.9971851925148228
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY_611_stool_852572",
        "episode_history": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the white stool in the room?",
        "answer": "The white stool is under the long wooden desk, positioned between two storage units with multiple drawers, near the window with curtains.",
        "object_id": 611,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            -0.9974979758262634,
            0.05638301372528076,
            11.338451385498047
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3971680196527435,
            0.0,
            0.9177459148179947
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY_662_stool_892976",
        "episode_history": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "Is there enough space under the desk for me to store another stool identical to the one already there?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 662,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            4.507641792297363,
            0.05638301372528076,
            5.617273330688477
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.48771590607953114,
            0.0,
            0.8730024026066721
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY_613_storage_box_811496",
        "episode_history": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where are the stackable storage boxes with drawers?",
        "answer": "The stackable storage boxes with drawers are on the long wooden desk under the bulletin board, next to the window with the curtains.",
        "object_id": 613,
        "class": "storage box",
        "position": [
            -0.9664607048034668,
            0.05638301372528076,
            11.11844539642334
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4983287547593181,
            0.0,
            0.8669881499651696
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY_756_cardboard_box_248556",
        "episode_history": "00434-L5QEsaVqwrY",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the cardboard box on the top shelf in the kitchen open?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 756,
        "class": "cardboard box",
        "position": [
            -2.3315088748931885,
            0.05638301372528076,
            5.175029754638672
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.180846025138189,
            0.0,
            0.9835114209767559
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00444-sX9xad6ULKc_24_sofa_chair_738500",
        "episode_history": "00444-sX9xad6ULKc",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there a cushion on the sofa chair in the living room next to the wooden side table?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 24,
        "class": "sofa chair",
        "position": [
            5.785521507263184,
            0.08200240880250931,
            -1.5600191354751587
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7892980535997085,
            0.0,
            0.6140102463181797
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00444-sX9xad6ULKc_142_dining_table_294095",
        "episode_history": "00444-sX9xad6ULKc",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the dining table in the dining area?",
        "answer": "A chandelier with multiple light fixtures.",
        "object_id": 142,
        "class": "dining table",
        "position": [
            3.4805850982666016,
            0.21234259009361267,
            -2.805880546569824
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6346101031617333,
            0.0,
            0.7728324637106377
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00444-sX9xad6ULKc_65_electric_box_979255",
        "episode_history": "00444-sX9xad6ULKc",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the electric box that is mounted on the wall near the glass door leading to the patio?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 65,
        "class": "electric box",
        "position": [
            13.120430946350098,
            0.08200240880250931,
            -3.473325729370117
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9593683913228681,
            0.0,
            0.28215649865025594
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00444-sX9xad6ULKc_220_desk_226769",
        "episode_history": "00444-sX9xad6ULKc",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the mirror that is hanging on the wall near the desk with a black chair?",
        "answer": "The mirror is circular with a decorative frame.",
        "object_id": 220,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            -1.3778481483459473,
            0.08200240880250931,
            -1.7613742351531982
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4194713363391341,
            0.0,
            0.9077685817375819
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00444-sX9xad6ULKc_102_coffee_machine_227627",
        "episode_history": "00444-sX9xad6ULKc",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to make a cup of coffee in the morning?",
        "answer": "The coffee machine on the kitchen counter.",
        "object_id": 102,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            10.189891815185547,
            0.08200240880250931,
            -2.695132255554199
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8781080416018942,
            0.0,
            0.4784623990180276
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00444-sX9xad6ULKc_79_oven_and_stove_500449",
        "episode_history": "00444-sX9xad6ULKc",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the oven and stove that is located below the microwave and next to the wooden cabinets in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 79,
        "class": "oven and stove",
        "position": [
            12.627458572387695,
            0.08200240880250931,
            -3.1390459537506104
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4440018790949681,
            0.0,
            0.8960258541806354
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00444-sX9xad6ULKc_80_microwave_299778",
        "episode_history": "00444-sX9xad6ULKc",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The microwave is above the stove, mounted on the wall between the wooden cabinets in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 80,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            9.57109260559082,
            0.08200240880250931,
            -2.8731861114501953
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.1884960246717914,
            0.0,
            0.982073952756579
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00444-sX9xad6ULKc_226_computer_359592",
        "episode_history": "00444-sX9xad6ULKc",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the computer that is on the wooden desk near the large window with blinds?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 226,
        "class": "computer",
        "position": [
            -2.725698947906494,
            0.08200240880250931,
            -4.213375091552734
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9932762706870568,
            0.0,
            0.11576808752853675
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00444-sX9xad6ULKc_239_rack_356774",
        "episode_history": "00444-sX9xad6ULKc",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the top shelf of the left rack in the room empty?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 239,
        "class": "rack",
        "position": [
            -1.6192395687103271,
            0.08200240880250931,
            -3.558821678161621
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9618710483206624,
            0.0,
            0.27350335720519076
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00444-sX9xad6ULKc_410_drawer_895899",
        "episode_history": "00444-sX9xad6ULKc",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are all the drawers in the wooden dresser under the mirror in the bedroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 410,
        "class": "drawer",
        "position": [
            11.132766723632812,
            0.08200240880250931,
            7.392509460449219
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4644205702198062,
            0.0,
            0.8856147774042109
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_71_wall_board_923815",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wall board located in the basement?",
        "answer": "The wall board is mounted on the wall above the black storage shelves filled with various items, including bags and boxes, in the basement.",
        "object_id": 71,
        "class": "wall board",
        "position": [
            -10.153253555297852,
            -2.59987473487854,
            0.20293833315372467
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9047107933353454,
            0.0,
            0.4260262672917361
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_93_washing_machine_and_dryer_808616",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located to the right of the washing machine and dryer in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "A black storage rack with various cleaning supplies and other items.",
        "object_id": 93,
        "class": "washing machine and dryer",
        "position": [
            -7.948749542236328,
            -2.59987473487854,
            0.8363088369369507
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.911331649818623,
            0.0,
            0.4116729576239694
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_94_washing_machine_and_dryer_467324",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the washing machine next to the dryer in the basement open?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 94,
        "class": "washing machine and dryer",
        "position": [
            -8.902155876159668,
            -2.59987473487854,
            0.1449507772922516
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9996500108369457,
            0.0,
            0.026454788482000016
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_103_refrigerator_316710",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the refrigerator next to the washing machine in the basement closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 103,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -9.937400817871094,
            -2.59987473487854,
            0.6655343174934387
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9138172976454252,
            0.0,
            0.40612553050013045
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_512_refrigerator_773267",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located directly above the refrigerator in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A wooden cabinet and a clock.",
        "object_id": 512,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -9.316308975219727,
            0.09277992695569992,
            1.9622337818145752
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6144833303736289,
            0.0,
            0.7889298046676483
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_347_painting_277473",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the painting of the tree?",
        "answer": "The painting of the tree is hanging on the wall above the sofa in the living room, between two lamps on side tables.",
        "object_id": 347,
        "class": "painting",
        "position": [
            0.1210426464676857,
            -0.04145461320877075,
            2.099199056625366
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.16292679417740288,
            0.0,
            0.9866381604920186
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_352_chest_of_drawers_425585",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located between the sofa and the window in the living room?",
        "answer": "A chest of drawers.",
        "object_id": 352,
        "class": "chest of drawers",
        "position": [
            2.361207962036133,
            0.0001251697540283203,
            2.758098602294922
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.00889635172755876,
            0.0,
            0.9999604266799459
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_356_side_table_514177",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lamp on the side table next to the sofa in the living room turned on?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 356,
        "class": "side table",
        "position": [
            0.9146841764450073,
            0.0001251697540283203,
            1.2421125173568726
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.39981727728474814,
            0.0,
            0.9165948640400571
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_472_side_table_691561",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the side table that is placed against the wall with floral wallpaper in the dining room?",
        "answer": "The side table has intricate carvings with floral and scroll patterns.",
        "object_id": 472,
        "class": "side table",
        "position": [
            -10.681248664855957,
            0.20012521743774414,
            -3.2159361839294434
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9988079141305982,
            0.0,
            0.048813427149573846
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_368_tv_557463",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the small table against the wall, below the decorative mirror in the living room?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 368,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -0.8625528812408447,
            -0.11021667718887329,
            0.7577882409095764
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9389032766805844,
            0.0,
            0.34418111081008135
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_369_tv_stand_558648",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What are the colors of the TV stand that is placed below the decorative mirror on the wall?",
        "answer": "The TV stand has light wood legs and a gray shelf.",
        "object_id": 369,
        "class": "tv stand",
        "position": [
            2.8733129501342773,
            0.0001251697540283203,
            0.8618641495704651
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9231191415671453,
            0.0,
            0.38451404457098426
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_413_fireplace_571358",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to warm up the living room?",
        "answer": "The fireplace.",
        "object_id": 413,
        "class": "fireplace",
        "position": [
            -7.230520248413086,
            0.03979281336069107,
            -1.6311781406402588
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.252007605507619,
            0.0,
            0.9677252537607542
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_447_coffee_table_235699",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object in front of the sofa and between the two armchairs in the living room?",
        "answer": "A coffee table.",
        "object_id": 447,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            -6.908367156982422,
            0.06294560432434082,
            -0.6290315389633179
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3850300256130143,
            0.0,
            0.9229040466789825
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_473_dining_table_529503",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the dining table that is placed on the patterned rug in the dining room?",
        "answer": "Dark brown.",
        "object_id": 473,
        "class": "dining table",
        "position": [
            -8.965996742248535,
            0.0465313196182251,
            0.6322604417800903
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.13447462164128926,
            0.0,
            0.9909170379675748
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_489_recycle_bin_919392",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to dispose of recyclable materials?",
        "answer": "The recycle bin next to the table.",
        "object_id": 489,
        "class": "recycle bin",
        "position": [
            -9.236776351928711,
            0.09933540225028992,
            2.180298328399658
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6656372623279307,
            0.0,
            0.7462754417777511
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_506_window_shade_389434",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the window shade that is above the kitchen sink and surrounded by wooden cabinets?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 506,
        "class": "window shade",
        "position": [
            -8.220008850097656,
            0.0001251697540283203,
            0.2741723656654358
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9938417296134248,
            0.0,
            0.11080891877008431
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_520_microwave_837592",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to quickly heat up my leftovers?",
        "answer": "The microwave above the stove.",
        "object_id": 520,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -9.228586196899414,
            0.09215108305215836,
            0.5145798921585083
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9998536030941839,
            0.0,
            0.017110592609439142
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_526_cooker_575389",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the toaster oven on the kitchen counter next to the refrigerator closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 526,
        "class": "cooker",
        "position": [
            -7.847940921783447,
            0.0001251697540283203,
            2.0779032707214355
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6985471020341874,
            0.0,
            0.7155640755653114
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_536_kitchen_table_353998",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object in the center of the kitchen with a floral tablecloth and surrounded by chairs?",
        "answer": "A kitchen table.",
        "object_id": 536,
        "class": "kitchen table",
        "position": [
            -7.280978202819824,
            0.05812445282936096,
            0.5760141015052795
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7872417370037763,
            0.0,
            0.6166445065994484
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_569_blinds_463897",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the blinds in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A toilet paper holder.",
        "object_id": 569,
        "class": "blinds",
        "position": [
            -5.502061367034912,
            0.09639471769332886,
            0.38769692182540894
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9999855763351742,
            0.0,
            0.005370951590019573
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_571_toilet_51358",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to relieve myself?",
        "answer": "The toilet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 571,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -5.144987106323242,
            0.021002285182476044,
            0.9659323692321777
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9904329890388069,
            0.0,
            0.13799454418074594
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_771_toilet_811703",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to relieve myself?",
        "answer": "The toilet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 771,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -6.081755638122559,
            2.8001253604888916,
            0.3157806098461151
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9995308290219842,
            0.0,
            0.030628774617813246
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_645_file_cabinet_937826",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the top drawer of the file cabinet in the room with the slanted ceiling closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 645,
        "class": "file cabinet",
        "position": [
            -0.6909552812576294,
            2.8001253604888916,
            0.6779637336730957
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9460502760446319,
            0.0,
            0.3240198685202436
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_701_nightstand_753054",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the drawer of the nightstand next to the bed in the bedroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 701,
        "class": "nightstand",
        "position": [
            -7.4003095626831055,
            2.8001253604888916,
            -1.289581298828125
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.07964868379715412,
            0.0,
            0.9968229969103747
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_742_desk_71857",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are all the drawers of the wooden desk in the room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 742,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            -8.070850372314453,
            2.957963466644287,
            2.4795267581939697
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.28565047783303876,
            0.0,
            0.9583338690215204
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8_766_bathtub_949314",
        "episode_history": "00487-erXNfWVjqZ8",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the large white object with a towel hanging over it in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A bathtub.",
        "object_id": 766,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            -6.561436653137207,
            2.8001253604888916,
            0.36734887957572937
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9650850017520028,
            0.0,
            0.2619368996406143
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k_130_table_434589",
        "episode_history": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the drawer of the table in the hallway under the round mirror closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 130,
        "class": "table",
        "position": [
            2.1149861812591553,
            0.08998584747314453,
            1.969797134399414
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5502568696679513,
            0.0,
            0.8349954355463431
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k_105_painting_frame_912422",
        "episode_history": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where are the two painting frames with golden borders located?",
        "answer": "The two painting frames with golden borders are hung on the wall in the hallway, near the staircase and the entrance to the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 105,
        "class": "painting frame",
        "position": [
            3.1200613975524902,
            0.08998584747314453,
            0.9305545687675476
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2985825660134043,
            0.0,
            0.9543838071095145
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k_182_stool_761520",
        "episode_history": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are the two stools in front of the kitchen counter aligned evenly?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 182,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            -5.710502624511719,
            0.08998584747314453,
            -3.788339614868164
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9657739659513568,
            0.0,
            0.25938513197673374
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k_183_stool_553798",
        "episode_history": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "How many stools are placed under the counter in the kitchen area?",
        "answer": "Two stools.",
        "object_id": 183,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            -7.132994174957275,
            0.08998584747314453,
            -3.04571533203125
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8779967505916471,
            0.0,
            0.4786665916381768
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k_194_microwave_943161",
        "episode_history": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the microwave that is installed above the stove and below the wooden cabinets?",
        "answer": "Silver.",
        "object_id": 194,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -3.6283864974975586,
            0.08998584747314453,
            0.2885653078556061
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9950221251425238,
            0.0,
            0.09965425468516097
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k_294_cabinet_956942",
        "episode_history": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the cabinet that is next to the glass doors leading to the patio?",
        "answer": "Wood.",
        "object_id": 294,
        "class": "cabinet",
        "position": [
            -6.2374420166015625,
            0.08998584747314453,
            -4.223640441894531
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9686135225526954,
            0.0,
            0.24857160724438848
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k_204_refrigerator_731518",
        "episode_history": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the refrigerator in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A white door.",
        "object_id": 204,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -3.6562764644622803,
            0.08998584747314453,
            4.485642910003662
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3341626937345374,
            0.0,
            0.9425154078931961
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k_258_wall_tv_943674",
        "episode_history": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the wall-mounted TV in the living room turned off?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 258,
        "class": "wall tv",
        "position": [
            -5.718389511108398,
            0.08998584747314453,
            -2.7783420085906982
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3697622872597087,
            0.0,
            0.9291263912517331
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k_263_lamp_shade_671490",
        "episode_history": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lamp shade on the table next to the sofa in the living room straightened?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 263,
        "class": "lamp shade",
        "position": [
            -5.223812103271484,
            0.08998584747314453,
            -3.733583927154541
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7932048116312969,
            0.0,
            0.6089549464492089
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k_268_armchair_372868",
        "episode_history": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is behind the armchair near the fireplace?",
        "answer": "A floor lamp and a window.",
        "object_id": 268,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            -6.55678653717041,
            0.08998584747314453,
            -3.9368157386779785
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.11817604603432601,
            0.0,
            0.9929926596625439
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k_492_armchair_267770",
        "episode_history": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object with a yellow blanket draped over it, located near the large window in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "An armchair.",
        "object_id": 492,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            -5.343933582305908,
            2.8899857997894287,
            0.1385277509689331
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8348487562384785,
            0.0,
            0.5504793858148236
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k_280_fireplace_929068",
        "episode_history": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to warm up the living room on a cold day?",
        "answer": "The fireplace in the living room.",
        "object_id": 280,
        "class": "fireplace",
        "position": [
            -6.461463928222656,
            0.08998584747314453,
            -4.760139465332031
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.1487267469881948,
            0.0,
            0.9888783316112804
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k_289_decorative_plant_250386",
        "episode_history": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the decorative plant located?",
        "answer": "The decorative plant is on a black console table under the TV, near the door and next to the armchair in the living room.",
        "object_id": 289,
        "class": "decorative plant",
        "position": [
            -6.505099296569824,
            0.08998584747314453,
            -3.0277299880981445
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2301237516363513,
            0.0,
            0.9731613735310352
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k_307_dining_table_16760",
        "episode_history": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I set up a place to eat my meals?",
        "answer": "The dining table in the dining area.",
        "object_id": 307,
        "class": "dining table",
        "position": [
            -6.579274654388428,
            0.08998584747314453,
            -1.6486456394195557
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9856221949983133,
            0.0,
            0.16896416403104114
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k_349_washing_machine_and_dryer_700586",
        "episode_history": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the washing machine and dryer that are placed side by side under the shelf in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 349,
        "class": "washing machine and dryer",
        "position": [
            -1.9046082496643066,
            0.08998584747314453,
            -4.461066246032715
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.1684650660837232,
            0.0,
            0.9857076247596986
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k_361_chest_382510",
        "episode_history": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wooden chest with the curved legs?",
        "answer": "The wooden chest with the curved legs is in the room with the large window, placed against the wall directly under the window.",
        "object_id": 361,
        "class": "chest",
        "position": [
            0.8907685279846191,
            2.8899857997894287,
            -4.110792636871338
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8634982285379635,
            0.0,
            0.5043518705346485
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k_465_mirror_frame_900302",
        "episode_history": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the mirror with the wooden frame located?",
        "answer": "The mirror with the wooden frame is on top of the dresser in the bedroom, next to a lamp and some electronic devices.",
        "object_id": 465,
        "class": "mirror frame",
        "position": [
            -7.897922515869141,
            2.8899857997894287,
            0.5802670121192932
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.319564577478643,
            0.0,
            0.9475644995570995
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k_533_mirror_frame_859109",
        "episode_history": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the frame of the mirror that is above the sink and next to the bathtub in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The frame is gray.",
        "object_id": 533,
        "class": "mirror frame",
        "position": [
            -5.137921333312988,
            2.8899857997894287,
            -2.0653059482574463
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.009794908377179612,
            0.0,
            0.9999520287343202
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k_513_shower_cabin_180911",
        "episode_history": "00534-DBBESbk4Y3k",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the frame material of the shower cabin that is next to the bathtub and toilet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "Metal.",
        "object_id": 513,
        "class": "shower cabin",
        "position": [
            -4.883060932159424,
            2.8899857997894287,
            -3.2151060104370117
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8520535161378597,
            0.0,
            0.5234546834608609
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR_54_trashcan_255477",
        "episode_history": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the small trashcan next to the toilet in the bathroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 54,
        "class": "trashcan",
        "position": [
            -5.654139041900635,
            -0.3383864760398865,
            -0.4014148712158203
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9386239949613967,
            0.0,
            0.34494201843600986
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR_141_shower_tub_76201",
        "episode_history": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the glass door of the shower tub in the bathroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 141,
        "class": "shower tub",
        "position": [
            6.887487411499023,
            -0.4827690124511719,
            1.9691864252090454
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3282427160824999,
            0.0,
            0.9445934148292499
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR_143_soap_dispenser_shelf_in_shower_78865",
        "episode_history": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the soap dispenser shelf in the shower empty?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 143,
        "class": "soap dispenser shelf in shower",
        "position": [
            8.734468460083008,
            -0.3828825354576111,
            0.2908761501312256
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.04974673049181434,
            0.0,
            0.9987618649134411
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR_267_tv_393318",
        "episode_history": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the TV mounted on the wall in the living room?",
        "answer": "A brown leather recliner chair.",
        "object_id": 267,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            8.881757736206055,
            2.717231035232544,
            6.768195629119873
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.40852422086212276,
            0.0,
            0.9127474793002693
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR_444_tv_914961",
        "episode_history": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the TV that is mounted on the wall between two white chairs?",
        "answer": "It is in rectangular shape.",
        "object_id": 444,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -5.338683128356934,
            2.717231035232544,
            6.807657718658447
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5962500383527962,
            0.0,
            0.8027987865986651
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR_285_refrigerator_167788",
        "episode_history": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the stainless steel refrigerator?",
        "answer": "The stainless steel refrigerator is in the kitchen, next to the door and adjacent to the stove and white cabinets.",
        "object_id": 285,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            6.081679344177246,
            2.717231035232544,
            4.0483245849609375
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.49196727519467043,
            0.0,
            0.8706136916781928
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR_320_bench_731591",
        "episode_history": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the small wooden bench with white legs?",
        "answer": "The small wooden bench with white legs is in the hallway, placed on a rug under a wall-mounted shelf with hooks.",
        "object_id": 320,
        "class": "bench",
        "position": [
            -0.3413163125514984,
            2.717231035232544,
            -0.4639941453933716
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8292666813450479,
            0.0,
            0.5588530855340883
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR_359_shelf_310991",
        "episode_history": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object mounted on the wall above the bench in the hallway?",
        "answer": "A shelf.",
        "object_id": 359,
        "class": "shelf",
        "position": [
            -0.3187985122203827,
            2.717231035232544,
            -0.5059467554092407
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7426900687003894,
            0.0,
            0.6696353200465242
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR_381_coffee_machine_666079",
        "episode_history": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to make a cup of coffee in the morning?",
        "answer": "The coffee machine on the kitchen counter.",
        "object_id": 381,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            4.402807712554932,
            2.717231035232544,
            0.14451400935649872
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3312446989930337,
            0.0,
            0.9435448846711081
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR_387_basket_937152",
        "episode_history": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the basket on the kitchen counter?",
        "answer": "A set of white kitchen cabinets.",
        "object_id": 387,
        "class": "basket",
        "position": [
            8.057051658630371,
            2.717231035232544,
            0.17482152581214905
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.36461104168638164,
            0.0,
            0.9311599155249176
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR_473_shower_mat_471065",
        "episode_history": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the texture pattern of the shower mat that is placed in front of the shower area near the bathtub?",
        "answer": "The pattern is a gradient of small, densely packed loops, transitioning from light to dark shades.",
        "object_id": 473,
        "class": "shower mat",
        "position": [
            -5.790288925170898,
            2.717231035232544,
            2.040217399597168
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.12559288711123412,
            0.0,
            0.9920818649219755
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR_474_shower_mat_13922",
        "episode_history": "00539-zUG6FL9TYeR",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color pattern of the shower mat that is placed in front of the shower and the bathroom sink?",
        "answer": "The pattern consists of alternating light and dark gray stripes.",
        "object_id": 474,
        "class": "shower mat",
        "position": [
            -6.604769706726074,
            2.842057466506958,
            2.1954452991485596
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4379249754149063,
            0.0,
            0.8990115215656881
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S_18_tv_887409",
        "episode_history": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the TV that is placed on the cabinet below the wall with multiple framed pictures?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 18,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            3.8606040477752686,
            0.1610340178012848,
            -0.900944173336029
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9170457221789067,
            0.0,
            0.398782075115429
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S_80_laundry_basket_906314",
        "episode_history": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the laundry basket next to the washing machine in the laundry room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 80,
        "class": "laundry basket",
        "position": [
            3.94612717628479,
            0.1610340178012848,
            1.9058935642242432
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6966231654430377,
            0.0,
            0.7174372205065207
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S_82_laundry_machine_920437",
        "episode_history": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the laundry machine located?",
        "answer": "The laundry machine is in the laundry room, at the end of the hallway with the floral rug, next to the wicker basket.",
        "object_id": 82,
        "class": "laundry machine",
        "position": [
            5.631932258605957,
            0.1610340178012848,
            1.94669508934021
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7905280399143317,
            0.0,
            0.6124258470290134
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S_395_basket_694543",
        "episode_history": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the woven basket in the corner of the room next to the window empty?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 395,
        "class": "basket",
        "position": [
            1.7841588258743286,
            2.7610340118408203,
            3.1481361389160156
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3588554004973579,
            0.0,
            0.9333931655705867
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S_119_fridge_800306",
        "episode_history": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the fridge in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The fridge is in the kitchen, positioned next to the pantry door and across from the counter with bar stools.",
        "object_id": 119,
        "class": "fridge",
        "position": [
            6.966452121734619,
            0.1610340178012848,
            1.7681519985198975
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8493199733282675,
            0.0,
            0.5278783788958125
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S_133_cooker_844086",
        "episode_history": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the cooker in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The cooker is in the kitchen, positioned between the countertop and the cabinets, directly under the microwave.",
        "object_id": 133,
        "class": "cooker",
        "position": [
            7.161357402801514,
            0.1610340178012848,
            0.5443262457847595
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7361688591040163,
            0.0,
            0.6767979099299074
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S_134_cooker_504156",
        "episode_history": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the cooker that is located below the microwave and between the wooden cabinets in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 134,
        "class": "cooker",
        "position": [
            8.76518440246582,
            0.1610340178012848,
            0.12931759655475616
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8271256901748589,
            0.0,
            0.562016986089178
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S_412_towel_bar_260782",
        "episode_history": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the towel hanging on the towel bar in the bathroom neatly folded?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 412,
        "class": "towel bar",
        "position": [
            4.894744873046875,
            2.7610340118408203,
            3.2887067794799805
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.10753688489410115,
            0.0,
            0.9942010955472101
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S_229_toilet_554346",
        "episode_history": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located to the right of the toilet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A wooden vanity with a sink and a floral arrangement on top.",
        "object_id": 229,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            7.506529808044434,
            0.1610340178012848,
            4.207046031951904
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6455163257483819,
            0.0,
            0.7637464718035095
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S_437_bathtub_123631",
        "episode_history": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the bathtub in the bathroom empty?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 437,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            8.952220916748047,
            2.7610340118408203,
            0.6415724754333496
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6471971341147915,
            0.0,
            0.7623226807550728
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S_482_nightstand_629595",
        "episode_history": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the nightstand that is next to the bed with floral-patterned pillows and a lamp on top?",
        "answer": "Dark brown.",
        "object_id": 482,
        "class": "nightstand",
        "position": [
            10.955521583557129,
            2.7610340118408203,
            -0.4454426169395447
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6830223305315963,
            0.0,
            0.7303974917777215
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S_484_nightstand_929484",
        "episode_history": "00547-9h5JJxM6E5S",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the nightstand with the lamp on it?",
        "answer": "The nightstand with the lamp on it is in the bedroom, next to the bed and near the closet door.",
        "object_id": 484,
        "class": "nightstand",
        "position": [
            10.933985710144043,
            2.7610340118408203,
            1.6478452682495117
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7717564185511002,
            0.0,
            0.6359182576598811
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00557-fRZhp6vWGw7_440_basket_684943",
        "episode_history": "00557-fRZhp6vWGw7",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the floor next to the bookshelf in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "A basket.",
        "object_id": 440,
        "class": "basket",
        "position": [
            2.518585205078125,
            -3.0916595458984375,
            -4.260024070739746
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9516190147090537,
            0.0,
            0.3072804107719364
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00557-fRZhp6vWGw7_135_rocking_chair_706558",
        "episode_history": "00557-fRZhp6vWGw7",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the cushion of the rocking chair that is placed near the window with tree-patterned curtains?",
        "answer": "The pattern on the cushion is floral.",
        "object_id": 135,
        "class": "rocking chair",
        "position": [
            2.1346852779388428,
            0.10834050178527832,
            -6.121950149536133
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8233115156679429,
            0.0,
            0.5675897710217782
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00557-fRZhp6vWGw7_139_wall_clock_675328",
        "episode_history": "00557-fRZhp6vWGw7",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the round object with Roman numerals on the wall next to the window in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A wall clock.",
        "object_id": 139,
        "class": "wall clock",
        "position": [
            0.5220201015472412,
            0.10834050178527832,
            -5.954526901245117
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.49744038974207383,
            0.0,
            0.8674981606051125
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00557-fRZhp6vWGw7_458_globe_908152",
        "episode_history": "00557-fRZhp6vWGw7",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the globe on the stand in the corner of the room next to the window covered with dust?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 458,
        "class": "globe",
        "position": [
            0.06387333571910858,
            -3.0916595458984375,
            -4.602413177490234
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.15629818851040161,
            0.0,
            0.9877099150400218
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8_99_desk_839735",
        "episode_history": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the chair at the desk in the room with the colorful wall silhouettes pushed in?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 99,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            7.91834020614624,
            0.08355426788330078,
            -12.82282543182373
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9016241385088126,
            0.0,
            0.4325204190072899
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8_132_tv_517653",
        "episode_history": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the TV mounted on the wall in the bedroom turned on?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 132,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            11.08642578125,
            0.08355426788330078,
            -12.071088790893555
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8746410226103494,
            0.0,
            0.4847711641250149
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8_326_tv_965705",
        "episode_history": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wall-mounted TV located?",
        "answer": "The wall-mounted TV is in the living room, positioned on the wall between the large sofa and the window with curtains.",
        "object_id": 326,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            9.848074913024902,
            0.08355426788330078,
            2.9484453201293945
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4264797207908447,
            0.0,
            0.9044971242376413
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8_247_bathtub_484805",
        "episode_history": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the towel hanging over the bathtub in the bathroom dry?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 247,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            7.931812763214111,
            0.08355426788330078,
            -6.598785877227783
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9143867982725115,
            0.0,
            0.40484167664031984
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8_243_trashcan_599100",
        "episode_history": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I dispose of the used tissues?",
        "answer": "The trashcan next to the sink in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 243,
        "class": "trashcan",
        "position": [
            7.461017608642578,
            0.08355426788330078,
            -5.1326470375061035
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.938461153165461,
            0.0,
            0.3453848056868641
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8_302_basket_783205",
        "episode_history": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the basket that is placed on the floor near the console table with decorative items?",
        "answer": "The basket is in a cylindrical shape.",
        "object_id": 302,
        "class": "basket",
        "position": [
            5.094473838806152,
            0.08355426788330078,
            0.5082180500030518
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9161218618331712,
            0.0,
            0.40089990555165234
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8_327_basket_93156",
        "episode_history": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is the object to the left of the basket under the TV?",
        "answer": "A sofa.",
        "object_id": 327,
        "class": "basket",
        "position": [
            9.731678009033203,
            0.08355426788330078,
            0.8761321902275085
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6660306909425876,
            0.0,
            0.7459243384704238
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8_346_magazine_162852",
        "episode_history": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the magazine that is placed on the small table near the two velvet armchairs and the large window with curtains?",
        "answer": "The magazine has a mix of colors, primarily featuring shades of brown and beige.",
        "object_id": 346,
        "class": "magazine",
        "position": [
            7.387479782104492,
            0.08355426788330078,
            4.328073501586914
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5654910585364801,
            0.0,
            0.8247544257021548
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8_359_stack_of_trays_442438",
        "episode_history": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color pattern of the stack of trays that is placed on the mirrored coffee table in front of the TV?",
        "answer": "The trays have a striped pattern with alternating black and white colors.",
        "object_id": 359,
        "class": "stack of trays",
        "position": [
            9.149365425109863,
            0.08355426788330078,
            2.5537490844726562
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6275793508385727,
            0.0,
            0.7785526047744209
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8_390_microwave_805913",
        "episode_history": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The microwave is built into the wall cabinet next to the oven in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 390,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            0.9378761649131775,
            0.08355426788330078,
            2.346367120742798
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6969586670953395,
            0.0,
            0.7171112998417245
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8_391_oven_797234",
        "episode_history": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the built-in oven in the kitchen closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 391,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            1.3127540349960327,
            0.08355426788330078,
            2.9623615741729736
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6104671480605697,
            0.0,
            0.7920415779103989
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8_418_coffee_machine_76696",
        "episode_history": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the coffee machine on the kitchen counter?",
        "answer": "A set of white cabinets.",
        "object_id": 418,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            -0.39130693674087524,
            0.08355426788330078,
            4.728350639343262
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2751902025091978,
            0.0,
            0.9613898025478255
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8_512_dresser_354363",
        "episode_history": "00567-KjZrPggnHm8",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the top drawer of the dresser in the hallway closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 512,
        "class": "dresser",
        "position": [
            3.5138683319091797,
            0.08355426788330078,
            -2.6596601009368896
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3019635486006382,
            0.0,
            0.9533194718018247
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00590-qgZhhx1MpTi_170_tv_388786",
        "episode_history": "00590-qgZhhx1MpTi",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object mounted on the wall near the entrance to the closet in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 170,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            2.9427952766418457,
            2.9378414154052734,
            -3.252826690673828
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9370776484583091,
            0.0,
            0.3491210116275527
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00590-qgZhhx1MpTi_274_tv_596461",
        "episode_history": "00590-qgZhhx1MpTi",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the TV mounted on the wall in the living room turned off?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 274,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            9.945070266723633,
            0.13784140348434448,
            -1.6896686553955078
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.07403640959990397,
            0.0,
            0.99725553899367
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00590-qgZhhx1MpTi_172_desk_98872",
        "episode_history": "00590-qgZhhx1MpTi",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed against the wall under the window next to the bed in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A desk.",
        "object_id": 172,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            2.825340986251831,
            2.9378414154052734,
            -1.6596155166625977
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7745527080613313,
            0.0,
            0.6325093694443253
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00590-qgZhhx1MpTi_256_armchair_847642",
        "episode_history": "00590-qgZhhx1MpTi",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the cushion of the armchair that is placed near the sliding glass door and next to the wicker sofa?",
        "answer": "The pattern on the cushion is a series of circular designs.",
        "object_id": 256,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            12.262423515319824,
            -0.062158599495887756,
            -1.5975303649902344
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.01964264004628175,
            0.0,
            0.9998070647339977
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00590-qgZhhx1MpTi_287_blanket_91711",
        "episode_history": "00590-qgZhhx1MpTi",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the blanket that is draped over the back of the brown couch near the lamp?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 287,
        "class": "blanket",
        "position": [
            9.417512893676758,
            0.295101523399353,
            0.9942425489425659
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3134770862800369,
            0.0,
            0.9495957647216937
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00590-qgZhhx1MpTi_292_tray_573032",
        "episode_history": "00590-qgZhhx1MpTi",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the tray that is placed on the dark brown ottoman in the living room?",
        "answer": "Wood.",
        "object_id": 292,
        "class": "tray",
        "position": [
            10.714263916015625,
            0.13784140348434448,
            -3.3178067207336426
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8964588479746076,
            0.0,
            0.44312699521473453
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00590-qgZhhx1MpTi_326_refrigerator_40555",
        "episode_history": "00590-qgZhhx1MpTi",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the large stainless steel object located between the wooden cabinets in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A refrigerator.",
        "object_id": 326,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            5.958346843719482,
            0.13784140348434448,
            -1.7409167289733887
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7692086672079174,
            0.0,
            0.6389976731508648
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00590-qgZhhx1MpTi_333_microwave_546511",
        "episode_history": "00590-qgZhhx1MpTi",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located above the stove in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A microwave.",
        "object_id": 333,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            3.860382318496704,
            0.15640723705291748,
            -1.5416351556777954
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4029049041899533,
            0.0,
            0.9152418468250262
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00590-qgZhhx1MpTi_358_coffee_machine_885196",
        "episode_history": "00590-qgZhhx1MpTi",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to make a cup of coffee in the morning?",
        "answer": "The coffee machine on the countertop.",
        "object_id": 358,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            3.6665496826171875,
            0.1748931109905243,
            -1.83689546585083
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9012753672235367,
            0.0,
            0.43324671081968885
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00590-qgZhhx1MpTi_472_ladder_813993",
        "episode_history": "00590-qgZhhx1MpTi",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object leaning against the wall above the white refrigerator in the garage?",
        "answer": "A ladder.",
        "object_id": 472,
        "class": "ladder",
        "position": [
            0.8270139098167419,
            -0.062158599495887756,
            -2.04392147064209
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.05115627698189988,
            0.0,
            0.9986906604776833
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb_25_fire_extinguisher_572486",
        "episode_history": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the red object mounted on the wall near the hallway entrance with patterned carpet?",
        "answer": "A fire extinguisher.",
        "object_id": 25,
        "class": "fire extinguisher",
        "position": [
            12.026787757873535,
            0.13590310513973236,
            -9.500799179077148
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.24138649005798776,
            0.0,
            0.97042906099183
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb_26_painting_207117",
        "episode_history": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the painting with the ornate frame?",
        "answer": "The painting with the ornate frame is hung on the wall between two wall sconces, above a small table with two chairs in the hallway.",
        "object_id": 26,
        "class": "painting",
        "position": [
            10.088048934936523,
            0.13590310513973236,
            -10.525493621826172
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7361417351949953,
            0.0,
            0.6768274120513305
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb_98_painting_430402",
        "episode_history": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object hanging on the wall between the mirror and the desk in the room?",
        "answer": "A painting.",
        "object_id": 98,
        "class": "painting",
        "position": [
            2.0231246948242188,
            0.13590310513973236,
            -8.952184677124023
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9978501177800932,
            0.0,
            0.06553733627677438
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb_31_sofa_116338",
        "episode_history": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the patterned sofa with the pink cushion?",
        "answer": "The patterned sofa with the pink cushion is in the hallway, against the wall with the wall-mounted lights, near the entrance to another room.",
        "object_id": 31,
        "class": "sofa",
        "position": [
            13.000761985778809,
            0.13590310513973236,
            -10.879509925842285
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9212143635128106,
            0.0,
            0.3890553899609763
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb_158_toilet_132762",
        "episode_history": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the tiles on the floor around the toilet that is next to the radiator and sink?",
        "answer": "Red.",
        "object_id": 158,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            5.215944290161133,
            0.13590310513973236,
            -1.3309202194213867
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3921414826685393,
            0.0,
            0.9199049176792783
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb_163_sink_207735",
        "episode_history": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash my hands?",
        "answer": "The sink in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 163,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            5.756577014923096,
            0.13590310513973236,
            -3.2333929538726807
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9711171385898771,
            0.0,
            0.23860323371029435
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb_113_desk_861222",
        "episode_history": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the desk that is positioned below the wall-mounted painting of mountains and a lake?",
        "answer": "Light brown.",
        "object_id": 113,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            1.6692726612091064,
            0.13590310513973236,
            -9.274774551391602
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9890338536915739,
            0.0,
            0.14768898487021867
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb_228_desk_589166",
        "episode_history": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the desk that is positioned below the painting of a deer and next to the window with curtains?",
        "answer": "Light brown.",
        "object_id": 228,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            2.1104118824005127,
            0.13590310513973236,
            -4.777472496032715
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8886852518080365,
            0.0,
            0.4585177458058597
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb_114_desk_chair_311100",
        "episode_history": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the desk chair in front of the wooden desk in the room pushed in?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 114,
        "class": "desk chair",
        "position": [
            2.0443031787872314,
            0.13590310513973236,
            -7.961985111236572
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9422663391462743,
            0.0,
            0.3348643697258311
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb_229_desk_chair_15056",
        "episode_history": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly behind the desk chair in the living room?",
        "answer": "A painting of a deer on the wall.",
        "object_id": 229,
        "class": "desk chair",
        "position": [
            2.117013692855835,
            0.13590310513973236,
            -3.8301095962524414
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.84362698121054,
            0.0,
            0.5369297128801788
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb_115_tv_496731",
        "episode_history": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the TV that is placed on the wooden desk near the window with sheer curtains?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 115,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            2.5951502323150635,
            0.13590310513973236,
            -8.215919494628906
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9612863491235885,
            0.0,
            0.2755513654269232
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb_200_tv_702848",
        "episode_history": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the small TV on the stand?",
        "answer": "The small TV is on a stand next to the floor lamp and near the desk with a chair in the room with red carpet and large curtains.",
        "object_id": 200,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            0.1343401074409485,
            0.13590310513973236,
            0.002679097931832075
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.17313925158684706,
            0.0,
            0.9848973548344754
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb_118_coffee_machine_542057",
        "episode_history": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the coffee machine on the wooden desk?",
        "answer": "A set of cups and saucers.",
        "object_id": 118,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            1.0406402349472046,
            0.13590310513973236,
            -7.3696465492248535
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.929298624380166,
            0.0,
            0.3693292118491736
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb_127_couch_401924",
        "episode_history": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the brown couch with a pillow?",
        "answer": "The brown couch with a pillow is in the living room, positioned against the wall with large windows and next to a small round table.",
        "object_id": 127,
        "class": "couch",
        "position": [
            2.201425552368164,
            0.13590310513973236,
            -10.835124969482422
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9245867470553788,
            0.0,
            0.3809715831522778
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb_217_pouffe_822968",
        "episode_history": "00612-GsQBY83r3hb",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the pouffe located?",
        "answer": "The pouffe is in the hallway, right in front of the large mirror and next to the wall-mounted light.",
        "object_id": 217,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            1.4226731061935425,
            0.13590310513973236,
            -4.459421157836914
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5242481036914645,
            0.0,
            0.8515655733858102
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00619-R9fYpvCUkV7_181_table_748342",
        "episode_history": "00619-R9fYpvCUkV7",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on the lower shelf of the table next to the patterned sofa?",
        "answer": "A stack of magazines.",
        "object_id": 181,
        "class": "table",
        "position": [
            -5.943158149719238,
            2.8190526962280273,
            4.634500503540039
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8095017001455915,
            0.0,
            0.587117532919429
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00619-R9fYpvCUkV7_182_sofa_454482",
        "episode_history": "00619-R9fYpvCUkV7",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the sofa that is near the door with the forest-themed wallpaper?",
        "answer": "The pattern consists of circular shapes in various colors, including white, yellow, and blue.",
        "object_id": 182,
        "class": "sofa",
        "position": [
            -3.8514482975006104,
            2.8190526962280273,
            3.036236524581909
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9983934950622022,
            0.0,
            0.05666064787377305
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00619-R9fYpvCUkV7_186_storage_cabinet_802499",
        "episode_history": "00619-R9fYpvCUkV7",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on top of the yellow storage cabinet in the hallway?",
        "answer": "A decorative item and a small blue figurine.",
        "object_id": 186,
        "class": "storage cabinet",
        "position": [
            -4.78876256942749,
            2.8190526962280273,
            4.674107551574707
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6504835388530248,
            0.0,
            0.759520352381189
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00619-R9fYpvCUkV7_214_exercise_mat_623189",
        "episode_history": "00619-R9fYpvCUkV7",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to do my yoga exercises?",
        "answer": "The exercise mat on the floor.",
        "object_id": 214,
        "class": "exercise mat",
        "position": [
            1.5713894367218018,
            2.8190526962280273,
            3.862220287322998
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9752154946568842,
            0.0,
            0.22125717837197925
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00619-R9fYpvCUkV7_248_exercise_mat_50238",
        "episode_history": "00619-R9fYpvCUkV7",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the exercise mat that is placed on the floor near the wall with the colorful yoga mural?",
        "answer": "Purple.",
        "object_id": 248,
        "class": "exercise mat",
        "position": [
            -2.5898001194000244,
            2.8190526962280273,
            4.927055358886719
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9560108396729452,
            0.0,
            0.2933313389800517
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00619-R9fYpvCUkV7_215_exercise_mat_roll_451167",
        "episode_history": "00619-R9fYpvCUkV7",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to do my yoga exercises?",
        "answer": "The exercise mat roll in the corner.",
        "object_id": 215,
        "class": "exercise mat roll",
        "position": [
            0.14544828236103058,
            2.9123494625091553,
            6.1329450607299805
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7904725072674726,
            0.0,
            0.6124975226515414
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00619-R9fYpvCUkV7_350_picture_624815",
        "episode_history": "00619-R9fYpvCUkV7",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object hanging on the left wall of the hallway?",
        "answer": "A picture.",
        "object_id": 350,
        "class": "picture",
        "position": [
            -3.69059419631958,
            2.8190526962280273,
            4.315832138061523
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.1247549239516092,
            0.0,
            0.9921875875810119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00619-R9fYpvCUkV7_362_pouffe_599507",
        "episode_history": "00619-R9fYpvCUkV7",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the pouffe that is placed next to the red lockers and near the door?",
        "answer": "Grey.",
        "object_id": 362,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            -6.83400297164917,
            2.8190526962280273,
            3.5877525806427
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.47735833708138276,
            0.0,
            0.8787087219431118
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00624-ooq3SnvC79d_333_office_chair_420488",
        "episode_history": "00624-ooq3SnvC79d",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object in front of the desk with the red tablecloth in the office room?",
        "answer": "An office chair.",
        "object_id": 333,
        "class": "office chair",
        "position": [
            3.1812446117401123,
            0.11453929543495178,
            5.718318462371826
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9899686785540506,
            0.0,
            0.14128699686081314
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00624-ooq3SnvC79d_376_dish_676094",
        "episode_history": "00624-ooq3SnvC79d",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to serve food during dinner?",
        "answer": "The dish on the middle shelf.",
        "object_id": 376,
        "class": "dish",
        "position": [
            2.568910837173462,
            0.11453929543495178,
            10.642253875732422
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.400232586819674,
            0.0,
            0.9164135946436152
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00624-ooq3SnvC79d_388_bag_with_something_360456",
        "episode_history": "00624-ooq3SnvC79d",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color pattern of the bag that is on the floor near the white cabinet with silver handles?",
        "answer": "The bag has a colorful pattern with multiple colors including blue, yellow, and purple.",
        "object_id": 388,
        "class": "bag with something",
        "position": [
            1.8870115280151367,
            0.11453929543495178,
            11.076169967651367
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.284910371526359,
            0.0,
            0.958554161326689
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00624-ooq3SnvC79d_407_toaster_677255",
        "episode_history": "00624-ooq3SnvC79d",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly to the left of the red toaster on the kitchen counter?",
        "answer": "A sink with some dishes and a cutting board.",
        "object_id": 407,
        "class": "toaster",
        "position": [
            2.8908894062042236,
            0.11453929543495178,
            11.211048126220703
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9029052419263734,
            0.0,
            0.42983964929014784
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00624-ooq3SnvC79d_488_basket_128874",
        "episode_history": "00624-ooq3SnvC79d",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located directly behind the basket on the kitchen island?",
        "answer": "A vase with sunflowers.",
        "object_id": 488,
        "class": "basket",
        "position": [
            4.911175727844238,
            0.11453929543495178,
            9.011642456054688
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8878112062600346,
            0.0,
            0.4602078465640306
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00624-ooq3SnvC79d_508_decorative_plate_703565",
        "episode_history": "00624-ooq3SnvC79d",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the decorative plate that is placed on the kitchen counter near the teapot?",
        "answer": "The pattern on the decorative plate is a combination of brown and white designs.",
        "object_id": 508,
        "class": "decorative plate",
        "position": [
            8.179486274719238,
            0.11453929543495178,
            11.241036415100098
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9495843155041236,
            0.0,
            0.31351176652330803
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00624-ooq3SnvC79d_511_stove_891398",
        "episode_history": "00624-ooq3SnvC79d",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the stove that is located below the wooden cabinets and near the window with decorative plates?",
        "answer": "Silver.",
        "object_id": 511,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            7.523233413696289,
            0.11453929543495178,
            10.896794319152832
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9539828954030896,
            0.0,
            0.2998610266078901
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00624-ooq3SnvC79d_518_plate_427534",
        "episode_history": "00624-ooq3SnvC79d",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is next to the plate on the dining table?",
        "answer": "A lamp and a bag.",
        "object_id": 518,
        "class": "plate",
        "position": [
            5.825991630554199,
            0.11453929543495178,
            8.963905334472656
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.21491963647690415,
            0.0,
            0.976631737072186
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00624-ooq3SnvC79d_520_backpack_154272",
        "episode_history": "00624-ooq3SnvC79d",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is the object to the right of the backpack on the dining table?",
        "answer": "A candle holder with a candle.",
        "object_id": 520,
        "class": "backpack",
        "position": [
            5.1975507736206055,
            0.11453929543495178,
            6.230642318725586
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9426813976385866,
            0.0,
            0.33369414520809476
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00638-iePHCSf119p_71_poster_541513",
        "episode_history": "00638-iePHCSf119p",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the poster with the text \"MEXI-CALI\"?",
        "answer": "A brown cushioned bench.",
        "object_id": 71,
        "class": "poster",
        "position": [
            8.044000625610352,
            0.15613390505313873,
            -0.2207047939300537
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.964819468112527,
            0.0,
            0.2629132821883675
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00638-iePHCSf119p_127_cash_register_723913",
        "episode_history": "00638-iePHCSf119p",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the cash register on the counter in the restaurant turned on?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 127,
        "class": "cash register",
        "position": [
            6.684637069702148,
            0.15613390505313873,
            0.6839790344238281
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.1960144829626111,
            0.0,
            0.9806010006464915
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00638-iePHCSf119p_488_trashcan_536600",
        "episode_history": "00638-iePHCSf119p",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located on the floor beneath the shelves in the kitchen area?",
        "answer": "A trashcan.",
        "object_id": 488,
        "class": "trashcan",
        "position": [
            4.807772159576416,
            0.21990302205085754,
            -3.1576719284057617
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9988362791563205,
            0.0,
            0.04822952872625199
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00662-aRKASs4e8j1_188_recycle_bin_648921",
        "episode_history": "00662-aRKASs4e8j1",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the glass-only recycle bin next to the black table in the corner of the room empty?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 188,
        "class": "recycle bin",
        "position": [
            1.0527093410491943,
            0.19740638136863708,
            10.066948890686035
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8183020005106693,
            0.0,
            0.5747885141164849
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00662-aRKASs4e8j1_236_coat_765481",
        "episode_history": "00662-aRKASs4e8j1",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where are the lab coats hanging?",
        "answer": "The lab coats are hanging on the wall hooks next to the sink and above the stool in the room.",
        "object_id": 236,
        "class": "coat",
        "position": [
            0.20338627696037292,
            0.19740638136863708,
            2.8364315032958984
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3060864904029843,
            0.0,
            0.9520037081822653
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00662-aRKASs4e8j1_240_stool_115732",
        "episode_history": "00662-aRKASs4e8j1",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the wooden object placed in the corner next to the door and under the hanging white coats?",
        "answer": "A stool.",
        "object_id": 240,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            0.19822058081626892,
            0.19740638136863708,
            1.455388069152832
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.36627586436712084,
            0.0,
            0.9305063090501421
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00662-aRKASs4e8j1_496_refrigerator_726844",
        "episode_history": "00662-aRKASs4e8j1",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the white appliance located on the counter near the center pillar in the laboratory?",
        "answer": "A refrigerator.",
        "object_id": 496,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            5.100951194763184,
            0.05275547876954079,
            -1.7645924091339111
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.40751799957269796,
            0.0,
            0.9131971747789557
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00664-u5atqC7vRCY_121_box_752577",
        "episode_history": "00664-u5atqC7vRCY",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on top of the toilet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A box.",
        "object_id": 121,
        "class": "box",
        "position": [
            2.966057538986206,
            -0.07384070754051208,
            3.640627384185791
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9888213131339855,
            0.0,
            0.14910536775039288
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00664-u5atqC7vRCY_170_oven_413453",
        "episode_history": "00664-u5atqC7vRCY",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located below the stovetop in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "An oven.",
        "object_id": 170,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            2.0872440338134766,
            -0.07384070754051208,
            -0.4847221374511719
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6363602095269144,
            0.0,
            0.771392042823143
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00664-u5atqC7vRCY_171_stove_589191",
        "episode_history": "00664-u5atqC7vRCY",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located below the range hood and between the wooden cabinets in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A stove.",
        "object_id": 171,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            3.10929536819458,
            -0.07384070754051208,
            0.07981833815574646
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4827758185382141,
            0.0,
            0.8757439745923219
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00664-u5atqC7vRCY_188_microwave_458630",
        "episode_history": "00664-u5atqC7vRCY",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the white electronic device located on the kitchen counter between the cabinets and the wall?",
        "answer": "A microwave.",
        "object_id": 188,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            3.17728328704834,
            -0.07384070754051208,
            -0.15846215188503265
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.590472248198838,
            0.0,
            0.8070579434631753
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00664-u5atqC7vRCY_192_trashcan_19649",
        "episode_history": "00664-u5atqC7vRCY",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the red-lidded object located between the wooden cabinet and the doorway in the kitchen area?",
        "answer": "A trashcan.",
        "object_id": 192,
        "class": "trashcan",
        "position": [
            2.8157167434692383,
            -0.07384070754051208,
            -0.9126787185668945
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9995099116313544,
            0.0,
            0.03130393826190948
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00664-u5atqC7vRCY_194_ventilation_hood_305744",
        "episode_history": "00664-u5atqC7vRCY",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the ventilation hood above the stove in the kitchen clean?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 194,
        "class": "ventilation hood",
        "position": [
            3.8368663787841797,
            -0.07384070754051208,
            0.2531840205192566
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.30433383002529296,
            0.0,
            0.9525654412701188
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00664-u5atqC7vRCY_257_sofa_20346",
        "episode_history": "00664-u5atqC7vRCY",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the small sofa in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "The small sofa is located in the bedroom, near the window and next to the bed.",
        "object_id": 257,
        "class": "sofa",
        "position": [
            5.54570198059082,
            -0.26712679862976074,
            0.5253156423568726
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.06813704930872491,
            0.0,
            0.9976759706996557
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00664-u5atqC7vRCY_372_cuddly_toy_410419",
        "episode_history": "00664-u5atqC7vRCY",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What animal is the cuddly toy that is lying on the floor near the white shelf and the window designed to resemble?",
        "answer": "A dolphin.",
        "object_id": 372,
        "class": "cuddly toy",
        "position": [
            5.01622200012207,
            2.7261593341827393,
            5.137725830078125
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7590954477464686,
            0.0,
            0.6509793400796897
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00664-u5atqC7vRCY_533_rug_225049",
        "episode_history": "00664-u5atqC7vRCY",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the rug at the bottom of the stairs in the hallway neatly placed?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 533,
        "class": "rug",
        "position": [
            -6.994629383087158,
            -0.2049909085035324,
            5.350326061248779
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9663890654375729,
            0.0,
            0.25708398278129807
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00668-6YtDG3FhNvx_48_painting_199666",
        "episode_history": "00668-6YtDG3FhNvx",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the dominant color of the painting that is hung on the wall above the bed with a black headboard?",
        "answer": "Green.",
        "object_id": 48,
        "class": "painting",
        "position": [
            2.4637603759765625,
            0.14003509283065796,
            2.516321897506714
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.08975195076164527,
            0.0,
            0.9959641496231073
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00668-6YtDG3FhNvx_79_toaster_377669",
        "episode_history": "00668-6YtDG3FhNvx",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the toaster on the kitchen counter next to the window plugged in?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 79,
        "class": "toaster",
        "position": [
            -2.0211668014526367,
            0.14003509283065796,
            2.192631244659424
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4371733640812909,
            0.0,
            0.8993772566269658
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00668-6YtDG3FhNvx_111_washing_machine_848489",
        "episode_history": "00668-6YtDG3FhNvx",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the washing machine under the counter in the kitchen closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 111,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -1.3837884664535522,
            0.14003509283065796,
            3.2401981353759766
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9278042067861653,
            0.0,
            0.3730674923789189
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00668-6YtDG3FhNvx_114_washing_machine_880576",
        "episode_history": "00668-6YtDG3FhNvx",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the washing machine located in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The washing machine is located under the countertop, between the sink and the refrigerator, in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 114,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -0.7133966684341431,
            0.14003509283065796,
            1.8354909420013428
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.881844110896607,
            0.0,
            0.471541052377174
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00668-6YtDG3FhNvx_117_trashcan_21499",
        "episode_history": "00668-6YtDG3FhNvx",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I dispose of the kitchen waste?",
        "answer": "The trashcan under the counter.",
        "object_id": 117,
        "class": "trashcan",
        "position": [
            -1.4133299589157104,
            0.14003509283065796,
            2.470836877822876
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6126086720552195,
            0.0,
            0.7903863706585157
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00668-6YtDG3FhNvx_347_shower_cabin_684209",
        "episode_history": "00668-6YtDG3FhNvx",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the shower cabin that is visible through the doorway with a yellow floor?",
        "answer": "Orange.",
        "object_id": 347,
        "class": "shower cabin",
        "position": [
            -0.124589703977108,
            2.740035057067871,
            6.312044143676758
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9992449993569118,
            0.0,
            0.03885139972053985
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00668-6YtDG3FhNvx_186_vase_450206",
        "episode_history": "00668-6YtDG3FhNvx",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is next to the vase on the wooden side table near the sofa?",
        "answer": "A remote control and some keys.",
        "object_id": 186,
        "class": "vase",
        "position": [
            -2.337869882583618,
            0.14003509283065796,
            7.710554122924805
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.963842201460098,
            0.0,
            0.266473658519096
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00668-6YtDG3FhNvx_193_tv_410048",
        "episode_history": "00668-6YtDG3FhNvx",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object mounted on the wall with colorful artwork behind it in the room near the open door?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 193,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -3.106994152069092,
            0.14003509283065796,
            8.27901840209961
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.15281001776319894,
            0.0,
            0.9882555835770476
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ_165_table_1691",
        "episode_history": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there a plant placed on the dining table near the window in the dining area?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 165,
        "class": "table",
        "position": [
            0.38534390926361084,
            0.18881310522556305,
            13.527801513671875
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7847984530174564,
            0.0,
            0.6197510694959769
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ_142_fridge_698227",
        "episode_history": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to store my groceries and keep them fresh?",
        "answer": "The fridge next to the pantry door.",
        "object_id": 142,
        "class": "fridge",
        "position": [
            0.9770225882530212,
            0.18881310522556305,
            11.135921478271484
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.21159616719056046,
            0.0,
            0.9773571824211783
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ_152_microwave_633862",
        "episode_history": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to quickly heat up my leftovers?",
        "answer": "The microwave above the stove.",
        "object_id": 152,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            2.745041608810425,
            0.18881310522556305,
            8.89673900604248
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8873865174315234,
            0.0,
            0.4610262125744616
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ_171_oven_382396",
        "episode_history": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the oven in the kitchen with white cabinets open?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 171,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            1.4704952239990234,
            0.18881310522556305,
            9.051122665405273
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8225869565050045,
            0.0,
            0.56863933999314
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ_174_toaster_691843",
        "episode_history": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the silver toaster in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The silver toaster is on the granite countertop, between the white cabinets and the window with white shutters.",
        "object_id": 174,
        "class": "toaster",
        "position": [
            2.9310238361358643,
            0.18881310522556305,
            11.511669158935547
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8396157964587793,
            0.0,
            0.543180738186554
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ_227_cork_board_758815",
        "episode_history": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the cork board with the photo pinned on it?",
        "answer": "The cork board with the photo pinned on it is in the kitchen, mounted on the wall next to the window and above the countertop with the laptop and plants.",
        "object_id": 227,
        "class": "cork board",
        "position": [
            3.3278260231018066,
            0.18881310522556305,
            6.853862285614014
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3449357210291517,
            0.0,
            0.9386263092190092
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ_304_pouffe_782228",
        "episode_history": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the pouffe in the living room?",
        "answer": "The pouffe is in front of the brick fireplace, between the two leather sofas and next to a small side table with a lamp.",
        "object_id": 304,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            0.9550674557685852,
            0.18881310522556305,
            11.068201065063477
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8589053086291479,
            0.0,
            0.5121344265021326
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ_455_bathroom_cabinet_700770",
        "episode_history": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bathroom cabinet with the mirror?",
        "answer": "The bathroom cabinet with the mirror is located in the bathroom, next to the sink and under the light fixtures, near the door leading to the bedroom.",
        "object_id": 455,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            -4.271221160888672,
            0.18881310522556305,
            13.068570137023926
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7962757481200632,
            0.0,
            0.6049338252700321
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ_457_bathroom_cabinet_700643",
        "episode_history": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the white object with drawers and a countertop next to the door in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A bathroom cabinet.",
        "object_id": 457,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            -6.5009918212890625,
            0.18881310522556305,
            12.996613502502441
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.805006012091529,
            0.0,
            0.5932666521021497
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ_534_bedside_table_136706",
        "episode_history": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the small piece of furniture next to the lower bunk bed in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A bedside table.",
        "object_id": 534,
        "class": "bedside table",
        "position": [
            2.5857138633728027,
            3.588813066482544,
            4.70672082901001
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5245886975520553,
            0.0,
            0.8513558001215698
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ_606_shelf___cabinet_715779",
        "episode_history": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the shelf/cabinet in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "A desk with a chair.",
        "object_id": 606,
        "class": "shelf / cabinet",
        "position": [
            0.2026100903749466,
            3.7888131141662598,
            10.02418327331543
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9181195448717655,
            0.0,
            0.3963035469491309
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ_647_tv_stand_92531",
        "episode_history": "00685-ENiCjXWB6aQ",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the TV stand that is positioned next to the white double doors in the living room?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 647,
        "class": "tv stand",
        "position": [
            -1.300220012664795,
            3.7888131141662598,
            10.640941619873047
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9770602283270395,
            0.0,
            0.21296316634928772
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ_199_cabinet_671615",
        "episode_history": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on top of the wooden cabinet next to the window?",
        "answer": "A printer.",
        "object_id": 199,
        "class": "cabinet",
        "position": [
            10.606740951538086,
            -2.556666374206543,
            2.846919298171997
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8421145576669742,
            0.0,
            0.5392986851136914
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ_11_sofa_chair_950759",
        "episode_history": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the patterned object to the right of the sofa in the living room?",
        "answer": "A sofa chair.",
        "object_id": 11,
        "class": "sofa chair",
        "position": [
            5.21536922454834,
            -2.556666374206543,
            0.46787792444229126
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2780284430259818,
            0.0,
            0.9605728420419497
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ_351_armchair_25772",
        "episode_history": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the armchair that is placed near the two windows with white curtains in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "Beige.",
        "object_id": 351,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            2.9571003913879395,
            0.04333353042602539,
            -0.7057410478591919
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8053976025942992,
            0.0,
            0.5927349337902696
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ_35_tray_595936",
        "episode_history": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on the tray placed on the ottoman in front of the sofa?",
        "answer": "A decorative bowl and a folded cloth.",
        "object_id": 35,
        "class": "tray",
        "position": [
            2.946371078491211,
            -2.556666374206543,
            -0.171749085187912
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4432333797349646,
            0.0,
            0.8964062533743954
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ_36_coffee_table_795595",
        "episode_history": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on the coffee table in the living room?",
        "answer": "A decorative item, possibly a sculpture or ornament.",
        "object_id": 36,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            4.772098064422607,
            -2.556666374206543,
            -1.2249488830566406
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7381001709676508,
            0.0,
            0.6746911423885189
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ_40_cabinet_table_460800",
        "episode_history": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lamp on the cabinet table next to the sofa in the living room turned on?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 40,
        "class": "cabinet table",
        "position": [
            0.30554819107055664,
            -2.556666374206543,
            0.025353893637657166
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.05150581493191358,
            0.0,
            0.9986726946443462
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ_311_cabinet_table_392147",
        "episode_history": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the picture frame on the cabinet table in the bedroom standing upright?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 311,
        "class": "cabinet table",
        "position": [
            2.2481689453125,
            0.04333353042602539,
            2.9617159366607666
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2797636235095552,
            0.0,
            0.9600689115687497
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ_417_basket_of_something_422592",
        "episode_history": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the basket of blankets?",
        "answer": "The basket of blankets is under the wooden side table next to the bed in the bedroom.",
        "object_id": 417,
        "class": "basket of something",
        "position": [
            10.872535705566406,
            0.04333353042602539,
            1.4765760898590088
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6258884819236511,
            0.0,
            0.7799125644553417
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ_153_microwave_192309",
        "episode_history": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the microwave that is installed above the stove and next to the refrigerator?",
        "answer": "Stainless steel.",
        "object_id": 153,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            11.88430404663086,
            -2.556666374206543,
            -0.4119209051132202
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.10465384668007886,
            0.0,
            0.9945087090493792
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ_155_cloth_24780",
        "episode_history": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object hanging on the oven door in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A cloth.",
        "object_id": 155,
        "class": "cloth",
        "position": [
            11.751220703125,
            -2.556666374206543,
            -0.9071266651153564
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.20013536054589712,
            0.0,
            0.9797682570175275
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ_169_kitchen_top_74947",
        "episode_history": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the backsplash above the kitchen top that is between the refrigerator and the stove?",
        "answer": "The pattern on the backsplash is a repeating geometric design.",
        "object_id": 169,
        "class": "kitchen top",
        "position": [
            11.582730293273926,
            -2.556666374206543,
            -1.4430365562438965
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.32289138847126975,
            0.0,
            0.9464360259685255
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ_175_refrigerator_252137",
        "episode_history": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the left door of the stainless steel refrigerator in the kitchen slightly open?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 175,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            10.547490119934082,
            -2.556666374206543,
            0.42203250527381897
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.10477121913414711,
            0.0,
            0.9944963507430002
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ_198_printer_828437",
        "episode_history": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there any paper in the output tray of the printer on the small table next to the window in the study room?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 198,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            10.774907112121582,
            -2.556666374206543,
            2.3871915340423584
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8988703129965648,
            0.0,
            0.43821474235066254
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ_203_office_table_438538",
        "episode_history": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there a computer on the office table in the room with the carpeted floor?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 203,
        "class": "office table",
        "position": [
            10.607239723205566,
            -2.556666374206543,
            0.5168297290802002
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.961063569515222,
            0.0,
            0.276327369890607
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ_497_bathroom_cabinet_912714",
        "episode_history": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the drawer of the bathroom cabinet in the bathroom open?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 497,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            10.048101425170898,
            0.04333353042602539,
            -0.7863701581954956
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.41183132849338855,
            0.0,
            0.9112600928776431
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ_269_shower_curtain_899617",
        "episode_history": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the shower curtain in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The shower curtain is in the bathroom, hanging next to the toilet and near the vanity with the large mirror.",
        "object_id": 269,
        "class": "shower curtain",
        "position": [
            3.6468122005462646,
            0.04333353042602539,
            1.751113772392273
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8986721099325714,
            0.0,
            0.4386210651910602
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ_272_bathtub_411758",
        "episode_history": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the shower curtain in the bathroom pulled across the bathtub?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 272,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            3.968611001968384,
            0.04333353042602539,
            2.494899272918701
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7795975940384051,
            0.0,
            0.6262807608170078
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ_335_shower_floor_210278",
        "episode_history": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the shower floor in the bathroom clean?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 335,
        "class": "shower floor",
        "position": [
            4.880385875701904,
            0.04333353042602539,
            0.7131524085998535
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2366588439428843,
            0.0,
            0.9715928116158629
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ_356_dresser_707581",
        "episode_history": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lamp on the dresser in the bedroom turned on?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 356,
        "class": "dresser",
        "position": [
            5.681585311889648,
            0.04333353042602539,
            -2.1737992763519287
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6457160088997398,
            0.0,
            0.7635776554159971
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ_398_dresser_48498",
        "episode_history": "00688-SgkmkWjjmDJ",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object with multiple drawers located against the wall near the hallway entrance in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A dresser.",
        "object_id": 398,
        "class": "dresser",
        "position": [
            11.126089096069336,
            0.04333353042602539,
            1.6284356117248535
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.37910560383721276,
            0.0,
            0.9253534141825069
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00696-DsEJeNPcZtE_13_bucket_857320",
        "episode_history": "00696-DsEJeNPcZtE",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What material is the bucket that is placed next to the dark wooden chair made of?",
        "answer": "Metal.",
        "object_id": 13,
        "class": "bucket",
        "position": [
            -8.665117263793945,
            0.061951253563165665,
            0.9583427309989929
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2120888792131761,
            0.0,
            0.9772503810764663
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00696-DsEJeNPcZtE_18_bag_888879",
        "episode_history": "00696-DsEJeNPcZtE",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the blue bag hanging on the wall in the hallway open?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 18,
        "class": "bag",
        "position": [
            -8.681386947631836,
            0.004059880971908569,
            -0.4766469895839691
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.286508406637011,
            0.0,
            0.958077728019142
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00696-DsEJeNPcZtE_99_refrigerator_660974",
        "episode_history": "00696-DsEJeNPcZtE",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to store my groceries and keep them fresh?",
        "answer": "The refrigerator in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 99,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -4.303136825561523,
            0.204059898853302,
            -5.200851917266846
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7772105935232182,
            0.0,
            0.6292405687138163
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00696-DsEJeNPcZtE_325_blanket_43987",
        "episode_history": "00696-DsEJeNPcZtE",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the blanket on the bed in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A wooden chest.",
        "object_id": 325,
        "class": "blanket",
        "position": [
            2.88110089302063,
            0.12204740196466446,
            -4.63376522064209
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.44048535049065607,
            0.0,
            0.8977597986115907
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00696-DsEJeNPcZtE_329_tv_411011",
        "episode_history": "00696-DsEJeNPcZtE",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the TV that is placed on the dark wooden dresser near the hallway entrance?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 329,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            3.1647531986236572,
            0.204059898853302,
            -6.485703945159912
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9634320873628262,
            0.0,
            0.26795263208206777
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00696-DsEJeNPcZtE_402_tv_411373",
        "episode_history": "00696-DsEJeNPcZtE",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wall-mounted TV?",
        "answer": "The wall-mounted TV is in the bedroom, above a white shelf filled with various items, next to an ironing board and a stack of water bottles.",
        "object_id": 402,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            1.96109938621521,
            0.23623278737068176,
            -6.071750164031982
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.811985150878526,
            0.0,
            0.5836780917190377
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00696-DsEJeNPcZtE_396_box_772165",
        "episode_history": "00696-DsEJeNPcZtE",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the cardboard box next to the ironing board in the room sealed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 396,
        "class": "box",
        "position": [
            1.2894867658615112,
            0.018395937979221344,
            -6.2176055908203125
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5609354320073264,
            0.0,
            0.8278595539816848
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00696-DsEJeNPcZtE_399_ironing_board_542580",
        "episode_history": "00696-DsEJeNPcZtE",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to iron my clothes?",
        "answer": "The ironing board in the corner of the room.",
        "object_id": 399,
        "class": "ironing board",
        "position": [
            2.199634552001953,
            0.3339000940322876,
            -6.16864538192749
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6584883335016379,
            0.0,
            0.7525909344672148
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00696-DsEJeNPcZtE_443_clock_730007",
        "episode_history": "00696-DsEJeNPcZtE",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What type of numerals are used on the clock that is above the white brick fireplace?",
        "answer": "Roman numerals.",
        "object_id": 443,
        "class": "clock",
        "position": [
            -1.3555434942245483,
            0.204059898853302,
            -10.930133819580078
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.44846923314721976,
            0.0,
            0.8937982697009123
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00712-HZ2iMMBsBQ9_21_armchair_663630",
        "episode_history": "00712-HZ2iMMBsBQ9",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the cushion on the armchair that is placed near the large potted plant and the wooden side table?",
        "answer": "The cushion is brown.",
        "object_id": 21,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            8.716066360473633,
            0.1964448243379593,
            -0.8170355558395386
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7821536033853174,
            0.0,
            0.6230856608134742
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00712-HZ2iMMBsBQ9_25_stool_883746",
        "episode_history": "00712-HZ2iMMBsBQ9",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there a black object placed on the wooden stool next to the chair with a cushion and throw blanket in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 25,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            9.247942924499512,
            0.1964448243379593,
            -0.667138934135437
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8581507693591336,
            0.0,
            0.5133977571516329
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00712-HZ2iMMBsBQ9_39_bedside_lamp_535050",
        "episode_history": "00712-HZ2iMMBsBQ9",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bedside lamp with the golden base?",
        "answer": "The bedside lamp with the golden base is on the nightstand next to the bed in the bedroom, under the two framed pictures on the wall.",
        "object_id": 39,
        "class": "bedside lamp",
        "position": [
            11.493345260620117,
            0.1964448243379593,
            -1.2789326906204224
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.09608280475106358,
            0.0,
            0.9953733443443064
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00712-HZ2iMMBsBQ9_42_bedside_lamp_542840",
        "episode_history": "00712-HZ2iMMBsBQ9",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the base of the bedside lamp that is placed on the wooden nightstand next to the bed with two abstract paintings above it?",
        "answer": "The base of the bedside lamp is round.",
        "object_id": 42,
        "class": "bedside lamp",
        "position": [
            8.839941024780273,
            0.1964448243379593,
            -1.15829336643219
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.01956174128624692,
            0.0,
            0.9998086508316728
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00712-HZ2iMMBsBQ9_54_toilet_310811",
        "episode_history": "00712-HZ2iMMBsBQ9",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the white object located between the shower and the sink in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A toilet.",
        "object_id": 54,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            8.440057754516602,
            0.1964448243379593,
            -1.5707367658615112
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.439973781341611,
            0.0,
            0.8980106189416495
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00712-HZ2iMMBsBQ9_135_led_tv_798368",
        "episode_history": "00712-HZ2iMMBsBQ9",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the LED TV that is mounted on the wall above the wooden cabinet with a vase on it?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 135,
        "class": "led tv",
        "position": [
            2.1830637454986572,
            0.1964448243379593,
            -4.178383827209473
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4023646407521154,
            0.0,
            0.915479489596802
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00712-HZ2iMMBsBQ9_419_led_tv_921458",
        "episode_history": "00712-HZ2iMMBsBQ9",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the LED TV mounted on the wall in the living room turned on?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 419,
        "class": "led tv",
        "position": [
            -3.889187812805176,
            0.1964448243379593,
            -0.798691987991333
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.17269545409724196,
            0.0,
            0.9849752687931547
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00712-HZ2iMMBsBQ9_388_table_665895",
        "episode_history": "00712-HZ2iMMBsBQ9",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the round object in front of the sofa in the living room that has items placed on it?",
        "answer": "A table.",
        "object_id": 388,
        "class": "table",
        "position": [
            -4.525003433227539,
            0.1964448243379593,
            -1.8195828199386597
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8982503530016077,
            0.0,
            0.43948413319764695
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00712-HZ2iMMBsBQ9_478_table_37734",
        "episode_history": "00712-HZ2iMMBsBQ9",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What material is the table that is positioned near the large sliding glass door made of?",
        "answer": "Glass.",
        "object_id": 478,
        "class": "table",
        "position": [
            3.423325300216675,
            0.1964448243379593,
            -0.9313969612121582
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8903547261356799,
            0.0,
            0.45526746166166826
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy_59_bath_677992",
        "episode_history": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the bathtub in the bathroom empty?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 59,
        "class": "bath",
        "position": [
            -1.1695977449417114,
            2.8473377227783203,
            0.11764135956764221
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9242934080412616,
            0.0,
            0.38168271620741445
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy_69_toilet_389797",
        "episode_history": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the toilet in the house?",
        "answer": "The toilet is in the bathroom, directly in front of the sink and mirror, next to a small plant and a framed picture on the wall.",
        "object_id": 69,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -1.9720680713653564,
            2.7521231174468994,
            -0.5722556114196777
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.999986314739454,
            0.0,
            0.005231666487426899
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy_321_sofa_135411",
        "episode_history": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the brown leather sofa in the basement positioned against the wall?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 321,
        "class": "sofa",
        "position": [
            -2.063485860824585,
            -2.5526623725891113,
            1.4741771221160889
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7242525507609611,
            0.0,
            0.6895348016715628
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy_224_coffee_machine_49648",
        "episode_history": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the kitchen counter next to the refrigerator?",
        "answer": "A coffee machine.",
        "object_id": 224,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            -4.695199966430664,
            0.04733753204345703,
            -1.9831397533416748
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.41635173048081003,
            0.0,
            0.9092036276465437
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy_235_microwave_972802",
        "episode_history": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the microwave in the house?",
        "answer": "The microwave is in the kitchen, mounted above the countertop and stove, next to the living room area.",
        "object_id": 235,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -6.004702091217041,
            0.04733753204345703,
            -2.272610902786255
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9480878416511156,
            0.0,
            0.31800856044032716
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy_281_towel_126842",
        "episode_history": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the towel that is hanging on the rack below the framed picture in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 281,
        "class": "towel",
        "position": [
            -0.3934761881828308,
            0.04733753204345703,
            -0.15570533275604248
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9945410507633445,
            0.0,
            0.10434605093887986
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy_328_tv_stand_352497",
        "episode_history": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the TV stand with the television on it?",
        "answer": "The TV stand is in the basement, positioned against the wall under the window, between a red chair and a brown leather sofa.",
        "object_id": 328,
        "class": "tv stand",
        "position": [
            -4.239321708679199,
            -2.5526623725891113,
            0.5146369934082031
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7249596948086526,
            0.0,
            0.6887912897989821
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy_329_tv_980419",
        "episode_history": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the TV stand that is directly below the TV in the basement room with exposed ceiling beams?",
        "answer": "The TV stand is made of light-colored wood.",
        "object_id": 329,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -4.501358985900879,
            -2.5526623725891113,
            0.004083290696144104
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7903061588707979,
            0.0,
            0.6127121471383485
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy_330_desk_842464",
        "episode_history": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the desk that has multiple computer monitors on it and is located near the red cushioned chair?",
        "answer": "The desk is brown.",
        "object_id": 330,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            -4.9755401611328125,
            -2.5526623725891113,
            0.014545723795890808
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.41333551776879024,
            0.0,
            0.9105787993088825
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy_343_desk_102344",
        "episode_history": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the desk that is positioned against the wall under the exposed ceiling pipes?",
        "answer": "The desk is light wood-colored with white legs.",
        "object_id": 343,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            -6.380402088165283,
            -2.5526623725891113,
            0.3477485179901123
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.24636585343342773,
            0.0,
            0.9691769014282268
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy_378_washing_machine_968568",
        "episode_history": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the washing machine in the laundry area?",
        "answer": "A wooden shelf with various items stored on it.",
        "object_id": 378,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -1.938188076019287,
            -2.5526623725891113,
            0.7570450901985168
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.43275706889601523,
            0.0,
            0.9015105763775206
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy_379_washing_machine_293869",
        "episode_history": "00738-GPyDUnjwZQy",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the washing machine located?",
        "answer": "The washing machine is in the laundry room, next to the dryer and near the shelves with various items, close to the utility area with pipes and electrical panels.",
        "object_id": 379,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -3.0820329189300537,
            -2.5526623725891113,
            0.4212321639060974
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.21535582153292976,
            0.0,
            0.97653564713833
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00741-w8GiikYuFRk_66_cloth_91646",
        "episode_history": "00741-w8GiikYuFRk",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the brown cloth hanging on the wall in the room clean?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 66,
        "class": "cloth",
        "position": [
            -9.484818458557129,
            0.1185784563422203,
            -5.7439422607421875
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7050761758560866,
            0.0,
            0.7091315718822261
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00741-w8GiikYuFRk_70_bin_646051",
        "episode_history": "00741-w8GiikYuFRk",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is hanging above the bin in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "A red and brown tapestry and a brown garment.",
        "object_id": 70,
        "class": "bin",
        "position": [
            -8.042976379394531,
            0.1185784563422203,
            -7.383179187774658
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9674744333835309,
            0.0,
            0.2529688137878184
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00741-w8GiikYuFRk_190_couch_794605",
        "episode_history": "00741-w8GiikYuFRk",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed between the two chairs under the large painting in the living room?",
        "answer": "A couch.",
        "object_id": 190,
        "class": "couch",
        "position": [
            -5.300850868225098,
            0.1185784563422203,
            -7.367972373962402
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7825155848496838,
            0.0,
            0.6226309978368869
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00741-w8GiikYuFRk_421_wall_board_356833",
        "episode_history": "00741-w8GiikYuFRk",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bulletin board with various notes and papers?",
        "answer": "The bulletin board is mounted on the wall to the right of the double doors, above the wooden counter with magazines and newspapers.",
        "object_id": 421,
        "class": "wall board",
        "position": [
            4.761191368103027,
            0.1185784563422203,
            -1.4925971031188965
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6056908664295702,
            0.0,
            0.7957000529871772
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00741-w8GiikYuFRk_549_bed_small_843235",
        "episode_history": "00741-w8GiikYuFRk",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the small bed near the window?",
        "answer": "A large wooden chest.",
        "object_id": 549,
        "class": "bed small",
        "position": [
            -4.2457075119018555,
            0.1185784563422203,
            -1.7673031091690063
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9302055107792465,
            0.0,
            0.3670391092457598
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_8_fridge_536930",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the large stainless steel object next to the kitchen counter and cabinets?",
        "answer": "A fridge.",
        "object_id": 8,
        "class": "fridge",
        "position": [
            -9.119405746459961,
            0.19159936904907227,
            -4.70419454574585
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7573641653990575,
            0.0,
            0.6529927418964081
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_22_toaster_26321",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the small appliance with two slots located on the kitchen counter between the paper towel holder and the window?",
        "answer": "A toaster.",
        "object_id": 22,
        "class": "toaster",
        "position": [
            -7.066555976867676,
            0.19159936904907227,
            -6.563541412353516
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.42279391406574873,
            0.0,
            0.9062258582875266
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_20_breadbox_201394",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the shiny rectangular object on the kitchen counter between the toaster and the knife block?",
        "answer": "A breadbox.",
        "object_id": 20,
        "class": "breadbox",
        "position": [
            -7.355329513549805,
            0.19159936904907227,
            -6.70987606048584
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7108968166193542,
            0.0,
            0.7032963217026436
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_39_microwave_585553",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The stove.",
        "object_id": 39,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -8.285642623901367,
            0.19159936904907227,
            -6.217738628387451
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7717729301034589,
            0.0,
            0.6358982185535051
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_42_flower_vase_129323",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed in the center of the kitchen island?",
        "answer": "A flower vase.",
        "object_id": 42,
        "class": "flower vase",
        "position": [
            -9.063831329345703,
            0.19159936904907227,
            -6.032228946685791
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.912612374807193,
            0.0,
            0.40882594505336284
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_64_fireplace_917823",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the fireplace that is below the painting of a person and next to a black display cabinet?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 64,
        "class": "fireplace",
        "position": [
            -7.99208927154541,
            0.19159936904907227,
            -3.4142374992370605
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5390672047062464,
            0.0,
            0.8422627552077759
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_98_vase_842829",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the large green vase next to the white armchair and the potted plant in the living room empty?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 98,
        "class": "vase",
        "position": [
            -9.565703392028809,
            0.19159936904907227,
            0.7715005278587341
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7286856660975846,
            0.0,
            0.6848483043885846
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_297_bathtub_480788",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bathtub in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The bathtub is located at the far end of the bathroom, next to the toilet and behind the shower curtain.",
        "object_id": 297,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            -4.2589030265808105,
            0.19159936904907227,
            -2.7662060260772705
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9995438376359513,
            0.0,
            0.030201268912155615
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_169_toilet_342840",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to flush away waste?",
        "answer": "The toilet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 169,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -4.835447788238525,
            0.19159936904907227,
            -6.21170711517334
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.940359738733352,
            0.0,
            0.34018165995441607
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_526_laptop_848839",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the laptop on the wooden desk?",
        "answer": "A television.",
        "object_id": 526,
        "class": "laptop",
        "position": [
            -8.385623931884766,
            -2.608400583267212,
            0.0500316321849823
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9791492140940173,
            0.0,
            0.2031423553547297
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_343_washing_machine_521174",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the washing machine that is located next to the dryer in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 343,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -7.466890811920166,
            -2.608400583267212,
            -2.741236686706543
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3439323154687165,
            0.0,
            0.9389944421434705
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_344_washing_machine_907955",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the washing machine that is located in the laundry area next to the hallway with wooden flooring?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 344,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -7.80192756652832,
            -2.608400583267212,
            -2.639476776123047
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.465171555783937,
            0.0,
            0.8852205508739343
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_346_laundry_basket_412839",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the laundry basket with folded clothes?",
        "answer": "The laundry basket with folded clothes is on top of the washing machine in the laundry room.",
        "object_id": 346,
        "class": "laundry basket",
        "position": [
            -6.575085639953613,
            -2.608400583267212,
            -3.457789897918701
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3414508026152263,
            0.0,
            0.9398996485760689
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_380_stool_427293",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the small wooden object with a cushion on top, located near the bottom of the stairs and next to the gray chair in the living room?",
        "answer": "A stool.",
        "object_id": 380,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            -5.937220573425293,
            -2.608400583267212,
            -2.948282241821289
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9650041111247868,
            0.0,
            0.26223475267831986
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_395_tv_stand_171393",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object directly below the TV in the living room?",
        "answer": "A TV stand.",
        "object_id": 395,
        "class": "tv stand",
        "position": [
            -1.9189491271972656,
            -2.608400583267212,
            -3.228947162628174
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8810348738888514,
            0.0,
            0.47305131961728614
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_396_tv_133477",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the TV in the living room?",
        "answer": "A wooden cabinet with glass doors.",
        "object_id": 396,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -1.7922120094299316,
            -2.608400583267212,
            -3.300288438796997
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8945377067951168,
            0.0,
            0.44699249559890125
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_429_closet_259691",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I store my clothes neatly?",
        "answer": "The closet in the room.",
        "object_id": 429,
        "class": "closet",
        "position": [
            -3.151583194732666,
            -2.608400583267212,
            -3.141493797302246
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5856022474543106,
            0.0,
            0.8105985490836142
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_485_treadmill_264353",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the exercise equipment located next to the wall with the picture frames and near the desk?",
        "answer": "A treadmill.",
        "object_id": 485,
        "class": "treadmill",
        "position": [
            -8.306648254394531,
            -2.608400583267212,
            -2.2767245769500732
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9311700091757638,
            0.0,
            0.3645852630203368
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_531_monitor_781646",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the monitor in the study room?",
        "answer": "The monitor is on the wooden desk in front of the window, next to a laptop and a wooden chair.",
        "object_id": 531,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            -9.304021835327148,
            -2.4883248805999756,
            -1.246694803237915
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9958939444268976,
            0.0,
            0.09052762812443187
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_536_radio_213182",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the radio on the small wooden table between the two red chairs in the living room turned on?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 536,
        "class": "radio",
        "position": [
            -9.414999961853027,
            -2.605196237564087,
            -2.171782970428467
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3469788201709935,
            0.0,
            0.9378729649332821
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_541_basket_196580",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the basket next to the wooden desk in the study room filled with items?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 541,
        "class": "basket",
        "position": [
            -9.964034080505371,
            -2.608400583267212,
            -3.6003384590148926
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.23098714719683697,
            0.0,
            0.9729568016257797
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_553_guitar_878713",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to play some acoustic music?",
        "answer": "The guitar leaning against the wall.",
        "object_id": 553,
        "class": "guitar",
        "position": [
            -8.32835578918457,
            -2.608400583267212,
            -4.407050132751465
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.1345974494639633,
            0.0,
            0.9909003615892952
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_562_guitar_300818",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the red electric guitar leaning against the black trunk in the music room properly placed on a stand?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 562,
        "class": "guitar",
        "position": [
            -9.521020889282227,
            -2.608400583267212,
            -5.4600372314453125
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.27895424081876496,
            0.0,
            0.9603043952462295
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK_571_printer_53653",
        "episode_history": "00744-1S7LAXRdDqK",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the printer located?",
        "answer": "The printer is on a table next to the desk with the computer, under the window with blinds, in the corner of the room.",
        "object_id": 571,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            -8.778340339660645,
            -2.608400583267212,
            -6.413195610046387
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.60591859831064,
            0.0,
            0.7955266508554376
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB_20_dresser_791842",
        "episode_history": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on top of the dresser near the window?",
        "answer": "A mirror and some small items.",
        "object_id": 20,
        "class": "dresser",
        "position": [
            12.93701171875,
            0.06217825412750244,
            8.818403244018555
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5808584113707577,
            0.0,
            0.8140046105151
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB_98_sink_115574",
        "episode_history": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the sink on the bathroom counter?",
        "answer": "A potted plant.",
        "object_id": 98,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            13.250929832458496,
            0.06217825412750244,
            4.124517917633057
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8940744337339522,
            0.0,
            0.4479184154991984
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB_362_sink_926199",
        "episode_history": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located directly to the right of the sink on the bathroom counter?",
        "answer": "A vase with flowers.",
        "object_id": 362,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            7.5924201011657715,
            0.06217825412750244,
            2.75079607963562
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9980078839919521,
            0.0,
            0.06308932944567867
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB_121_bathtub_360542",
        "episode_history": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bathtub with the plants around it?",
        "answer": "The bathtub is in the bathroom, next to the wall with the towel rack and under the skylight. It has plants placed around it and is adjacent to the toilet.",
        "object_id": 121,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            12.667181015014648,
            0.06217825412750244,
            4.624197959899902
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8756396820855208,
            0.0,
            0.4829649543778183
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB_355_bathtub_22936",
        "episode_history": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to take a bath?",
        "answer": "The bathtub in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 355,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            9.010213851928711,
            0.06217825412750244,
            4.996603965759277
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.00573473291772069,
            0.0,
            0.9999835562839834
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB_199_desk_108817",
        "episode_history": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the wooden object with drawers and a lamp on top, located against the wall between the two doorways?",
        "answer": "A desk.",
        "object_id": 199,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            13.131587982177734,
            0.06217825412750244,
            0.6518819332122803
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9788998514326436,
            0.0,
            0.20434060013895633
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB_382_toilet_512269",
        "episode_history": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the toilet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A wooden cabinet.",
        "object_id": 382,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            9.707893371582031,
            0.06217825412750244,
            9.426717758178711
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.47663323906068356,
            0.0,
            0.8791022440094902
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB_405_washing_machine_853585",
        "episode_history": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the washing machine in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "Wooden cabinets.",
        "object_id": 405,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            10.682716369628906,
            0.06217825412750244,
            9.777145385742188
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6496821292106827,
            0.0,
            0.7602059793136816
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB_406_washing_machine_735813",
        "episode_history": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the washing machine located?",
        "answer": "The washing machine is in the laundry room, to the left of the dryer and under the wooden cabinets.",
        "object_id": 406,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            10.538763046264648,
            0.06217825412750244,
            9.306249618530273
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8751528288469259,
            0.0,
            0.48384659362366417
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB_437_step_stool_200856",
        "episode_history": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the step stool that is placed next to the couch with decorative pillows and near the tall wooden shelf?",
        "answer": "Wood.",
        "object_id": 437,
        "class": "step stool",
        "position": [
            3.93471360206604,
            0.06217825412750244,
            1.8837037086486816
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9710794415969778,
            0.0,
            0.23875660851105443
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB_463_computer_desk_337895",
        "episode_history": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the chair that is placed in front of the computer desk near the window with wooden blinds?",
        "answer": "The chair is black and yellow.",
        "object_id": 463,
        "class": "computer desk",
        "position": [
            5.831550598144531,
            0.06217825412750244,
            2.534841775894165
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.15908019372101526,
            0.0,
            0.9872656643303687
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB_467_keyboard_433567",
        "episode_history": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the keyboard that is on the wooden desk near the window with blinds?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 467,
        "class": "keyboard",
        "position": [
            3.9735851287841797,
            0.06217825412750244,
            0.8703523874282837
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3882289086169895,
            0.0,
            0.9215629737104574
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB_472_monitor_339993",
        "episode_history": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the monitor that is on the wooden desk near the window with blinds?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 472,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            4.170540809631348,
            0.06217825412750244,
            1.7843801975250244
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.17248035213142932,
            0.0,
            0.9850129583556848
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB_656_stool_250897",
        "episode_history": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the small wooden stool that is placed near the windows and the wooden cabinet with a lamp on it?",
        "answer": "The stool is brown.",
        "object_id": 656,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            0.7551162242889404,
            0.06217825412750244,
            7.319398403167725
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.785626133066023,
            0.0,
            0.6187015266214618
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB_546_refrigerator_487313",
        "episode_history": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the refrigerator in the kitchen closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 546,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            5.1442341804504395,
            0.06217825412750244,
            5.291398048400879
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9300240046921504,
            0.0,
            0.36749877645561635
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB_553_dishwasher_756822",
        "episode_history": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the dishwasher under the counter in the kitchen closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 553,
        "class": "dishwasher",
        "position": [
            6.2211761474609375,
            0.06217825412750244,
            8.32790756225586
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.998740888312078,
            0.0,
            0.05016610422964934
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB_554_dishwasher_383481",
        "episode_history": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the dishwasher in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A window with a view outside.",
        "object_id": 554,
        "class": "dishwasher",
        "position": [
            4.036617279052734,
            0.06217825412750244,
            7.682649612426758
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9996612945560146,
            0.0,
            0.02602491434357047
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB_564_led_tv_252425",
        "episode_history": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located to the left of the LED TV on the kitchen counter?",
        "answer": "A small decorative pot.",
        "object_id": 564,
        "class": "led tv",
        "position": [
            4.4753594398498535,
            0.06217825412750244,
            9.787273406982422
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9040371943191703,
            0.0,
            0.4274538001790636
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB_618_led_tv_285355",
        "episode_history": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to watch my favorite TV shows?",
        "answer": "The LED TV on the cabinet.",
        "object_id": 618,
        "class": "led tv",
        "position": [
            1.5169851779937744,
            0.06217825412750244,
            8.20854377746582
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9910903476005857,
            0.0,
            0.13319130186671563
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB_792_radio_140135",
        "episode_history": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the vintage radio located?",
        "answer": "The vintage radio is on the wooden entertainment center in the living room, above the shelves with baskets and electronic devices.",
        "object_id": 792,
        "class": "radio",
        "position": [
            -2.62701416015625,
            0.06217825412750244,
            2.3118844032287598
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7706896144074198,
            0.0,
            0.637210732995406
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB_751_flower_vase_450172",
        "episode_history": "00750-E1NrAhMoqvB",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the large flower vase with the green plant?",
        "answer": "The large flower vase with the green plant is in the corner of the room, near the window and next to a smaller red pot.",
        "object_id": 751,
        "class": "flower vase",
        "position": [
            -8.003724098205566,
            0.06217825412750244,
            1.2720738649368286
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2916353562517849,
            0.0,
            0.9565295703656498
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00758-HfMobPm86Xn_4_fireplace_263267",
        "episode_history": "00758-HfMobPm86Xn",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located to the right of the fireplace in the living room?",
        "answer": "A side table with a lamp on it.",
        "object_id": 4,
        "class": "fireplace",
        "position": [
            1.6729377508163452,
            0.14596408605575562,
            7.340233325958252
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8335129992206783,
            0.0,
            0.5524998462716072
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00758-HfMobPm86Xn_85_sink_957971",
        "episode_history": "00758-HfMobPm86Xn",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located in the corner of the kitchen counter, beneath the wall outlet?",
        "answer": "A sink.",
        "object_id": 85,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            2.6083285808563232,
            0.14596408605575562,
            2.7163734436035156
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8326936470265913,
            0.0,
            0.5537339525454028
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00758-HfMobPm86Xn_292_range_hood_86126",
        "episode_history": "00758-HfMobPm86Xn",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the range hood that is located above the stove and between the white cabinets in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 292,
        "class": "range hood",
        "position": [
            -8.958700180053711,
            0.14596408605575562,
            -2.0474162101745605
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9991481096079989,
            0.0,
            0.04126808775246998
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00758-HfMobPm86Xn_294_stove_526196",
        "episode_history": "00758-HfMobPm86Xn",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the stove that is installed on the white tiled countertop in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 294,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            -10.531655311584473,
            0.14596408605575562,
            -1.3746113777160645
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9083470960681848,
            0.0,
            0.41821711235253867
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00758-HfMobPm86Xn_349_sink_cabinet_922716",
        "episode_history": "00758-HfMobPm86Xn",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the wallpaper above the sink cabinet that is located near the door leading outside?",
        "answer": "The pattern on the wallpaper is a floral design.",
        "object_id": 349,
        "class": "sink cabinet",
        "position": [
            -17.57649803161621,
            0.14596408605575562,
            -4.4512715339660645
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7401421293883788,
            0.0,
            0.6724504653165438
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00758-HfMobPm86Xn_723_tv_978051",
        "episode_history": "00758-HfMobPm86Xn",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the TV on the wooden cabinet in the study room turned off?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 723,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -22.99617576599121,
            0.14596408605575562,
            -3.873248815536499
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5255398435235036,
            0.0,
            0.8507689891323563
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00758-HfMobPm86Xn_752_ottoman_363783",
        "episode_history": "00758-HfMobPm86Xn",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the ottoman in the library room?",
        "answer": "The ottoman is in the library room, placed in front of a yellow armchair next to the bookshelf.",
        "object_id": 752,
        "class": "ottoman",
        "position": [
            -16.2960205078125,
            0.14596408605575562,
            1.0915517807006836
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3379537647766749,
            0.0,
            0.9411627132824971
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00758-HfMobPm86Xn_882_ladder_88320",
        "episode_history": "00758-HfMobPm86Xn",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the ladder leaning against the wall in the storage room upright?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 882,
        "class": "ladder",
        "position": [
            -17.08334732055664,
            0.24471057951450348,
            -8.415473937988281
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9840430216009277,
            0.0,
            0.1779306933570373
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00758-HfMobPm86Xn_904_ladder_83730",
        "episode_history": "00758-HfMobPm86Xn",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object leaning against the wall next to the ironing boards in the storage room?",
        "answer": "A ladder.",
        "object_id": 904,
        "class": "ladder",
        "position": [
            -19.532711029052734,
            0.24941283464431763,
            -8.033610343933105
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8740924682417895,
            0.0,
            0.48575956703185613
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00745-yX5efd48dLf_18_bedside_lamp_73027",
        "episode_history": "00745-yX5efd48dLf",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the bedside lamp on the white nightstand next to the bed in the bedroom turned on?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 18,
        "class": "bedside lamp",
        "position": [
            0.6479666233062744,
            0.05998396873474121,
            3.0139997005462646
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9982532308740539,
            0.0,
            0.059080344019862736
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00745-yX5efd48dLf_56_air_conditioner_115715",
        "episode_history": "00745-yX5efd48dLf",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the air conditioner that is mounted above the framed artwork on the dark wall?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 56,
        "class": "air conditioner",
        "position": [
            2.5902371406555176,
            0.05998396873474121,
            -2.5718908309936523
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.09422544561143492,
            0.0,
            0.9955508853892535
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00745-yX5efd48dLf_62_pouffe_676415",
        "episode_history": "00745-yX5efd48dLf",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the round pouffe in the living room?",
        "answer": "The round pouffe is in the living room, placed near the French doors and next to the curtains. It is positioned close to a small table with a vase on it.",
        "object_id": 62,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            1.4766254425048828,
            0.05998396873474121,
            -2.2264914512634277
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5606158313266845,
            0.0,
            0.8280760168401754
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00745-yX5efd48dLf_65_decorative_plant_24145",
        "episode_history": "00745-yX5efd48dLf",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the pot that holds the decorative plant on the small table near the bay window?",
        "answer": "Blue.",
        "object_id": 65,
        "class": "decorative plant",
        "position": [
            0.13982252776622772,
            0.05998396873474121,
            -3.177276849746704
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.24327530206188747,
            0.0,
            0.969957281227734
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00745-yX5efd48dLf_132_fireplace_722636",
        "episode_history": "00745-yX5efd48dLf",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the fireplace in the living room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 132,
        "class": "fireplace",
        "position": [
            6.396771430969238,
            0.08050898462533951,
            -4.665524959564209
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9696158053505802,
            0.0,
            0.24463276561888914
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00745-yX5efd48dLf_183_oven_405839",
        "episode_history": "00745-yX5efd48dLf",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the oven that is located below the range hood and next to the white cabinets in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 183,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            7.510202407836914,
            0.05998396873474121,
            -3.7291183471679688
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6453930474040431,
            0.0,
            0.7638506492518826
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00745-yX5efd48dLf_195_microwave_430383",
        "episode_history": "00745-yX5efd48dLf",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The microwave is on the countertop in the corner of the kitchen, next to a basket of fruits and under a decorative jar.",
        "object_id": 195,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            9.250974655151367,
            0.05998396873474121,
            -4.619204521179199
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9781111245254711,
            0.0,
            0.2080832239261938
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00745-yX5efd48dLf_348_desk_319515",
        "episode_history": "00745-yX5efd48dLf",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed against the wall with a painting above it in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A desk.",
        "object_id": 348,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            5.374527454376221,
            0.05998396873474121,
            0.013850878924131393
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9586101732485921,
            0.0,
            0.2847218568081917
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00745-yX5efd48dLf_354_guitar_672743",
        "episode_history": "00745-yX5efd48dLf",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the guitar leaning against the dresser?",
        "answer": "Clothes and other items are stacked on top of the dresser above the guitar.",
        "object_id": 354,
        "class": "guitar",
        "position": [
            4.785841941833496,
            0.05998396873474121,
            3.1929874420166016
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2559229277280384,
            0.0,
            0.9666971889185927
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00745-yX5efd48dLf_488_tv_289433",
        "episode_history": "00745-yX5efd48dLf",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to watch my favorite shows and movies?",
        "answer": "The TV on the wooden stand.",
        "object_id": 488,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            1.2244372367858887,
            0.05998396873474121,
            -3.0424675941467285
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9045360424017606,
            0.0,
            0.42639717165591146
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00746-RTV2n6fXB2w_10_tv_735100",
        "episode_history": "00746-RTV2n6fXB2w",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to watch my favorite shows and movies?",
        "answer": "The TV on the wooden cabinet.",
        "object_id": 10,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            4.429856300354004,
            0.09139084070920944,
            -0.19839191436767578
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6548997872344287,
            0.0,
            0.7557157327198503
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00746-RTV2n6fXB2w_15_desk_768578",
        "episode_history": "00746-RTV2n6fXB2w",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wooden desk with the blue pedestal next to it?",
        "answer": "The wooden desk is in the room with patterned wallpaper and wooden flooring, positioned near the window with lace curtains. The blue pedestal is placed right in front of the desk.",
        "object_id": 15,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            3.5318055152893066,
            0.09139084070920944,
            0.272177129983902
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7414639402152096,
            0.0,
            0.6709927163245039
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00746-RTV2n6fXB2w_30_mirror_223567",
        "episode_history": "00746-RTV2n6fXB2w",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object hanging on the wall to the right of the doorway in the hallway?",
        "answer": "A mirror.",
        "object_id": 30,
        "class": "mirror",
        "position": [
            5.367502689361572,
            0.09139084070920944,
            -0.3459836542606354
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6292613589029583,
            0.0,
            0.7771937610349187
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00746-RTV2n6fXB2w_68_piano_stool_151903",
        "episode_history": "00746-RTV2n6fXB2w",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the small red-cushioned object in front of the piano in the living room?",
        "answer": "A piano stool.",
        "object_id": 68,
        "class": "piano stool",
        "position": [
            1.7006748914718628,
            0.09139084070920944,
            1.4452004432678223
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5795306536264021,
            0.0,
            0.814950441135751
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00746-RTV2n6fXB2w_69_christmas_tree_89048",
        "episode_history": "00746-RTV2n6fXB2w",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to decorate for the holiday season?",
        "answer": "The Christmas tree in the living room.",
        "object_id": 69,
        "class": "christmas tree",
        "position": [
            4.041987895965576,
            0.09139084070920944,
            0.9381310939788818
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6427626836794023,
            0.0,
            0.7660653578313359
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00746-RTV2n6fXB2w_80_bookshelf_583571",
        "episode_history": "00746-RTV2n6fXB2w",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are there any books on the small bookshelf next to the piano in the room with the Christmas tree?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 80,
        "class": "bookshelf",
        "position": [
            2.946077585220337,
            0.09139084070920944,
            0.7978538274765015
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8444939110084356,
            0.0,
            0.5355651540846142
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00746-RTV2n6fXB2w_140_globe_stand_606343",
        "episode_history": "00746-RTV2n6fXB2w",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the spherical object on the small table next to the window in the room with patterned wallpaper?",
        "answer": "A globe stand.",
        "object_id": 140,
        "class": "globe stand",
        "position": [
            0.6000385880470276,
            0.09139084070920944,
            0.5259178876876831
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5091420268791933,
            0.0,
            0.8606825178109213
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00746-RTV2n6fXB2w_170_kitchen_table_575184",
        "episode_history": "00746-RTV2n6fXB2w",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the tablecloth that covers the kitchen table surrounded by wooden chairs?",
        "answer": "The tablecloth has a floral pattern.",
        "object_id": 170,
        "class": "kitchen table",
        "position": [
            2.811016082763672,
            0.09139084070920944,
            4.928030967712402
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.659226710489913,
            0.0,
            0.7519442427312336
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00746-RTV2n6fXB2w_218_toilet_463073",
        "episode_history": "00746-RTV2n6fXB2w",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the toilet in the house?",
        "answer": "The toilet is in a small bathroom adjacent to a room with a Christmas tree and presents. It is located next to a sink and under a framed picture on the wall.",
        "object_id": 218,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            1.7478375434875488,
            0.09139084070920944,
            4.820384502410889
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3161116329884294,
            0.0,
            0.9487220011622943
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00746-RTV2n6fXB2w_533_display_cabinet_12573",
        "episode_history": "00746-RTV2n6fXB2w",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the tall, greenish object with glass doors near the window in the room with floral wallpaper?",
        "answer": "A display cabinet.",
        "object_id": 533,
        "class": "display cabinet",
        "position": [
            2.335540294647217,
            3.0544111728668213,
            4.773453712463379
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.16001610412513892,
            0.0,
            0.9871144039171005
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv_19_basket_of_something_13744",
        "episode_history": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is next to the basket of items on the floor near the sofa?",
        "answer": "A heating vent.",
        "object_id": 19,
        "class": "basket of something",
        "position": [
            -0.538489580154419,
            0.035755131393671036,
            -2.652681827545166
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7911082784434308,
            0.0,
            0.6116761330788305
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv_20_coffee_table_394145",
        "episode_history": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on the coffee table in front of the sofa?",
        "answer": "A candle and a tray.",
        "object_id": 20,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            -1.6504875421524048,
            0.06624135375022888,
            -2.194486141204834
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.49262329031050667,
            0.0,
            0.8702426637689342
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv_55_coffee_table_910563",
        "episode_history": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to place my coffee cup and magazines while I relax on the sofa?",
        "answer": "The coffee table in the living room.",
        "object_id": 55,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            -1.576789140701294,
            0.1080285832285881,
            -2.335937976837158
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9953782277518229,
            0.0,
            0.0960322014620015
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv_34_basket_of_towels_703303",
        "episode_history": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the basket of towels?",
        "answer": "The basket of towels is in the living room, placed on the floor between the TV stand and the red armchair.",
        "object_id": 34,
        "class": "basket of towels",
        "position": [
            -0.7909435033798218,
            0.19365596771240234,
            -3.7408909797668457
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7618035264623317,
            0.0,
            0.64780814063236
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv_61_magazine_30497",
        "episode_history": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to read some articles and stay updated with the latest news?",
        "answer": "The magazine on the coffee table.",
        "object_id": 61,
        "class": "magazine",
        "position": [
            0.8447372913360596,
            0.19365596771240234,
            -0.010542377829551697
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8213330248205887,
            0.0,
            0.5704490006469134
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv_67_decorative_lantern_933585",
        "episode_history": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the decorative lantern that is placed on the stone shelf above the stacked firewood?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 67,
        "class": "decorative lantern",
        "position": [
            0.5563069581985474,
            0.11556997150182724,
            1.2252568006515503
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9295180560350733,
            0.0,
            0.36877660379256494
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv_75_side_table_367534",
        "episode_history": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there a book on the side table next to the sofa and under the lamp in the living room?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 75,
        "class": "side table",
        "position": [
            0.24697428941726685,
            0.16067250072956085,
            0.29903483390808105
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9988221819274159,
            0.0,
            0.0485206027349058
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv_231_side_table_267020",
        "episode_history": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the side table near the window?",
        "answer": "A heating vent.",
        "object_id": 231,
        "class": "side table",
        "position": [
            -10.064201354980469,
            0.19365596771240234,
            -2.0463976860046387
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.1890412372146611,
            0.0,
            0.9819691495318731
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv_87_stool_788812",
        "episode_history": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the stool that is placed near the staircase and the large mirror?",
        "answer": "The pattern on the stool is a zebra print.",
        "object_id": 87,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            -1.2757378816604614,
            -0.0043786317110061646,
            -1.5477070808410645
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7247574124822015,
            0.0,
            0.6890041313752073
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv_218_table_877009",
        "episode_history": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the table that is near the colorful painting and surrounded by chairs?",
        "answer": "Rectangular.",
        "object_id": 218,
        "class": "table",
        "position": [
            -13.228948593139648,
            0.021420776844024658,
            -0.9309418201446533
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6068138436194038,
            0.0,
            0.7948439841829626
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv_148_coffee_machine_920880",
        "episode_history": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to make a cup of coffee in the morning?",
        "answer": "The coffee machine on the kitchen counter.",
        "object_id": 148,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            -6.042449951171875,
            0.19365596771240234,
            -2.5609400272369385
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9999910348427138,
            0.0,
            0.004234410518964788
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv_152_fridge_758445",
        "episode_history": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the fridge that is located between the wooden cabinets in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Stainless steel.",
        "object_id": 152,
        "class": "fridge",
        "position": [
            -8.15376091003418,
            0.19365596771240234,
            -2.7157392501831055
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7738729421105449,
            0.0,
            0.6333408793605297
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv_186_bowl_of_fruit_714675",
        "episode_history": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the bowl of fruit on the kitchen counter under the wooden cabinets filled with fruit?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 186,
        "class": "bowl of fruit",
        "position": [
            -6.152316093444824,
            0.19365596771240234,
            -2.7405669689178467
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.08933268215864992,
            0.0,
            0.9960018433207549
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv_194_oven_867392",
        "episode_history": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the oven that is located next to the doorway leading to the room with a lamp and a plant?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 194,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            -7.264899730682373,
            0.19365596771240234,
            -1.9924390316009521
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3668859610831041,
            0.0,
            0.9302659251849048
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv_426_pouffe_629677",
        "episode_history": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the pouffe in front of the red bed in the bedroom covered with a floral pattern?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 426,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            -3.8967158794403076,
            2.79365611076355,
            0.9057490229606628
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6351230658935558,
            0.0,
            0.7724109600270894
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv_454_bathtub_590926",
        "episode_history": "00757-LVgQNuK8vtv",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the window above the bathtub that is next to the white shower curtain?",
        "answer": "Rectangular.",
        "object_id": 454,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            -4.921082496643066,
            2.79365611076355,
            1.0763962268829346
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9985747814834529,
            0.0,
            0.05337045798274547
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00800-TEEsavR23oF_10_tv_839805",
        "episode_history": "00800-TEEsavR23oF",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the TV on the wooden dresser in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A beige armchair with an ottoman.",
        "object_id": 10,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -2.099252223968506,
            3.1633780002593994,
            -6.853832721710205
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9269838824395439,
            0.0,
            0.37510116195142595
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00800-TEEsavR23oF_111_board_163673",
        "episode_history": "00800-TEEsavR23oF",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the small chalkboard with the yellow and blue bag?",
        "answer": "The small chalkboard is leaning against a door in the hallway, with a yellow and blue bag hanging from the door handle.",
        "object_id": 111,
        "class": "board",
        "position": [
            -6.425183296203613,
            3.1633780002593994,
            -4.873526573181152
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.38476290651464695,
            0.0,
            0.9230154417832894
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00800-TEEsavR23oF_138_magazine_599891",
        "episode_history": "00800-TEEsavR23oF",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the bottom shelf of the wooden rack, next to the colorful blankets?",
        "answer": "A magazine.",
        "object_id": 138,
        "class": "magazine",
        "position": [
            -4.584046363830566,
            3.1633780002593994,
            -1.479710578918457
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7939645421972376,
            0.0,
            0.6079640661531988
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00800-TEEsavR23oF_553_trashcan_493407",
        "episode_history": "00800-TEEsavR23oF",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "Is the trashcan in the bathroom placed on a rug or directly on the tile floor?",
        "answer": "The trashcan is placed on a rug.",
        "object_id": 553,
        "class": "trashcan",
        "position": [
            -1.1427191495895386,
            0.16913901269435883,
            -6.954323768615723
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7820348037964572,
            0.0,
            0.6232347596620689
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00800-TEEsavR23oF_510_led_tv_813355",
        "episode_history": "00800-TEEsavR23oF",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to watch my favorite TV shows and movies?",
        "answer": "The LED TV on top of the dresser.",
        "object_id": 510,
        "class": "led tv",
        "position": [
            3.055110216140747,
            0.16337794065475464,
            -7.287457466125488
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9638362546837659,
            0.0,
            0.26649516723042177
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00800-TEEsavR23oF_306_wall_clock_295839",
        "episode_history": "00800-TEEsavR23oF",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the wall clock in the living room?",
        "answer": "A light switch.",
        "object_id": 306,
        "class": "wall clock",
        "position": [
            -4.178521156311035,
            0.16337794065475464,
            -1.9183557033538818
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.28981339824300045,
            0.0,
            0.9570831699485913
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00800-TEEsavR23oF_330_coffee_machine_751794",
        "episode_history": "00800-TEEsavR23oF",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the coffee machine on the kitchen counter next to the toaster and under the cabinets clean?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 330,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            -4.303323268890381,
            0.16337794065475464,
            -0.07960974425077438
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6829878993124323,
            0.0,
            0.7304296881923618
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00800-TEEsavR23oF_334_coffee_machine_225624",
        "episode_history": "00800-TEEsavR23oF",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the coffee machine on the kitchen counter?",
        "answer": "A toaster.",
        "object_id": 334,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            -4.7739105224609375,
            0.16337794065475464,
            -0.3466593623161316
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9150194882501766,
            0.0,
            0.40340963811290437
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00800-TEEsavR23oF_345_microwave_27192",
        "episode_history": "00800-TEEsavR23oF",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The microwave is mounted above the stove in the kitchen, between the dark wooden cabinets.",
        "object_id": 345,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -6.92744779586792,
            0.16337794065475464,
            -1.5599652528762817
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9880355759641469,
            0.0,
            0.15422613471522315
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00800-TEEsavR23oF_361_dishwasher_481621",
        "episode_history": "00800-TEEsavR23oF",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the dishwasher in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The dishwasher is located under the counter, to the right of the sink and below the window with the arched curtain.",
        "object_id": 361,
        "class": "dishwasher",
        "position": [
            -4.115231513977051,
            0.16337794065475464,
            -2.804527759552002
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9998752537494537,
            0.0,
            0.015794839016550148
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00800-TEEsavR23oF_480_dresser_727679",
        "episode_history": "00800-TEEsavR23oF",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on top of the dresser near the windows in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A decorative item and a small box.",
        "object_id": 480,
        "class": "dresser",
        "position": [
            1.229508638381958,
            0.16337794065475464,
            -5.453958511352539
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5035261358831473,
            0.0,
            0.8639799942606231
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00800-TEEsavR23oF_508_laundry_basket_990435",
        "episode_history": "00800-TEEsavR23oF",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to collect my dirty clothes?",
        "answer": "The laundry basket in the corner of the room.",
        "object_id": 508,
        "class": "laundry basket",
        "position": [
            1.6452429294586182,
            0.16337794065475464,
            -5.943447589874268
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8437783809166152,
            0.0,
            0.5366917587384172
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00800-TEEsavR23oF_509_laundry_basket_651215",
        "episode_history": "00800-TEEsavR23oF",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the laundry basket with the white lining?",
        "answer": "The laundry basket with the white lining is in the bedroom, placed on the floor between the dresser and the wall.",
        "object_id": 509,
        "class": "laundry basket",
        "position": [
            3.1635255813598633,
            0.16337794065475464,
            -6.817698955535889
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9887899118707855,
            0.0,
            0.14931346283093053
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00802-wcojb4TFT35_340_sofa_892369",
        "episode_history": "00802-wcojb4TFT35",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are there any cushions on the sofa in the living room near the sliding glass door?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 340,
        "class": "sofa",
        "position": [
            -0.7972826957702637,
            0.19491982460021973,
            -3.4656128883361816
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9283831839595904,
            0.0,
            0.37162435837960484
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00802-wcojb4TFT35_349_tv_257698",
        "episode_history": "00802-wcojb4TFT35",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object mounted above the fireplace in the living room with large windows?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 349,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -0.5291762948036194,
            0.19491982460021973,
            -1.8820936679840088
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9981195225785713,
            0.0,
            0.06129778664455362
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00802-wcojb4TFT35_351_printer_709537",
        "episode_history": "00802-wcojb4TFT35",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the printer on the wooden desk?",
        "answer": "A lamp with a purple shade.",
        "object_id": 351,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            0.4722939729690552,
            0.19491982460021973,
            -4.153059005737305
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7485762408418468,
            0.0,
            0.6630487249419075
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00802-wcojb4TFT35_426_basket_with_books_76070",
        "episode_history": "00802-wcojb4TFT35",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the basket with books located?",
        "answer": "The basket with books is on the floor next to the piano and a large plant in the corner of the room.",
        "object_id": 426,
        "class": "basket with books",
        "position": [
            -1.9468400478363037,
            -0.005079984664916992,
            -6.743984699249268
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.996570767424362,
            0.0,
            0.08274482168221121
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00802-wcojb4TFT35_427_armchair_698968",
        "episode_history": "00802-wcojb4TFT35",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the armchair with the patterned fabric?",
        "answer": "The armchair with the patterned fabric is in the living room, near the large window and next to a small table with two lamps.",
        "object_id": 427,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            -2.750838041305542,
            0.008199036121368408,
            -9.531782150268555
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9997533260533075,
            0.0,
            0.02221006630635887
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00802-wcojb4TFT35_428_armchair_440195",
        "episode_history": "00802-wcojb4TFT35",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object with a floral pattern located to the left of the small table with a lamp in the living room?",
        "answer": "An armchair.",
        "object_id": 428,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            -0.30482223629951477,
            -0.005079984664916992,
            -7.434084892272949
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5570225943772663,
            0.0,
            0.8304973385587816
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00802-wcojb4TFT35_468_refrigerator_443555",
        "episode_history": "00802-wcojb4TFT35",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the refrigerator that is next to the sink and below the three flower paintings in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Stainless steel (silver).",
        "object_id": 468,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            0.9879574775695801,
            0.19491982460021973,
            -10.830708503723145
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9585254571472408,
            0.0,
            0.2850069262328085
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00802-wcojb4TFT35_469_coffee_machine_138070",
        "episode_history": "00802-wcojb4TFT35",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the kitchen counter next to the refrigerator and above the dishwasher?",
        "answer": "A coffee machine.",
        "object_id": 469,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            1.6031603813171387,
            0.1651085615158081,
            -9.283784866333008
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7987175444035658,
            0.0,
            0.6017061444442279
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00802-wcojb4TFT35_579_vacuum_cleaner_583818",
        "episode_history": "00802-wcojb4TFT35",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the vacuum cleaner that is placed next to the music stand and a container with wrapping paper rolls?",
        "answer": "Orange and black.",
        "object_id": 579,
        "class": "vacuum cleaner",
        "position": [
            0.15647296607494354,
            -2.205080032348633,
            -1.3176765441894531
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.11210978728709621,
            0.0,
            0.9936958264954332
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00802-wcojb4TFT35_589_backpack_660879",
        "episode_history": "00802-wcojb4TFT35",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the black and red backpack leaning against the wall in the basement upright?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 589,
        "class": "backpack",
        "position": [
            0.2278878390789032,
            -2.205080032348633,
            0.8231109976768494
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6490779916069084,
            0.0,
            0.76072186823539
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00802-wcojb4TFT35_696_ironing_board_336739",
        "episode_history": "00802-wcojb4TFT35",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the ironing board that is placed near the washing machine and broom in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "Light blue.",
        "object_id": 696,
        "class": "ironing board",
        "position": [
            1.3650351762771606,
            -2.205080032348633,
            -11.672398567199707
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9976898528052276,
            0.0,
            0.06793347929757627
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00802-wcojb4TFT35_700_washing_machine_292597",
        "episode_history": "00802-wcojb4TFT35",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located to the right of the washing machine in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "An ironing board.",
        "object_id": 700,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            1.3801114559173584,
            -2.205080032348633,
            -11.78943157196045
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9582967529511639,
            0.0,
            0.28577496965839405
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00802-wcojb4TFT35_794_curtain_925977",
        "episode_history": "00802-wcojb4TFT35",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the small white curtain located?",
        "answer": "The small white curtain is located in the basement, above the wooden wall paneling near the door.",
        "object_id": 794,
        "class": "curtain",
        "position": [
            1.8783559799194336,
            -2.205080032348633,
            -6.6957244873046875
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9923978569358667,
            0.0,
            0.12307109144352243
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00802-wcojb4TFT35_921_folding_chair_703949",
        "episode_history": "00802-wcojb4TFT35",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "Is the folding chair on the right side of the white metal rack in the garage?",
        "answer": "No, it is in front of the white metal rack.",
        "object_id": 921,
        "class": "folding chair",
        "position": [
            5.446674823760986,
            -0.2050800323486328,
            -14.084165573120117
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5087744913841107,
            0.0,
            0.860899829780933
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00813-svBbv1Pavdk_14_trashcan_329218",
        "episode_history": "00813-svBbv1Pavdk",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the woven trashcan?",
        "answer": "The woven trashcan is located next to the wooden desk in the corner of the room.",
        "object_id": 14,
        "class": "trashcan",
        "position": [
            0.8464276790618896,
            0.07754743099212646,
            -3.3033246994018555
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6757403372214726,
            0.0,
            0.7371397402472685
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00813-svBbv1Pavdk_21_desk_476761",
        "episode_history": "00813-svBbv1Pavdk",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wooden desk with the lamp and computer?",
        "answer": "The wooden desk with the lamp and computer is in the room with wooden flooring, positioned against the wall to the left of the sofa and beneath a wall-mounted picture.",
        "object_id": 21,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            0.8890436887741089,
            0.07754743099212646,
            -0.30546239018440247
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2741394595676843,
            0.0,
            0.9616899483242705
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00813-svBbv1Pavdk_41_toilet_484404",
        "episode_history": "00813-svBbv1Pavdk",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the toilet in the bathroom closed?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 41,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            4.732779026031494,
            0.07754743099212646,
            -1.434255599975586
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5049136365788238,
            0.0,
            0.863169867173749
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00813-svBbv1Pavdk_191_toilet_717233",
        "episode_history": "00813-svBbv1Pavdk",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located between the shower door and the sink in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A toilet.",
        "object_id": 191,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            3.2972097396850586,
            0.07754743099212646,
            5.117977142333984
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9349669282570644,
            0.0,
            0.35473489124351665
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00813-svBbv1Pavdk_57_shower_curtain_38630",
        "episode_history": "00813-svBbv1Pavdk",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the shower curtain that is next to the toilet and the bathtub in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 57,
        "class": "shower curtain",
        "position": [
            4.851751804351807,
            0.07754743099212646,
            -1.5105785131454468
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4553789013505216,
            0.0,
            0.8902977345836571
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00813-svBbv1Pavdk_58_bathtub_325422",
        "episode_history": "00813-svBbv1Pavdk",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the large white object with a curtain inside the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A bathtub.",
        "object_id": 58,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            4.841681480407715,
            0.07754743099212646,
            -1.2977639436721802
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.32564263827086953,
            0.0,
            0.9454929254838387
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00813-svBbv1Pavdk_220_washing_machine_37678",
        "episode_history": "00813-svBbv1Pavdk",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object next to the dryer in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "A washing machine.",
        "object_id": 220,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            0.2627817392349243,
            0.07754743099212646,
            3.4964492321014404
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9875200733836244,
            0.0,
            0.15749318926353936
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00813-svBbv1Pavdk_287_tv_478411",
        "episode_history": "00813-svBbv1Pavdk",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the white stand against the wall in the living room?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 287,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            7.2083282470703125,
            0.07754743099212646,
            1.3313050270080566
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9898332832381234,
            0.0,
            0.14223245548762103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00813-svBbv1Pavdk_381_cook_book_221407",
        "episode_history": "00813-svBbv1Pavdk",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to find a recipe for dinner?",
        "answer": "The cookbook on the kitchen counter.",
        "object_id": 381,
        "class": "cook book",
        "position": [
            0.4622681438922882,
            0.07754743099212646,
            3.463737964630127
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5410155775253757,
            0.0,
            0.8410125711752972
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00814-p53SfW6mjZe_435_tv_900336",
        "episode_history": "00814-p53SfW6mjZe",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to watch my favorite shows and movies?",
        "answer": "The TV on the cabinet.",
        "object_id": 435,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            4.1402692794799805,
            0.004813194274902344,
            4.287630558013916
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9574542636099126,
            0.0,
            0.2885850534854491
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00814-p53SfW6mjZe_178_desk_164524",
        "episode_history": "00814-p53SfW6mjZe",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the small white desk with a wooden top?",
        "answer": "The small white desk with a wooden top is in the bedroom, positioned in front of the windows, between the bed and a wooden dresser with a lamp on it.",
        "object_id": 178,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            -15.741167068481445,
            0.004813194274902344,
            3.4343771934509277
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9999978065893216,
            0.0,
            0.0020944705224595337
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00814-p53SfW6mjZe_203_toilet_brush_holder_448818",
        "episode_history": "00814-p53SfW6mjZe",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "Is there enough space between the toilet brush holder and the vanity to place a small trash can?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 203,
        "class": "toilet brush holder",
        "position": [
            -15.437210083007812,
            0.0904921442270279,
            2.219621181488037
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6462072517009013,
            0.0,
            0.7631619669828731
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00814-p53SfW6mjZe_242_refrigerator_221275",
        "episode_history": "00814-p53SfW6mjZe",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the refrigerator in the laundry room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 242,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -12.711851119995117,
            0.004813194274902344,
            -1.552098035812378
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7864902980123762,
            0.0,
            0.6176026320640188
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00814-p53SfW6mjZe_313_coffee_machine_113994",
        "episode_history": "00814-p53SfW6mjZe",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the coffee machine on the kitchen counter next to the teal coffee maker closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 313,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            -6.579902648925781,
            0.14070218801498413,
            0.3033226728439331
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.917966032153971,
            0.0,
            0.39665900192923254
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00814-p53SfW6mjZe_314_coffee_machine_325861",
        "episode_history": "00814-p53SfW6mjZe",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the coffee machine that is placed on the counter next to the jars of ingredients and under the shelves filled with food items?",
        "answer": "Turquoise.",
        "object_id": 314,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            -6.687315940856934,
            0.11868181079626083,
            0.5235264301300049
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9516759649867638,
            0.0,
            0.3071039851035989
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00814-p53SfW6mjZe_358_microwave_856757",
        "episode_history": "00814-p53SfW6mjZe",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The microwave is built into the kitchen island, which is located in the center of the kitchen. The island is surrounded by wooden beams and pendant lights hanging from the ceiling.",
        "object_id": 358,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -7.008742809295654,
            0.004813194274902344,
            6.894887447357178
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.40095829883856104,
            0.0,
            0.9160963063960509
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00814-p53SfW6mjZe_430_book_847387",
        "episode_history": "00814-p53SfW6mjZe",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What are the objects lined up on top of the dark wooden cabinet next to the stone fireplace in the living room?",
        "answer": "Books.",
        "object_id": 430,
        "class": "book",
        "position": [
            4.162392616271973,
            0.15264379978179932,
            1.6036503314971924
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8191750351151367,
            0.0,
            0.5735436006478623
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00814-p53SfW6mjZe_438_sofa_chair_628067",
        "episode_history": "00814-p53SfW6mjZe",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the beige sofa chair?",
        "answer": "The beige sofa chair is in the living room, positioned in front of the stone fireplace and next to a blue sofa.",
        "object_id": 438,
        "class": "sofa chair",
        "position": [
            -0.2413294017314911,
            0.004813194274902344,
            1.9758323431015015
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7704429517356862,
            0.0,
            0.6375089474829377
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM_48_mirror_524700",
        "episode_history": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the mirror in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A sink with a countertop.",
        "object_id": 48,
        "class": "mirror",
        "position": [
            5.603115081787109,
            2.8239920139312744,
            -1.415201187133789
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8971030219282723,
            0.0,
            0.44182142099174176
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM_59_toilet_936376",
        "episode_history": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located directly above the toilet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A toilet paper holder.",
        "object_id": 59,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            4.214893341064453,
            2.8239920139312744,
            -0.4464605748653412
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.98736186409922,
            0.0,
            0.15848201576997134
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM_89_bedside_lamp_44215",
        "episode_history": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to read a book at night without disturbing others?",
        "answer": "The bedside lamp on the nightstand.",
        "object_id": 89,
        "class": "bedside lamp",
        "position": [
            8.155259132385254,
            2.8239920139312744,
            -0.8353040218353271
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.008960166942586188,
            0.0,
            0.9999598568984462
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM_103_folding_chair_550362",
        "episode_history": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the folding chair on the patio leaning against the wall?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 103,
        "class": "folding chair",
        "position": [
            9.10271167755127,
            0.12470044195652008,
            0.6691467761993408
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9321040962333729,
            0.0,
            0.3621904937805069
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM_208_led_tv_237369",
        "episode_history": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the LED TV mounted on the wall in the living room turned on?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 208,
        "class": "led tv",
        "position": [
            6.798528671264648,
            0.023992061614990234,
            0.49363112449645996
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.10063813365676577,
            0.0,
            0.9949230955476323
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM_333_led_tv_302769",
        "episode_history": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the LED TV located?",
        "answer": "The LED TV is on a wooden stand in the room with a wicker room divider on the left and a guitar hanging on the wall to the right.",
        "object_id": 333,
        "class": "led tv",
        "position": [
            2.352475643157959,
            -2.576007843017578,
            0.05756104364991188
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9668676981561749,
            0.0,
            0.255277994081313
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM_210_fireplace_wall_575254",
        "episode_history": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the fireplace wall that is located beneath the metal chimney and next to the clock?",
        "answer": "Stone.",
        "object_id": 210,
        "class": "fireplace wall",
        "position": [
            5.508730888366699,
            0.023992061614990234,
            0.6771047115325928
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.30101255388974935,
            0.0,
            0.9536201772198252
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM_264_microwave_330681",
        "episode_history": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to quickly heat up my food?",
        "answer": "The microwave on the kitchen counter.",
        "object_id": 264,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            3.7442541122436523,
            0.023992061614990234,
            1.5708067417144775
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8261015312204033,
            0.0,
            0.5635213040474204
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM_265_coffee_machine_844857",
        "episode_history": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to make a cup of coffee in the morning?",
        "answer": "The coffee machine on the kitchen counter.",
        "object_id": 265,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            3.0984654426574707,
            0.023992061614990234,
            1.6760358810424805
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5055702088276641,
            0.0,
            0.8627854680892302
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM_277_refrigerator_616552",
        "episode_history": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the tall, black object located next to the kitchen counter and near the stove?",
        "answer": "A refrigerator.",
        "object_id": 277,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            6.388484001159668,
            0.023992061614990234,
            0.7186675071716309
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6754482864181576,
            0.0,
            0.737407358503273
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM_302_bed_light_374481",
        "episode_history": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on the nightstand next to the bed light?",
        "answer": "A book and a pair of glasses.",
        "object_id": 302,
        "class": "bed light",
        "position": [
            6.010675430297852,
            -2.576007843017578,
            -0.7861350774765015
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.020102160692739426,
            0.0,
            0.9997979311518319
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM_331_guitar_145152",
        "episode_history": "00820-mL8ThkuaVTM",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the primary color of the guitar that is hanging on the wall next to the colorful painting?",
        "answer": "The primary color is beige.",
        "object_id": 331,
        "class": "guitar",
        "position": [
            0.7658165693283081,
            -2.576007843017578,
            0.7993211150169373
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9812997862176157,
            0.0,
            0.1924856606847934
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00824-Dd4bFSTQ8gi_10_sofa_chair_887150",
        "episode_history": "00824-Dd4bFSTQ8gi",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where are the two dark grey sofa chairs located?",
        "answer": "The two dark grey sofa chairs are in the living room, positioned against the wall with a mirror above them, near the entrance to the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 10,
        "class": "sofa chair",
        "position": [
            8.44435977935791,
            0.06882309913635254,
            -3.7428359985351562
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6475930138560716,
            0.0,
            0.7619864095932485
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00824-Dd4bFSTQ8gi_11_sofa_chair_387779",
        "episode_history": "00824-Dd4bFSTQ8gi",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the sofa chair that is positioned near the large mirror with a wooden frame?",
        "answer": "Dark gray.",
        "object_id": 11,
        "class": "sofa chair",
        "position": [
            6.949157238006592,
            0.03027283027768135,
            -3.131875991821289
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.23537113054222575,
            0.0,
            0.971905566867108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00824-Dd4bFSTQ8gi_13_fireplace_wall_363013",
        "episode_history": "00824-Dd4bFSTQ8gi",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the decorative sign on the fireplace wall in the living room standing upright?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 13,
        "class": "fireplace wall",
        "position": [
            6.936933517456055,
            -0.1017330139875412,
            -1.7570250034332275
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6431478875278727,
            0.0,
            0.765741989686105
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00824-Dd4bFSTQ8gi_133_chair_990661",
        "episode_history": "00824-Dd4bFSTQ8gi",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly behind the blue chairs in the hallway?",
        "answer": "A large mirror.",
        "object_id": 133,
        "class": "chair",
        "position": [
            8.174188613891602,
            0.06882309913635254,
            4.737389087677002
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8751192508850559,
            0.0,
            0.48390732245997126
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00824-Dd4bFSTQ8gi_134_chair_474111",
        "episode_history": "00824-Dd4bFSTQ8gi",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are the two blue chairs in the living room positioned next to each other?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 134,
        "class": "chair",
        "position": [
            8.086512565612793,
            0.06882309913635254,
            6.932994842529297
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.47460618620009565,
            0.0,
            0.8801982549520307
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00824-Dd4bFSTQ8gi_176_stool_358846",
        "episode_history": "00824-Dd4bFSTQ8gi",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where are the two white stools located?",
        "answer": "The two white stools are located in the kitchen area, positioned at the counter under the cabinets, near the entrance to the living room.",
        "object_id": 176,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            4.109277725219727,
            0.06882309913635254,
            2.1576809883117676
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3692207417313907,
            0.0,
            0.9293417261025794
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00824-Dd4bFSTQ8gi_179_refrigerator_905210",
        "episode_history": "00824-Dd4bFSTQ8gi",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to store my groceries and keep them fresh?",
        "answer": "The refrigerator in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 179,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            0.33008256554603577,
            0.06882309913635254,
            0.29445549845695496
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.04541144659087893,
            0.0,
            0.9989683681271013
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00824-Dd4bFSTQ8gi_338_cabinet_111232",
        "episode_history": "00824-Dd4bFSTQ8gi",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the cabinet that is next to the bed with the wooden headboard and the lamp on top?",
        "answer": "Dark brown.",
        "object_id": 338,
        "class": "cabinet",
        "position": [
            -2.8567733764648438,
            0.06882309913635254,
            4.682326793670654
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9988806531925851,
            0.0,
            0.047301592759049306
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00824-Dd4bFSTQ8gi_204_tray_270998",
        "episode_history": "00824-Dd4bFSTQ8gi",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the coffee table in the living room?",
        "answer": "A tray.",
        "object_id": 204,
        "class": "tray",
        "position": [
            3.676300525665283,
            0.06882309913635254,
            0.4116934537887573
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.996064084640898,
            0.0,
            0.0886359931883835
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00824-Dd4bFSTQ8gi_381_toilet_229113",
        "episode_history": "00824-Dd4bFSTQ8gi",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the towel hanging next to the toilet that is below a window and near a starfish painting?",
        "answer": "Light blue.",
        "object_id": 381,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -4.1248459815979,
            0.06882309913635254,
            3.2215373516082764
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2955431217949372,
            0.0,
            0.9553294003429932
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs_16_bed_table_472444",
        "episode_history": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bed table with the lamps on it?",
        "answer": "The bed table is in the bedroom, positioned next to the bed and under the wall-mounted lamps. It is adjacent to the fire extinguisher cabinet on the wall.",
        "object_id": 16,
        "class": "bed table",
        "position": [
            3.629289150238037,
            0.13573911786079407,
            -1.8906928300857544
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7890061013738602,
            0.0,
            0.6143853611495166
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs_22_bed_table_874798",
        "episode_history": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the surface of the bed table that is placed between the bed and the sofa?",
        "answer": "Glass.",
        "object_id": 22,
        "class": "bed table",
        "position": [
            4.152352333068848,
            0.13573911786079407,
            1.3823410272598267
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7452337320233668,
            0.0,
            0.6668033328159995
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs_179_desk_469235",
        "episode_history": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wooden desk with the decorative items on top?",
        "answer": "The wooden desk is in the living room, positioned behind the sofa and next to the dining table. It has some decorative items placed on top of it.",
        "object_id": 179,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            0.29177799820899963,
            0.13573911786079407,
            2.660794734954834
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.53659267128527,
            0.0,
            0.8438413980855278
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs_39_bin_777158",
        "episode_history": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located under the desk next to the wooden cabinet in the room?",
        "answer": "A bin.",
        "object_id": 39,
        "class": "bin",
        "position": [
            4.039102554321289,
            0.13573911786079407,
            1.2254234552383423
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5793829460775152,
            0.0,
            0.8150554593366878
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs_186_bin_978650",
        "episode_history": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the green bin under the wooden table in the living room empty?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 186,
        "class": "bin",
        "position": [
            -1.2520709037780762,
            0.13573911786079407,
            2.2333450317382812
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.29274590525609234,
            0.0,
            0.9561902713141307
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs_51_cabinet_942207",
        "episode_history": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the cabinet with the mirror?",
        "answer": "The cabinet with the mirror is in the bedroom, next to the open closet and near the round ottoman.",
        "object_id": 51,
        "class": "cabinet",
        "position": [
            5.577820777893066,
            0.13573911786079407,
            -4.0815629959106445
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8205021163157252,
            0.0,
            0.5716434877801163
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs_66_cabinet_487897",
        "episode_history": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the cabinet with three paintings above it?",
        "answer": "The cabinet is in the walk-in closet, positioned between two open wardrobe sections, with three paintings hanging above it.",
        "object_id": 66,
        "class": "cabinet",
        "position": [
            4.4073805809021,
            0.13573911786079407,
            -2.081815719604492
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.010716575982407396,
            0.0,
            0.9999425758508402
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs_176_bowl_of_sweets_982257",
        "episode_history": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to offer some sweets to my guests?",
        "answer": "The bowl of sweets on the dining table.",
        "object_id": 176,
        "class": "bowl of sweets",
        "position": [
            0.5064483284950256,
            0.13573911786079407,
            0.03161260485649109
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.987025157976489,
            0.0,
            0.16056567977462
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs_197_tv_stand_981270",
        "episode_history": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object directly below the TV in the living room?",
        "answer": "A TV stand.",
        "object_id": 197,
        "class": "tv stand",
        "position": [
            -3.7017691135406494,
            0.13573911786079407,
            -0.2686501145362854
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8764892716824115,
            0.0,
            0.48142139194850475
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs_203_kitchen_cabinet_824367",
        "episode_history": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the white kitchen cabinet next to the sink in the hallway open?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 203,
        "class": "kitchen cabinet",
        "position": [
            -5.592046737670898,
            0.13573911786079407,
            -0.048151496797800064
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.43331570896064836,
            0.0,
            0.901242196286842
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs_237_toilet_345253",
        "episode_history": "00829-QaLdnwvtxbs",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to relieve myself?",
        "answer": "The toilet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 237,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -4.546037197113037,
            0.13573911786079407,
            -3.439164161682129
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4005774704534837,
            0.0,
            0.9162628935873636
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk_77_washing_machine_629471",
        "episode_history": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the washing machine that is next to the dryer and below the shelf with various laundry supplies?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 77,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -5.633413791656494,
            3.219202995300293,
            2.766014575958252
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9815331371603014,
            0.0,
            0.19129218660534705
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk_78_washing_machine_913393",
        "episode_history": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the left side of the dryer in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "A washing machine.",
        "object_id": 78,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -5.63149881362915,
            3.219202995300293,
            2.0653467178344727
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9998190104091492,
            0.0,
            0.019024889605257136
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk_106_sink_cabinet_713295",
        "episode_history": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object directly in front of the bathroom mirror and under the lights?",
        "answer": "A sink cabinet.",
        "object_id": 106,
        "class": "sink cabinet",
        "position": [
            -7.220086097717285,
            3.132370948791504,
            0.9038202166557312
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7159900756404484,
            0.0,
            0.6981104580110407
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk_109_shower_curtain_603982",
        "episode_history": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the shower curtain that is next to the bathtub in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The pattern on the shower curtain consists of floral designs.",
        "object_id": 109,
        "class": "shower curtain",
        "position": [
            -5.120767593383789,
            3.219202995300293,
            2.4044220447540283
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.14538883802126,
            0.0,
            0.9893745932551673
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk_110_shower_tub_836685",
        "episode_history": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the shower curtain in the bathroom pulled closed across the shower tub?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 110,
        "class": "shower tub",
        "position": [
            -4.396554946899414,
            3.219202995300293,
            2.115762710571289
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.1063507546724461,
            0.0,
            0.9943286765353804
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk_157_towel_945672",
        "episode_history": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the beige towel located?",
        "answer": "The beige towel is hanging on a towel rack on the wall between the bathroom sink and the shower.",
        "object_id": 157,
        "class": "towel",
        "position": [
            -1.5244941711425781,
            3.219202995300293,
            0.1271212100982666
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7004359131866709,
            0.0,
            0.7137153014461399
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk_197_dresser_92790",
        "episode_history": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wooden dresser with the lamp on top?",
        "answer": "The wooden dresser with the lamp on top is in the bedroom, positioned against the wall near the window and beside the bed.",
        "object_id": 197,
        "class": "dresser",
        "position": [
            -0.7473977208137512,
            3.219202995300293,
            2.883537769317627
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.755763620742787,
            0.0,
            0.6548445231974936
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk_557_dresser_446807",
        "episode_history": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the candle on the dresser in the corner of the room lit?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 557,
        "class": "dresser",
        "position": [
            -0.33000537753105164,
            -2.580796957015991,
            0.44013598561286926
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3056850534842621,
            0.0,
            0.9521326840710406
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk_278_microwave_129983",
        "episode_history": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the microwave above the stove in the kitchen closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 278,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -9.250808715820312,
            0.01920294761657715,
            3.488971471786499
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.943409996083129,
            0.0,
            0.33162867682157715
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk_320_refrigerator_745952",
        "episode_history": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the stainless steel refrigerator?",
        "answer": "The stainless steel refrigerator is in the kitchen, next to the wooden cabinets and across from the stove.",
        "object_id": 320,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -6.289742469787598,
            0.01920294761657715,
            0.5350212454795837
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9819833832518087,
            0.0,
            0.188967285574334
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk_413_fireplace_924182",
        "episode_history": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the frame around the fireplace that is below the painting of a landscape?",
        "answer": "The frame around the fireplace is gray.",
        "object_id": 413,
        "class": "fireplace",
        "position": [
            0.9008620977401733,
            0.01920294761657715,
            2.675201892852783
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.07640361113604825,
            0.0,
            0.9970769720565065
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk_436_printer_23695",
        "episode_history": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the printer next to the staircase?",
        "answer": "A stack of books and papers.",
        "object_id": 436,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            -0.10249284654855728,
            0.01920294761657715,
            0.9855343699455261
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9594248168801837,
            0.0,
            0.2819645735804868
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk_444_computer_362898",
        "episode_history": "00832-qyAac8rV8Zk",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to browse the internet and check my emails?",
        "answer": "The computer on the desk.",
        "object_id": 444,
        "class": "computer",
        "position": [
            0.1535153090953827,
            0.01920294761657715,
            3.409547805786133
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6866514017328079,
            0.0,
            0.7269868310350401
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s_195_tray_657601",
        "episode_history": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the kitchen counter next to the stove and under the cabinet?",
        "answer": "A tray.",
        "object_id": 195,
        "class": "tray",
        "position": [
            -2.6992855072021484,
            0.03521956503391266,
            0.9074467420578003
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9777209736979683,
            0.0,
            0.2099087839779385
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s_68_bath_sink_297386",
        "episode_history": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash my hands in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The bath sink.",
        "object_id": 68,
        "class": "bath sink",
        "position": [
            -5.271998405456543,
            0.03521956503391266,
            -1.2612794637680054
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3392385849696317,
            0.0,
            0.9407003680597781
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s_70_bathtub_239604",
        "episode_history": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the bathtub in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A showerhead and a shelf with some toiletries.",
        "object_id": 70,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            -6.495546340942383,
            0.03521956503391266,
            -1.2423166036605835
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4036553113388565,
            0.0,
            0.9149111375581406
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s_72_toilet_739496",
        "episode_history": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to relieve myself?",
        "answer": "The toilet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 72,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -5.1621246337890625,
            0.03521956503391266,
            -0.6305168271064758
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.16469199627999154,
            0.0,
            0.9863450442726984
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s_538_toilet_595454",
        "episode_history": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to relieve myself?",
        "answer": "The toilet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 538,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -5.979417324066162,
            2.6352195739746094,
            -1.5845038890838623
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.14539865447546524,
            0.0,
            0.9893731506750748
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s_110_fireplace_314265",
        "episode_history": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to warm up the room on a cold day?",
        "answer": "The fireplace in the corner of the room.",
        "object_id": 110,
        "class": "fireplace",
        "position": [
            -7.267784595489502,
            0.03521956503391266,
            1.3059016466140747
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.49873921880080646,
            0.0,
            0.8667520935249948
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s_112_fireplace_tool_set_45641",
        "episode_history": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the fireplace tool set that is placed next to the radiator and below the window with red floral curtains?",
        "answer": "Metal.",
        "object_id": 112,
        "class": "fireplace tool set",
        "position": [
            -8.426264762878418,
            0.03521956503391266,
            0.5711240172386169
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8182061493739299,
            0.0,
            0.574924949125263
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s_140_stool_458549",
        "episode_history": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the small wooden object on the floor next to the armchair with a red pillow and near the curtains?",
        "answer": "A stool.",
        "object_id": 140,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            -8.025285720825195,
            0.03521956503391266,
            1.6788617372512817
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.881612037351044,
            0.0,
            0.4719748039861253
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s_145_stool_140164",
        "episode_history": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is the stool next to in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "The stool is next to the radiator.",
        "object_id": 145,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            -8.624627113342285,
            0.03521956503391266,
            1.0260223150253296
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8675050973080849,
            0.0,
            0.4974282924648437
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s_144_couch_257423",
        "episode_history": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the blue couch with the white fur throw?",
        "answer": "The blue couch with the white fur throw is in the living room, positioned near the window and next to the wooden cabinet, facing the fireplace.",
        "object_id": 144,
        "class": "couch",
        "position": [
            -6.20900821685791,
            0.03521956503391266,
            1.215783715248108
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8081535018097737,
            0.0,
            0.5889719157248503
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s_165_shelf_770832",
        "episode_history": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the plates on the wooden shelf that is next to the fireplace?",
        "answer": "Blue and white.",
        "object_id": 165,
        "class": "shelf",
        "position": [
            -8.061753273010254,
            0.03521956503391266,
            1.8037786483764648
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3103757398998852,
            0.0,
            0.9506139595448821
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s_166_shelf_199910",
        "episode_history": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wooden shelf with the blue plate?",
        "answer": "The wooden shelf with the blue plate is in the corner of the room, to the right of the fireplace.",
        "object_id": 166,
        "class": "shelf",
        "position": [
            -7.65399169921875,
            0.03521956503391266,
            1.6381090879440308
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3897042670581734,
            0.0,
            0.9209400546380051
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s_558_sink_390077",
        "episode_history": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the sink in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A basket with towels and some round wicker items.",
        "object_id": 558,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            -6.038495063781738,
            2.6352195739746094,
            -2.3618791103363037
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.686734248282538,
            0.0,
            0.7269085721298225
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s_220_kitchen_lower_cabinet_793442",
        "episode_history": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the black lower cabinet next to the sink in the kitchen closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 220,
        "class": "kitchen lower cabinet",
        "position": [
            -3.6993963718414307,
            0.03521956503391266,
            -0.226478710770607
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9508481345885004,
            0.0,
            0.30965759307591406
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s_221_kitchen_lower_cabinet_37644",
        "episode_history": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the lower cabinet under the sink in the kitchen closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 221,
        "class": "kitchen lower cabinet",
        "position": [
            -4.447690010070801,
            0.03521956503391266,
            -0.00381353497505188
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8530393630714405,
            0.0,
            0.5218465723281808
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s_294_washing_machine_27587",
        "episode_history": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the washing machine in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "A dryer.",
        "object_id": 294,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -0.3997475504875183,
            0.03521956503391266,
            0.14027723670005798
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2849685188598734,
            0.0,
            0.9585368763166131
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s_377_tv_424163",
        "episode_history": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the TV that is placed against the wooden wall in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 377,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -4.2309699058532715,
            2.5592944622039795,
            -3.1897847652435303
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6228302225941834,
            0.0,
            0.7823570245247882
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s_469_chair_765724",
        "episode_history": "00835-q3zU7Yy5E5s",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the red cushioned chair in the bedroom next to the small wooden cabinet empty?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 469,
        "class": "chair",
        "position": [
            -7.034058094024658,
            2.6352195739746094,
            2.051335096359253
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2649133174442854,
            0.0,
            0.9642722303585556
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG_66_board_133545",
        "episode_history": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the primary color of the board that is labeled \"Snack Place\" and located between two windows in the game room?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 66,
        "class": "board",
        "position": [
            1.9466605186462402,
            0.11293673515319824,
            1.1509103775024414
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.14057689664672884,
            0.0,
            0.9900697632637687
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG_124_exercise_machine_416675",
        "episode_history": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located to the right of the exercise machine in the game room?",
        "answer": "A snack bar display.",
        "object_id": 124,
        "class": "exercise machine",
        "position": [
            0.5920218825340271,
            0.11293673515319824,
            1.6796033382415771
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.16156753506889612,
            0.0,
            0.9868616577878386
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG_126_basket_792494",
        "episode_history": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is inside the basket next to the sofa and exercise equipment?",
        "answer": "A stuffed Dalmatian toy.",
        "object_id": 126,
        "class": "basket",
        "position": [
            1.0096325874328613,
            0.11293673515319824,
            -0.3626962900161743
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.666388795034612,
            0.0,
            0.7456044352418498
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG_181_computer_chair_431795",
        "episode_history": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object in front of the desk and below the wall-mounted TV in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A computer chair.",
        "object_id": 181,
        "class": "computer chair",
        "position": [
            -3.7535388469696045,
            0.11293673515319824,
            1.8051189184188843
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3851008096089981,
            0.0,
            0.9228745128339465
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG_641_computer_chair_385583",
        "episode_history": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object in front of the desk and below the wall art in the office room?",
        "answer": "A computer chair.",
        "object_id": 641,
        "class": "computer chair",
        "position": [
            4.907873153686523,
            -2.8870632648468018,
            5.898019790649414
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.25962421679444053,
            0.0,
            0.9657097214245455
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG_276_floor_lamp_609142",
        "episode_history": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the tall object with a light source next to the black couch in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "A floor lamp.",
        "object_id": 276,
        "class": "floor lamp",
        "position": [
            4.674298286437988,
            0.11293673515319824,
            5.975578308105469
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5764396952846694,
            0.0,
            0.817139692892297
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG_514_coffee_table_717979",
        "episode_history": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the coffee table with the tray on top?",
        "answer": "The coffee table is in the living room, positioned in front of the sectional sofa and near the fireplace.",
        "object_id": 514,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            5.781752109527588,
            -2.8870632648468018,
            7.463989734649658
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8240018387251636,
            0.0,
            0.5665871246132845
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG_286_dog_bed_638876",
        "episode_history": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the floor between the two chairs in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "A dog bed.",
        "object_id": 286,
        "class": "dog bed",
        "position": [
            5.742187023162842,
            0.11293673515319824,
            7.067086219787598
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.458991993101274,
            0.0,
            0.8884404033298576
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG_314_footstool_588315",
        "episode_history": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the blanket on the footstool at the end of the bed in the bedroom neatly folded?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 314,
        "class": "footstool",
        "position": [
            5.096391677856445,
            0.11293673515319824,
            6.472653865814209
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9844684062362856,
            0.0,
            0.17556183276153417
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG_408_basket_of_something_21617",
        "episode_history": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the basket that is placed on the floor below the hanging clothes and next to the shoe rack?",
        "answer": "The basket has a striped pattern.",
        "object_id": 408,
        "class": "basket of something",
        "position": [
            -3.1750006675720215,
            0.11293673515319824,
            10.215106010437012
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9863243302453698,
            0.0,
            0.1648160051876757
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG_462_toilet_498655",
        "episode_history": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the toilet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The toilet is located next to the sink and under the shelves, adjacent to the shower curtain in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 462,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -1.4038885831832886,
            0.11293673515319824,
            6.357975006103516
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9861791197160263,
            0.0,
            0.16568266003454182
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG_566_kitchen_island_226465",
        "episode_history": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are there any items placed on the kitchen island in the center of the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 566,
        "class": "kitchen island",
        "position": [
            0.29455676674842834,
            -2.8870632648468018,
            8.258499145507812
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8259228140931375,
            0.0,
            0.5637832075900032
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG_579_microwave_348080",
        "episode_history": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the microwave on the kitchen counter next to the refrigerator closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 579,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -3.410860776901245,
            -2.8870632648468018,
            9.539275169372559
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5631499464605118,
            0.0,
            0.8263547287947971
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG_585_microwave_283931",
        "episode_history": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the microwave in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The microwave is mounted above the stove, between the white cabinets and next to the refrigerator in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 585,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -2.935206890106201,
            -2.8870632648468018,
            10.878868103027344
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4464064889550144,
            0.0,
            0.8948302892833124
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG_586_refrigerator_244527",
        "episode_history": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the large silver object next to the stove in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A refrigerator.",
        "object_id": 586,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -2.983067512512207,
            -2.8870632648468018,
            10.86417293548584
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.246186521358828,
            0.0,
            0.9692224701796999
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG_622_printer_477117",
        "episode_history": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the white printer on the turquoise desk in the study room closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 622,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            6.007255554199219,
            -2.8870632648468018,
            5.681453227996826
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9423825597137632,
            0.0,
            0.33453715959118047
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG_629_printer_428637",
        "episode_history": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located on the bottom shelf of the white storage unit, below the basket with folded clothes?",
        "answer": "A printer.",
        "object_id": 629,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            5.562469482421875,
            -2.8870632648468018,
            5.700959205627441
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8436023962050587,
            0.0,
            0.5369683390266908
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG_805_cabinet_table_119381",
        "episode_history": "00839-zt1RVoi7PcG",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the piece of furniture against the wall with multiple framed pictures above it and decorative items on top in the hallway?",
        "answer": "A cabinet table.",
        "object_id": 805,
        "class": "cabinet table",
        "position": [
            -1.525500774383545,
            -2.8870632648468018,
            -0.2270679622888565
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8843665900922331,
            0.0,
            0.46679303157677515
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00843-DYehNKdT76V_34_bath_cabinet_866954",
        "episode_history": "00843-DYehNKdT76V",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the bath cabinet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A toilet.",
        "object_id": 34,
        "class": "bath cabinet",
        "position": [
            -6.821103096008301,
            3.3365070819854736,
            -5.502967357635498
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.689087935578634,
            0.0,
            0.7246777332304176
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00843-DYehNKdT76V_49_led_tv_242530",
        "episode_history": "00843-DYehNKdT76V",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the LED TV mounted on the wall in the room turned off?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 49,
        "class": "led tv",
        "position": [
            -0.23538559675216675,
            3.3365070819854736,
            0.08102539926767349
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6664200290838794,
            0.0,
            0.7455765184311006
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00843-DYehNKdT76V_191_led_tv_206431",
        "episode_history": "00843-DYehNKdT76V",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the LED TV in the living room?",
        "answer": "The staircase.",
        "object_id": 191,
        "class": "led tv",
        "position": [
            -3.370487928390503,
            0.1365068554878235,
            -2.5243232250213623
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5255589737791276,
            0.0,
            0.8507571716302075
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00843-DYehNKdT76V_187_table_879369",
        "episode_history": "00843-DYehNKdT76V",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object between the two sofas in the living room?",
        "answer": "A table.",
        "object_id": 187,
        "class": "table",
        "position": [
            -4.365281581878662,
            0.1365068554878235,
            -3.7568981647491455
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.49987612553225097,
            0.0,
            0.8660969109302176
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00843-DYehNKdT76V_239_stove_446120",
        "episode_history": "00843-DYehNKdT76V",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located on the kitchen counter, directly below the cabinets and next to the sink?",
        "answer": "A stove.",
        "object_id": 239,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            3.491978168487549,
            0.1365068554878235,
            -1.9492790699005127
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4562164647235092,
            0.0,
            0.8898688315224795
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR_11_dog_bed_973009",
        "episode_history": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is next to the dog bed in the living room?",
        "answer": "A wooden cabinet with a TV on top.",
        "object_id": 11,
        "class": "dog bed",
        "position": [
            -0.5448609590530396,
            0.021223172545433044,
            1.9872981309890747
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9932120610208284,
            0.0,
            0.11631767639855749
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR_172_armchair_728923",
        "episode_history": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wooden armchair with white cushions?",
        "answer": "The wooden armchair with white cushions is in the bedroom, near the window with curtains, next to the door.",
        "object_id": 172,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            -4.2231903076171875,
            0.021223172545433044,
            5.215692520141602
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9991710538140732,
            0.0,
            0.04070878553929594
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR_65_bench_683026",
        "episode_history": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed between the dining table and the window in the dining room?",
        "answer": "A bench.",
        "object_id": 65,
        "class": "bench",
        "position": [
            3.4700160026550293,
            0.021223172545433044,
            5.664754867553711
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8459517143450176,
            0.0,
            0.533259502490791
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR_86_dishwasher_543853",
        "episode_history": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to clean the dirty dishes after a meal?",
        "answer": "The dishwasher under the counter.",
        "object_id": 86,
        "class": "dishwasher",
        "position": [
            4.071466445922852,
            0.021223172545433044,
            2.643756151199341
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.871136788047277,
            0.0,
            0.4910404224813608
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR_95_cooker_515838",
        "episode_history": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the oven door of the cooker in the kitchen closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 95,
        "class": "cooker",
        "position": [
            5.358122825622559,
            0.021223172545433044,
            4.020600318908691
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.019043022339102763,
            0.0,
            0.999818665208943
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR_135_washer-dryer_722607",
        "episode_history": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What are the two large white appliances next to each other in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "A washer and a dryer.",
        "object_id": 135,
        "class": "washer-dryer",
        "position": [
            3.953899383544922,
            0.021223172545433044,
            -0.4309365153312683
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7168473130836812,
            0.0,
            0.6972301841750017
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR_136_washer-dryer_887645",
        "episode_history": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where are the washer and dryer located?",
        "answer": "The washer and dryer are in the laundry room, positioned side by side against the far wall, beneath a white cabinet.",
        "object_id": 136,
        "class": "washer-dryer",
        "position": [
            3.865246534347534,
            0.021223172545433044,
            0.31823208928108215
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.737700932842072,
            0.0,
            0.6751276425120931
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR_155_book_816418",
        "episode_history": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed under the lamp on the nightstand next to the bed?",
        "answer": "A book.",
        "object_id": 155,
        "class": "book",
        "position": [
            -3.0725667476654053,
            0.021223172545433044,
            7.338715553283691
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.710515600611776,
            0.0,
            0.7036814487303805
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR_243_toilet_741267",
        "episode_history": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lid of the toilet in the bathroom closed?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 243,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -5.373894691467285,
            0.021223172545433044,
            2.056452751159668
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8213568640616158,
            0.0,
            0.5704146753537013
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR_257_bathroom_cabinet_807032",
        "episode_history": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the door of the bathroom cabinet under the sink in the bathroom open?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 257,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            -3.734511375427246,
            0.021223172545433044,
            1.0107691287994385
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8948790689969474,
            0.0,
            0.44630869571537246
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR_207_bathtub_115986",
        "episode_history": "00848-ziup5kvtCCR",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located directly above the bathtub in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A towel rack with a white towel hanging on it.",
        "object_id": 207,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            -5.212846279144287,
            0.021223172545433044,
            6.3650712966918945
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4580156295349566,
            0.0,
            0.8889441394720465
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_454_toilet_521743",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the toilet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The toilet is located next to the shower area, opposite the wooden vanity with the red flowers on top.",
        "object_id": 454,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            3.3955042362213135,
            0.018403440713882446,
            -2.2244410514831543
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8211765199381079,
            0.0,
            0.5706742705802832
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_97_storage_shelving_562826",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is stored on the top shelf of the storage shelving in the closet?",
        "answer": "Several storage boxes.",
        "object_id": 97,
        "class": "storage shelving",
        "position": [
            -2.7721052169799805,
            0.07936184108257294,
            5.137097358703613
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4075764276595148,
            0.0,
            0.9131710987631553
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_160_air_conditioner_755311",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the portable air conditioner that is placed next to the white distressed dresser near the bathroom entrance?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 160,
        "class": "air conditioner",
        "position": [
            -0.7514466643333435,
            0.018403440713882446,
            4.946180820465088
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4577791138241656,
            0.0,
            0.8890659609648554
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_165_armchair_382920",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the armchair with the floral upholstery?",
        "answer": "The armchair with the floral upholstery is in the bedroom, positioned between the large mirror and the dresser, near the window with sheer curtains.",
        "object_id": 165,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            0.7334417104721069,
            0.06386011838912964,
            2.168463706970215
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5874817517176499,
            0.0,
            0.8092374134941869
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_251_armchair_157046",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly in front of the armchair in the living room?",
        "answer": "A round wooden side table with a decorative lamp on it.",
        "object_id": 251,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            6.644309997558594,
            0.018403440713882446,
            1.60310959815979
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8325218806273146,
            0.0,
            0.5539921644542993
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_205_table_511769",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is hanging on the wall to the left of the table in the hallway?",
        "answer": "A mirror.",
        "object_id": 205,
        "class": "table",
        "position": [
            3.1457018852233887,
            0.018403440713882446,
            1.500941276550293
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3096886685696333,
            0.0,
            0.9508380138380921
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_209_display_cabinet_791810",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the tall, white object with glass doors located against the wall in the hallway?",
        "answer": "A display cabinet.",
        "object_id": 209,
        "class": "display cabinet",
        "position": [
            5.902946472167969,
            0.018403440713882446,
            1.9602279663085938
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.32629488156317465,
            0.0,
            0.9452680309127532
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_231_wall_tv_304153",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the frame of the wall-mounted TV that is above the wooden console table?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 231,
        "class": "wall tv",
        "position": [
            3.8422889709472656,
            0.018403440713882446,
            1.923706293106079
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9239410648778843,
            0.0,
            0.3825348462981131
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_363_wall_tv_711819",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the wall-mounted TV above the fireplace in the living room turned on?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 363,
        "class": "wall tv",
        "position": [
            11.306158065795898,
            0.06262651085853577,
            -4.466220378875732
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.24856588969085625,
            0.0,
            0.9686149898087439
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_252_coffee_table_909962",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there a decorative item on the round coffee table in the living room?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 252,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            2.551365613937378,
            0.018403440713882446,
            2.1047890186309814
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9518475915062237,
            0.0,
            0.3065716271017286
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_391_coffee_table_570912",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the coffee table that is placed between the two blue sofas in the living room?",
        "answer": "The pattern consists of circular designs in various shades of blue and white.",
        "object_id": 391,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            11.29334831237793,
            0.018403440713882446,
            -2.8137454986572266
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2886390627952379,
            0.0,
            0.9574379830718471
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_288_refrigerator_501624",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the large metallic object in the kitchen area next to the dining room?",
        "answer": "A refrigerator.",
        "object_id": 288,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            8.896174430847168,
            0.018403440713882446,
            2.9034337997436523
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.29574281272013364,
            0.0,
            0.9552676005834092
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_319_microwave_940356",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to quickly heat up my leftovers?",
        "answer": "The microwave in the kitchen island.",
        "object_id": 319,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            8.21211051940918,
            0.018403440713882446,
            -0.11944505572319031
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2758229990231693,
            0.0,
            0.9612084442044112
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_352_computer_desk_498231",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the computer desk with dual monitors?",
        "answer": "The computer desk with dual monitors is located in the living room, next to the fireplace and near the sliding glass doors that lead to the patio.",
        "object_id": 352,
        "class": "computer desk",
        "position": [
            8.52525520324707,
            0.018403440713882446,
            -6.521356582641602
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7135751997030223,
            0.0,
            0.7005786425297248
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_353_monitor_810612",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly behind the monitor on the wooden shelves?",
        "answer": "Framed artwork and a decorative plate.",
        "object_id": 353,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            11.303720474243164,
            0.06055106222629547,
            -4.747272491455078
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.10161591219835521,
            0.0,
            0.9948237061852195
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_354_monitor_445408",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the computer monitor located?",
        "answer": "The computer monitor is on the corner desk in the study area, next to the shelves with framed pictures and a decorative plate.",
        "object_id": 354,
        "class": "monitor",
        "position": [
            10.704169273376465,
            0.172956183552742,
            -5.179174423217773
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.24591919580024868,
            0.0,
            0.9692903327367703
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_357_office_chair_779591",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object in front of the desk and next to the fireplace in the living room?",
        "answer": "An office chair.",
        "object_id": 357,
        "class": "office chair",
        "position": [
            11.404518127441406,
            0.044768884778022766,
            -4.1987762451171875
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.08436465111800583,
            0.0,
            0.9964349480230695
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_365_fireplace_686615",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the fireplace with the TV mounted above it?",
        "answer": "The fireplace is in the living room, centered between two wooden shelves, with a TV mounted above it. There is a blue sofa to the left and a desk with a computer chair to the right.",
        "object_id": 365,
        "class": "fireplace",
        "position": [
            11.200835227966309,
            0.07669786363840103,
            -4.881832599639893
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2418918926025481,
            0.0,
            0.9703032063706465
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_395_decorative_bowl_503274",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the primary color of the decorative bowl that is on the round wooden table next to the lamp and the blue sofa?",
        "answer": "Brown.",
        "object_id": 395,
        "class": "decorative bowl",
        "position": [
            8.003240585327148,
            0.018403440713882446,
            -2.414958953857422
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.2579123683631925,
            0.0,
            0.9661683136210217
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_400_sofa_61036",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the blue sofa with the yellow and white pillows?",
        "answer": "The blue sofa with the yellow and white pillows is in the living room, positioned against the wall to the right of the sliding glass door and next to a matching blue armchair.",
        "object_id": 400,
        "class": "sofa",
        "position": [
            9.688739776611328,
            0.028451137244701385,
            -6.442912578582764
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.999976741341748,
            0.0,
            0.006820320787624241
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_416_washing_machine_580418",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the washing machine located?",
        "answer": "The washing machine is in the hallway, stacked with the dryer, between the doorways leading to the living room and the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 416,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            4.791873455047607,
            0.018403440713882446,
            -3.320614814758301
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9860153470212449,
            0.0,
            0.166654539207836
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_417_washing_machine_747380",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the washing machine that is stacked below the dryer in the laundry area?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 417,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            3.781935453414917,
            0.018403440713882446,
            -3.0931148529052734
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9960100565478823,
            0.0,
            0.08924106260840628
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_445_bathroom_towel_350263",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is mounted on the wall above the bathroom towel?",
        "answer": "A decorative metal sculpture of bicycles.",
        "object_id": 445,
        "class": "bathroom towel",
        "position": [
            2.6310551166534424,
            0.03134240210056305,
            -1.8188514709472656
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4854827148728464,
            0.0,
            0.8742462659684002
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_446_bathroom_towel_582968",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Are the bathroom towels hanging on the rack next to the shower dry?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 446,
        "class": "bathroom towel",
        "position": [
            2.4224133491516113,
            0.06777824461460114,
            -1.8692474365234375
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5093859993996995,
            0.0,
            0.8605381476817686
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_484_bar_chair_685837",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the white bar chair?",
        "answer": "The white bar chair is in the room with blue walls and wooden floors, positioned in front of a white ornate desk under the ceiling fan.",
        "object_id": 484,
        "class": "bar chair",
        "position": [
            3.7947120666503906,
            0.018403440713882446,
            -3.6082406044006348
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5183792700256432,
            0.0,
            0.8551508243623935
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL_515_bedside_lamp_288699",
        "episode_history": "00853-5cdEh9F2hJL",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the bedside lamp on the white nightstand next to the bed in the bedroom turned on?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 515,
        "class": "bedside lamp",
        "position": [
            5.993978977203369,
            0.21840344369411469,
            -4.610485076904297
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7264338139377906,
            0.0,
            0.687236432363561
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00873-bxsVRursffK_162_backpack_494442",
        "episode_history": "00873-bxsVRursffK",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the green backpack with the black patch?",
        "answer": "The green backpack with the black patch is hanging on a wire rack on the wall, next to a yellow hard hat and a stuffed tiger toy, in the room with the \"Under Construction\" sign.",
        "object_id": 162,
        "class": "backpack",
        "position": [
            -7.986814498901367,
            0.02467513084411621,
            -5.1858367919921875
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.45010900490216477,
            0.0,
            0.8929736187066127
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00873-bxsVRursffK_424_backpack_853633",
        "episode_history": "00873-bxsVRursffK",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to carry my belongings when I go out?",
        "answer": "The backpack hanging on the wall.",
        "object_id": 424,
        "class": "backpack",
        "position": [
            0.18045097589492798,
            -2.975324869155884,
            0.38384538888931274
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.041906302533755935,
            0.0,
            0.999121545062436
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00873-bxsVRursffK_179_nightstand_397929",
        "episode_history": "00873-bxsVRursffK",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on top of the nightstand next to the bed in the construction-themed room?",
        "answer": "A lamp and a toy truck.",
        "object_id": 179,
        "class": "nightstand",
        "position": [
            -8.58664321899414,
            0.02467513084411621,
            -3.65348219871521
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.10935177533314211,
            0.0,
            0.9940031132906426
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00873-bxsVRursffK_192_washing_machine_589268",
        "episode_history": "00873-bxsVRursffK",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash my clothes?",
        "answer": "The washing machine in the laundry room.",
        "object_id": 192,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -5.826694965362549,
            0.02467513084411621,
            -3.2207720279693604
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9110645621156039,
            0.0,
            0.41226370645146876
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00873-bxsVRursffK_220_bath_towel_986100",
        "episode_history": "00873-bxsVRursffK",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color pattern of the bath towel that is hanging next to the striped shower curtain in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "The bath towel is white with a subtle pattern.",
        "object_id": 220,
        "class": "bath towel",
        "position": [
            -5.8997883796691895,
            0.02467513084411621,
            -0.43795672059059143
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.622212882274717,
            0.0,
            0.7828480881572039
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00873-bxsVRursffK_305_fireplace_994523",
        "episode_history": "00873-bxsVRursffK",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the wall that the fireplace is built into, which is next to a large abstract painting and a potted plant?",
        "answer": "Blue.",
        "object_id": 305,
        "class": "fireplace",
        "position": [
            -5.397519111633301,
            -2.975324869155884,
            -0.641883134841919
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8622638323143534,
            0.0,
            0.50645936014903
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00873-bxsVRursffK_437_mirror_71528",
        "episode_history": "00873-bxsVRursffK",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the mirror in the house?",
        "answer": "The mirror is in the bathroom, which is located through the doorway next to the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 437,
        "class": "mirror",
        "position": [
            -5.283166885375977,
            -2.975324869155884,
            -2.6398415565490723
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.0009784936344138986,
            0.0,
            0.9999995212749891
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00873-bxsVRursffK_323_flower_vase_454081",
        "episode_history": "00873-bxsVRursffK",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed in the center of the dining table next to the small plant in the dining area?",
        "answer": "A flower vase.",
        "object_id": 323,
        "class": "flower vase",
        "position": [
            -2.9922871589660645,
            -2.975324869155884,
            -1.1927331686019897
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8928825457003392,
            0.0,
            0.450289639658389
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00873-bxsVRursffK_324_candle_holder_168370",
        "episode_history": "00873-bxsVRursffK",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the candle inside the black lantern-style candle holder on the dining table in the dining room lit?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 324,
        "class": "candle holder",
        "position": [
            -5.766668319702148,
            -2.975324869155884,
            -0.45925837755203247
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7436311453725343,
            0.0,
            0.6685900983651589
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00873-bxsVRursffK_358_refrigerator_113167",
        "episode_history": "00873-bxsVRursffK",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the stainless steel refrigerator?",
        "answer": "The stainless steel refrigerator is in the kitchen, next to the white door and opposite the kitchen island with a plate of vegetables on it.",
        "object_id": 358,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -6.397934913635254,
            -2.975324869155884,
            -3.5686638355255127
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.12137183124280021,
            0.0,
            0.9926071118931041
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00873-bxsVRursffK_364_kitchen_island_707069",
        "episode_history": "00873-bxsVRursffK",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is there a bowl of fruit on the kitchen island in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 364,
        "class": "kitchen island",
        "position": [
            -9.675832748413086,
            -2.975324869155884,
            -2.34737491607666
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3974717267408484,
            0.0,
            0.9176144214438047
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00873-bxsVRursffK_372_microwave_552816",
        "episode_history": "00873-bxsVRursffK",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to quickly heat up my leftovers?",
        "answer": "The microwave above the stove.",
        "object_id": 372,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -8.833938598632812,
            -2.975324869155884,
            -4.15123176574707
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.13727547068631013,
            0.0,
            0.9905329096743086
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00873-bxsVRursffK_380_coffee_machine_948740",
        "episode_history": "00873-bxsVRursffK",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the coffee machine that is placed next to the sink and under the window with blinds?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 380,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            -8.672690391540527,
            -2.975324869155884,
            -4.33673095703125
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3720054262470447,
            0.0,
            0.9282305547883858
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00873-bxsVRursffK_388_oven_and_stove_882511",
        "episode_history": "00873-bxsVRursffK",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the oven and stove in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A microwave.",
        "object_id": 388,
        "class": "oven and stove",
        "position": [
            -8.729082107543945,
            -2.975324869155884,
            -3.584871768951416
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.0999465165728987,
            0.0,
            0.9949928109413371
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00873-bxsVRursffK_425_bench_624211",
        "episode_history": "00873-bxsVRursffK",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the bench with black cushion?",
        "answer": "The bench with the black cushion is in the entryway, placed against the wall with patterned wallpaper, near the front door.",
        "object_id": 425,
        "class": "bench",
        "position": [
            -2.184084177017212,
            -2.975324869155884,
            -0.5847078561782837
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6431046453109794,
            0.0,
            0.7657783068091177
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53_77_newspaper_287118",
        "episode_history": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to catch up on the latest news?",
        "answer": "The newspaper on the wooden table.",
        "object_id": 77,
        "class": "newspaper",
        "position": [
            5.494961261749268,
            0.050354525446891785,
            7.942243576049805
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6789858210548977,
            0.0,
            0.7341513841207454
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53_78_newspaper_872085",
        "episode_history": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the newspaper that is on the wooden coffee table in front of the couch with blue and patterned pillows?",
        "answer": "The newspaper has a predominantly white color with some colored images and text.",
        "object_id": 78,
        "class": "newspaper",
        "position": [
            4.179234504699707,
            0.050354525446891785,
            9.171245574951172
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.18283784921245808,
            0.0,
            0.9831430826158329
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53_82_table_lamp_365357",
        "episode_history": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the table lamp with the white shade?",
        "answer": "The table lamp with the white shade is on a small wooden side table behind the sofa in the living room, near the large display cabinet with decorative vases.",
        "object_id": 82,
        "class": "table lamp",
        "position": [
            1.071166753768921,
            0.050354525446891785,
            7.144635200500488
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9282967156471901,
            0.0,
            0.37184029867490126
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53_83_pouffe_90128",
        "episode_history": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the small, round, upholstered object next to the wooden chair in front of the fireplace?",
        "answer": "A pouffe.",
        "object_id": 83,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            7.302702903747559,
            0.12950235605239868,
            7.614536285400391
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9250948719208486,
            0.0,
            0.37973606353064404
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53_401_pouffe_71593",
        "episode_history": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the round, woven object next to the wicker chair in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "A pouffe.",
        "object_id": 401,
        "class": "pouffe",
        "position": [
            -9.176655769348145,
            0.050354525446891785,
            6.842696189880371
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2295646524216019,
            0.0,
            0.9732934143199311
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53_89_led_tv_684323",
        "episode_history": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the cabinet next to the fireplace in the living room?",
        "answer": "An LED TV.",
        "object_id": 89,
        "class": "led tv",
        "position": [
            4.442086219787598,
            0.050354525446891785,
            9.6304349899292
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8773274522465548,
            0.0,
            0.47989221866432574
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53_222_led_tv_916382",
        "episode_history": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is being displayed on the LED TV that is mounted above the wooden cabinet near the large mirror?",
        "answer": "A scenic view of the ocean.",
        "object_id": 222,
        "class": "led tv",
        "position": [
            10.732342720031738,
            0.050354525446891785,
            -0.39196890592575073
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9983619034821385,
            0.0,
            0.057214593204232035
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53_107_ventilation_hood_314577",
        "episode_history": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the ventilation hood in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The ventilation hood is above the stove, between the cabinets and next to the window in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 107,
        "class": "ventilation hood",
        "position": [
            -0.2758404016494751,
            0.050354525446891785,
            3.001784324645996
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9046691756279943,
            0.0,
            0.42611463559535856
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53_133_coffee_machine_313563",
        "episode_history": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located between the toaster and the bread box on the kitchen counter?",
        "answer": "A coffee machine.",
        "object_id": 133,
        "class": "coffee machine",
        "position": [
            -1.642567753791809,
            0.050354525446891785,
            5.612570762634277
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9911377775662173,
            0.0,
            0.13283789324248282
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53_561_sofa_seat_802656",
        "episode_history": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the fabric of the sofa seat that is placed near the floor lamp and the window with sheer curtains?",
        "answer": "The pattern on the fabric of the sofa seat is striped.",
        "object_id": 561,
        "class": "sofa seat",
        "position": [
            4.850558757781982,
            0.050354525446891785,
            12.63966178894043
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9685043488442184,
            0.0,
            0.2489966390733744
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53_310_bathtub_312698",
        "episode_history": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to take a relaxing bath?",
        "answer": "The bathtub in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 310,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            4.107905864715576,
            0.050354525446891785,
            -3.075998306274414
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8818003105319129,
            0.0,
            0.47162295570277574
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53_613_bathtub_196517",
        "episode_history": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the large object with a faucet located in the corner of the bathroom under the windows?",
        "answer": "A bathtub.",
        "object_id": 613,
        "class": "bathtub",
        "position": [
            -0.42361438274383545,
            0.050354525446891785,
            15.188457489013672
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9586293397949024,
            0.0,
            0.2846573183397705
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53_340_washing_machine_918857",
        "episode_history": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash my clothes?",
        "answer": "The washing machine in the laundry room.",
        "object_id": 340,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -3.743954658508301,
            0.050354525446891785,
            10.44320011138916
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.419031878106966,
            0.0,
            0.9079715222021827
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53_368_toilet_981797",
        "episode_history": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to relieve myself?",
        "answer": "The toilet in the bathroom.",
        "object_id": 368,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -1.2535338401794434,
            0.050354525446891785,
            9.749466896057129
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.47962473553758617,
            0.0,
            0.8774737107517812
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53_591_safe_729744",
        "episode_history": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located on the middle shelf of the closet next to the hanging white robes?",
        "answer": "A safe.",
        "object_id": 591,
        "class": "safe",
        "position": [
            -1.5446341037750244,
            0.050354525446891785,
            12.606123924255371
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.04745144280653418,
            0.0,
            0.9988735458382999
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53_615_bath_towel_127727",
        "episode_history": "00876-mv2HUxq3B53",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to dry myself after a bath?",
        "answer": "The bath towel on the rack above the bathtub.",
        "object_id": 615,
        "class": "bath towel",
        "position": [
            -0.3548712432384491,
            0.059650614857673645,
            16.636425018310547
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8483907560814773,
            0.0,
            0.5293704987959749
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_1_bench_343026",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wooden bench with storage?",
        "answer": "The wooden bench with storage is in the room near the window, positioned between the door and a wooden chair.",
        "object_id": 1,
        "class": "bench",
        "position": [
            0.06333646178245544,
            -0.5355252027511597,
            2.46638822555542
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.17206933542171227,
            0.0,
            0.9850848409185526
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_4_refrigerator_476933",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the refrigerator in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "Three framed pieces of artwork depicting deer.",
        "object_id": 4,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            1.4469027519226074,
            -0.5355252027511597,
            3.609546184539795
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.956028300943969,
            0.0,
            0.2932744240369204
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_334_refrigerator_71307",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to keep my food cold?",
        "answer": "The refrigerator in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 334,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            5.331406116485596,
            2.0644748210906982,
            3.3467252254486084
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.796396974930261,
            0.0,
            0.6047742209468997
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_8_chair_695549",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the wooden chair with a backrest near the window in the room empty?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 8,
        "class": "chair",
        "position": [
            -0.11038213968276978,
            -0.23708203434944153,
            0.6387770771980286
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5778694990078949,
            0.0,
            0.8161291822477399
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_10_speaker_945581",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the middle shelf of the wooden cabinet in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "A speaker.",
        "object_id": 10,
        "class": "speaker",
        "position": [
            2.5244760513305664,
            -0.5355252027511597,
            0.7242802381515503
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.26017791694164544,
            0.0,
            0.9655606928287347
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_379_toilet_831582",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the toilet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A wooden cabinet.",
        "object_id": 379,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            3.386443614959717,
            2.0644748210906982,
            3.4264280796051025
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9800263787963067,
            0.0,
            0.198867535971556
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_98_mirror_293840",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the reflective object above the sink in the bathroom next to the hallway?",
        "answer": "A mirror.",
        "object_id": 98,
        "class": "mirror",
        "position": [
            3.2046847343444824,
            -0.5355252027511597,
            5.681288719177246
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3662087240288462,
            0.0,
            0.930532734752069
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_115_laundry_machine_860086",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the white appliance located directly in front of the doorway in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "A laundry machine.",
        "object_id": 115,
        "class": "laundry machine",
        "position": [
            6.432289123535156,
            -0.5355252027511597,
            3.026949644088745
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9999955375521542,
            0.0,
            0.0029874523013917625
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_160_couch_603710",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located to the right of the couch in the room?",
        "answer": "A small wooden side table.",
        "object_id": 160,
        "class": "couch",
        "position": [
            7.114259719848633,
            -0.5355252027511597,
            3.113454818725586
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8543077055428822,
            0.0,
            0.5197675867635997
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_201_nightstand_354254",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What items are on the nightstand next to the bed?",
        "answer": "A lamp, a phone, and some miscellaneous items.",
        "object_id": 201,
        "class": "nightstand",
        "position": [
            7.190281391143799,
            -0.5355252027511597,
            1.2915855646133423
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8117307400888831,
            0.0,
            0.5840318532364088
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_414_nightstand_429886",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on top of the nightstand next to the bed?",
        "answer": "A picture frame and a lamp.",
        "object_id": 414,
        "class": "nightstand",
        "position": [
            1.9164760112762451,
            2.0644748210906982,
            1.4139392375946045
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7388576071987544,
            0.0,
            0.6738615854049934
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_274_lamp_table_954651",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the lamp on the wooden table next to the black leather sofa in the living room turned on?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 274,
        "class": "lamp table",
        "position": [
            8.955086708068848,
            2.0644748210906982,
            0.3416248857975006
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.5172594292594845,
            0.0,
            0.8558286527349691
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_292_lamp_table_916147",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object next to the black armchair and under the lamp in the living room?",
        "answer": "A lamp table.",
        "object_id": 292,
        "class": "lamp table",
        "position": [
            9.740363121032715,
            2.0644748210906982,
            0.5085940361022949
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9989847270757174,
            0.0,
            0.045050139505057804
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_275_table_lamp_536440",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object on the wooden side table next to the blue armchair in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "A table lamp.",
        "object_id": 275,
        "class": "table lamp",
        "position": [
            7.843356132507324,
            2.0644748210906982,
            -0.5989872217178345
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6028751576222435,
            0.0,
            0.7978355371390492
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_283_tv_375168",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the wooden table between the two windows in the room?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 283,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            7.696114540100098,
            2.0644748210906982,
            1.2233426570892334
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.3576648202722173,
            0.0,
            0.9338500288267075
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_284_tv_stand_59609",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the material of the TV stand that is placed between two windows with blinds?",
        "answer": "Wood.",
        "object_id": 284,
        "class": "tv stand",
        "position": [
            9.492788314819336,
            2.0644748210906982,
            1.9212675094604492
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.009598620948029747,
            0.0,
            0.9999539321768258
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_487_armchair_332893",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the wooden armchair with the carved backrest?",
        "answer": "The wooden armchair with the carved backrest is in the room next to the large window with blinds, beside the wooden cabinet with double doors.",
        "object_id": 487,
        "class": "armchair",
        "position": [
            0.6328015327453613,
            2.0644748210906982,
            4.243118762969971
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9238199176994721,
            0.0,
            0.3828273235569012
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_298_dining_table_516022",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object in the dining area near the sliding glass door and surrounded by wooden chairs?",
        "answer": "A dining table.",
        "object_id": 298,
        "class": "dining table",
        "position": [
            7.260719299316406,
            2.0644748210906982,
            2.453247547149658
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9674887752138142,
            0.0,
            0.25291395737537775
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_324_microwave_569700",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the black microwave located in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "The black microwave is mounted above the stove, between the wooden cabinets in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 324,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            7.892483711242676,
            2.0644748210906982,
            5.006319999694824
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.6980428318054379,
            0.0,
            0.7160560068633215
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_374_bathroom_cabinet_805580",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the bathroom cabinet?",
        "answer": "The toilet.",
        "object_id": 374,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            3.1128273010253906,
            2.0644748210906982,
            3.170210599899292
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9578588858918577,
            0.0,
            0.28723919425804173
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_391_bathroom_cabinet_255287",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "Where can I store my toiletries and bathroom supplies?",
        "answer": "The bathroom cabinet above the toilet.",
        "object_id": 391,
        "class": "bathroom cabinet",
        "position": [
            2.290731191635132,
            2.0644748210906982,
            3.8445839881896973
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7796824693678559,
            0.0,
            0.6261750928937069
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_469_file_cabinet_713837",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located between the desk and the door in the office room?",
        "answer": "A file cabinet.",
        "object_id": 469,
        "class": "file cabinet",
        "position": [
            2.036479949951172,
            2.0644748210906982,
            4.3686981201171875
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6839905518464636,
            0.0,
            0.7294908669646044
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_472_file_cabinet_325363",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object next to the small table with a lamp and under the printer in the office room?",
        "answer": "A file cabinet.",
        "object_id": 472,
        "class": "file cabinet",
        "position": [
            1.7990957498550415,
            2.0644748210906982,
            5.198550701141357
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6125635941619227,
            0.0,
            0.7904213073465487
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_475_desk_lamp_382912",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the lampshade on the desk lamp that is placed on the dark wooden desk near the window?",
        "answer": "The lampshade is in a conical shape.",
        "object_id": 475,
        "class": "desk lamp",
        "position": [
            0.2961709201335907,
            2.0644748210906982,
            4.756808280944824
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9592811294426136,
            0.0,
            0.28245303095435825
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00877-4ok3usBNeis_481_recycle_bin_771292",
        "episode_history": "00877-4ok3usBNeis",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the left of the recycle bin near the closed door?",
        "answer": "A black filing cabinet.",
        "object_id": 481,
        "class": "recycle bin",
        "position": [
            0.8671058416366577,
            2.0644748210906982,
            5.753949165344238
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.08498464159556762,
            0.0,
            0.9963822613298939
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00878-XB4GS9ShBRE_140_coffee_table_789149",
        "episode_history": "00878-XB4GS9ShBRE",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the small round object next to the armchair and under the lamp in the corner of the room?",
        "answer": "A coffee table.",
        "object_id": 140,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            -2.2695424556732178,
            2.7961292266845703,
            -0.9485067129135132
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.669188863588387,
            0.0,
            0.7430923662972747
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00878-XB4GS9ShBRE_228_coffee_table_441348",
        "episode_history": "00878-XB4GS9ShBRE",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the coffee table that is placed near the large window and the television stand?",
        "answer": "Brown.",
        "object_id": 228,
        "class": "coffee table",
        "position": [
            -0.3396279215812683,
            0.19612908363342285,
            -0.008036687970161438
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.37656353780008783,
            0.0,
            0.9263907933477544
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00878-XB4GS9ShBRE_178_box_657828",
        "episode_history": "00878-XB4GS9ShBRE",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "Is the box on top of the dresser large enough to store some small accessories?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 178,
        "class": "box",
        "position": [
            -1.496328592300415,
            2.7961292266845703,
            -0.5159375667572021
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.09326917593497833,
            0.0,
            0.995640929663104
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00878-XB4GS9ShBRE_210_wall_clock_796480",
        "episode_history": "00878-XB4GS9ShBRE",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly below the wall clock in the dining area?",
        "answer": "A wooden cabinet with a chair in front of it.",
        "object_id": 210,
        "class": "wall clock",
        "position": [
            0.007579362019896507,
            0.19612908363342285,
            -1.5531615018844604
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.18672972734250395,
            0.0,
            0.9824113236962378
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00878-XB4GS9ShBRE_236_led_tv_472647",
        "episode_history": "00878-XB4GS9ShBRE",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly above the LED TV in the living room?",
        "answer": "A framed picture.",
        "object_id": 236,
        "class": "led tv",
        "position": [
            -1.611450433731079,
            -0.0038709640502929688,
            -2.0004847049713135
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.929121084262958,
            0.0,
            0.36977562220625826
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo_31_tv_984656",
        "episode_history": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the shape of the TV that is mounted on the wall above the wooden entertainment center?",
        "answer": "It is in rectangular shape.",
        "object_id": 31,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -10.086912155151367,
            0.1808570772409439,
            -1.3187310695648193
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5176073998182369,
            0.0,
            0.855618244109722
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo_125_tv_311932",
        "episode_history": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the TV that is placed on the wooden dresser in the bedroom?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 125,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -11.817434310913086,
            0.1808570772409439,
            4.722902774810791
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.32397206304054343,
            0.0,
            0.9460666479531208
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo_45_microwave_70951",
        "episode_history": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the microwave that is installed above the stove and next to the dark brown cabinets?",
        "answer": "Stainless steel (silver).",
        "object_id": 45,
        "class": "microwave",
        "position": [
            -7.699667930603027,
            0.1808570772409439,
            2.099489450454712
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9026855232846802,
            0.0,
            0.43030087851672255
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo_51_trashcan_60138",
        "episode_history": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the trashcan that is placed next to the kitchen island in the open living area?",
        "answer": "Silver.",
        "object_id": 51,
        "class": "trashcan",
        "position": [
            -13.24041748046875,
            0.1808570772409439,
            1.9157731533050537
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5925235622905247,
            0.0,
            0.8055531193723644
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo_55_refrigerator_10207",
        "episode_history": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is on top of the refrigerator in the kitchen?",
        "answer": "A yellow bag and some other items.",
        "object_id": 55,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -9.484916687011719,
            0.1808570772409439,
            -0.0571683794260025
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.835325752915189,
            0.0,
            0.5497552969428057
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo_60_coffee_maker_590881",
        "episode_history": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to make a cup of coffee in the morning?",
        "answer": "The coffee maker on the countertop next to the refrigerator.",
        "object_id": 60,
        "class": "coffee maker",
        "position": [
            -8.163409233093262,
            0.1808570772409439,
            2.004575490951538
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7050826615487522,
            0.0,
            0.7091251232210911
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo_297_bench_164708",
        "episode_history": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the wooden object placed against the right wall in the hallway leading to the closet?",
        "answer": "A bench.",
        "object_id": 297,
        "class": "bench",
        "position": [
            -11.146766662597656,
            0.1808570772409439,
            5.582221031188965
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.770321766149186,
            0.0,
            0.6376553744749578
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo_170_washing_machine_564758",
        "episode_history": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash my clothes?",
        "answer": "The washing machine in the laundry room.",
        "object_id": 170,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -4.708504676818848,
            0.1808570772409439,
            0.784656822681427
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9801637460438234,
            0.0,
            0.19818938150501486
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo_211_desk_717815",
        "episode_history": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the desk with the laptop and yellow water bottle?",
        "answer": "The desk with the laptop and yellow water bottle is in the room with the large window, next to the open door leading to another room.",
        "object_id": 211,
        "class": "desk",
        "position": [
            -3.3103129863739014,
            0.1808570772409439,
            -1.8109952211380005
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2354377348398045,
            0.0,
            0.9718894345621326
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo_212_laptop_949516",
        "episode_history": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the laptop in the house?",
        "answer": "The laptop is on a black desk near the window in a room with a blue chair and a door leading to another room.",
        "object_id": 212,
        "class": "laptop",
        "position": [
            -3.3557536602020264,
            0.1808570772409439,
            -2.931748390197754
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3604151434529565,
            0.0,
            0.93279200488093
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo_213_laptop_813959",
        "episode_history": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to browse the internet and check my emails?",
        "answer": "The laptop on the desk.",
        "object_id": 213,
        "class": "laptop",
        "position": [
            -5.229260444641113,
            0.1808570772409439,
            -3.1932878494262695
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5293033787797311,
            0.0,
            0.8484326332787775
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo_256_toilet_875036",
        "episode_history": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located between the shower curtain and the sink cabinet in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A toilet.",
        "object_id": 256,
        "class": "toilet",
        "position": [
            -0.09000344574451447,
            0.1808570772409439,
            -2.325075626373291
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.35923213250388064,
            0.0,
            0.9332482386678875
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo_323_clothes_203974",
        "episode_history": "00880-Nfvxx8J5NCo",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to find something to wear for the day?",
        "answer": "The clothes hanging in the closet.",
        "object_id": 323,
        "class": "clothes",
        "position": [
            -7.522064208984375,
            0.1808570772409439,
            5.719764709472656
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.7156261156203509,
            0.0,
            0.6984835450045536
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW_33_tv_stand_145573",
        "episode_history": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the TV stand that is placed against the wall near the brown sofa?",
        "answer": "Brown.",
        "object_id": 33,
        "class": "tv stand",
        "position": [
            7.228524208068848,
            0.09943583607673645,
            -1.7497837543487549
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7535454136002753,
            0.0,
            0.6573958545975097
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW_34_tv_758338",
        "episode_history": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the wooden stand against the wall in the living room?",
        "answer": "A tv.",
        "object_id": 34,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            3.1745448112487793,
            0.09943583607673645,
            -3.381988763809204
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9697806341708113,
            0.0,
            0.24397852689788033
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW_35_table_641597",
        "episode_history": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object in the center of the living room, placed between the two sofas?",
        "answer": "A table.",
        "object_id": 35,
        "class": "table",
        "position": [
            1.7855111360549927,
            0.09943583607673645,
            -1.4193634986877441
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5017081841497925,
            0.0,
            0.8650369344468003
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW_57_stool_794099",
        "episode_history": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is located to the right of the stool near the radiator?",
        "answer": "A children's playset with toys.",
        "object_id": 57,
        "class": "stool",
        "position": [
            0.8145708441734314,
            0.12251806259155273,
            -1.7987436056137085
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.2848457588375165,
            0.0,
            0.9585733637402405
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW_167_dining_table_91566",
        "episode_history": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the large wooden object in the center of the kitchen, surrounded by chairs?",
        "answer": "A dining table.",
        "object_id": 167,
        "class": "dining table",
        "position": [
            19.07863426208496,
            0.09943583607673645,
            -0.5628103017807007
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.6565097952901612,
            0.0,
            0.7543174985959631
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW_178_range_hood_791682",
        "episode_history": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the light under the range hood in the kitchen turned on?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 178,
        "class": "range hood",
        "position": [
            19.13793182373047,
            0.09943583607673645,
            -0.10179410129785538
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3118617340202922,
            0.0,
            0.9501274961045262
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW_210_jacket_330096",
        "episode_history": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the jacket that is hanging above the radiator and next to the door?",
        "answer": "The pattern on the jacket is floral.",
        "object_id": 210,
        "class": "jacket",
        "position": [
            23.577280044555664,
            0.09943583607673645,
            -0.8018702864646912
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7568542858272814,
            0.0,
            0.6535836518953605
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW_211_jacket_476530",
        "episode_history": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object hanging above the radiator and next to the door in the entryway?",
        "answer": "A jacket.",
        "object_id": 211,
        "class": "jacket",
        "position": [
            23.270111083984375,
            0.09943583607673645,
            -0.9666162729263306
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7587060770767255,
            0.0,
            0.6514331037081597
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW_217_washing_machine_287537",
        "episode_history": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the washing machine that is placed next to the dryer and below the shelf with cleaning supplies and bags?",
        "answer": "White.",
        "object_id": 217,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            22.673828125,
            0.09943583607673645,
            -0.38736701011657715
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4586154310155758,
            0.0,
            0.8886348442607895
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW_249_bedside_lamp_182854",
        "episode_history": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the woven bedside lamp?",
        "answer": "The woven bedside lamp is on the nightstand next to the bed in the bedroom, near the hallway entrance.",
        "object_id": 249,
        "class": "bedside lamp",
        "position": [
            2.3056883811950684,
            2.8994359970092773,
            -0.5336230993270874
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.4945424865630528,
            0.0,
            0.8691534553713934
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW_250_bedside_cabinet_73158",
        "episode_history": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the bedside cabinet that is next to the bed with brown and beige bedding?",
        "answer": "The color of the bedside cabinet is gray.",
        "object_id": 250,
        "class": "bedside cabinet",
        "position": [
            1.731553316116333,
            2.8994359970092773,
            -0.28043699264526367
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.5359766489844572,
            0.0,
            0.8442328066021789
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW_279_shelf_372276",
        "episode_history": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the shelf that is mounted on the blue wall above the dresser with a changing pad?",
        "answer": "Dark brown.",
        "object_id": 279,
        "class": "shelf",
        "position": [
            5.240277290344238,
            2.8994359970092773,
            -3.509000539779663
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.7770248267310093,
            0.0,
            0.6294699505485908
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW_405_potty_362539",
        "episode_history": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the white potty with a green base next to the radiator in the bathroom empty?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 405,
        "class": "potty",
        "position": [
            19.9735050201416,
            0.09943583607673645,
            -0.9414316415786743
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9831813614686645,
            0.0,
            0.18263189880364192
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW_557_scale_732690",
        "episode_history": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the primary color of the scale that is placed on the wooden floor near the bookshelf filled with books?",
        "answer": "Black.",
        "object_id": 557,
        "class": "scale",
        "position": [
            10.45923137664795,
            2.8994359970092773,
            -0.7651274800300598
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.21707968591588608,
            0.0,
            0.9761538864147703
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW_651_handbag_188502",
        "episode_history": "00890-6s7QHgap2fW",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the dark grey couch near the large mirror in the room?",
        "answer": "A handbag.",
        "object_id": 651,
        "class": "handbag",
        "position": [
            0.9251031875610352,
            2.8994359970092773,
            -1.6843280792236328
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9894702685042935,
            0.0,
            0.14473626962872937
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5_16_statue_484696",
        "episode_history": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is the color of the wall behind the statue in the alcove?",
        "answer": "Beige.",
        "object_id": 16,
        "class": "statue",
        "position": [
            -2.2999367713928223,
            0.07216382026672363,
            3.0299575328826904
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.291603410326759,
            0.0,
            0.9565393097441441
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5_27_lamp_table_179311",
        "episode_history": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object placed on the small round table at the base of the staircase in the hallway?",
        "answer": "A lamp.",
        "object_id": 27,
        "class": "lamp table",
        "position": [
            -2.603778839111328,
            0.07216382026672363,
            0.7429194450378418
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.8893323829151516,
            0.0,
            0.4572613177368695
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5_55_couch_721041",
        "episode_history": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the color of the throw pillows on the couch that is placed near the staircase with wooden railings?",
        "answer": "The throw pillows are a mix of colors, including shades of brown, beige, and red with various patterns.",
        "object_id": 55,
        "class": "couch",
        "position": [
            3.6107473373413086,
            0.07216382026672363,
            -0.01772761344909668
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9614532642886977,
            0.0,
            0.2749683992545464
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5_123_refrigerator_338846",
        "episode_history": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the stainless steel refrigerator?",
        "answer": "The stainless steel refrigerator is in the kitchen, next to the double oven and near the doorway leading to the adjacent room.",
        "object_id": 123,
        "class": "refrigerator",
        "position": [
            -1.1242729425430298,
            0.07216382026672363,
            7.199704647064209
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.1665237528768812,
            0.0,
            0.9860374433700778
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5_124_oven_378118",
        "episode_history": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to bake a cake?",
        "answer": "The oven in the kitchen.",
        "object_id": 124,
        "class": "oven",
        "position": [
            -2.399749994277954,
            0.07216382026672363,
            7.16313362121582
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.24995132429970407,
            0.0,
            0.9682584032585642
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5_145_stove_415800",
        "episode_history": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the stove with the red kettle on it?",
        "answer": "The stove is in the kitchen, located between the microwave and the corner of the countertop, with a red kettle sitting on it.",
        "object_id": 145,
        "class": "stove",
        "position": [
            0.2519806921482086,
            0.07216382026672363,
            5.44042444229126
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9624993677870092,
            0.0,
            0.2712839232420661
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5_870_sink_616866",
        "episode_history": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is to the right of the sink in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A urinal.",
        "object_id": 870,
        "class": "sink",
        "position": [
            -9.394806861877441,
            -2.9278361797332764,
            4.058708667755127
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4156408087213681,
            0.0,
            0.9095288440315937
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5_200_printer_273757",
        "episode_history": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the printer on the wooden stand next to the window in the study room turned on?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 200,
        "class": "printer",
        "position": [
            -2.7308053970336914,
            0.07216382026672363,
            -0.9094235897064209
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.49278050162218595,
            0.0,
            0.8701536515012661
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5_205_computer_desk_954441",
        "episode_history": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the chair at the computer desk in the study room pushed in?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 205,
        "class": "computer desk",
        "position": [
            -1.611738920211792,
            0.07216382026672363,
            1.8718061447143555
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.34476716027805804,
            0.0,
            0.9386882364202738
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5_206_computer_chair_705002",
        "episode_history": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the computer chair behind the wooden desk in the study room pushed in?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "object_id": 206,
        "class": "computer chair",
        "position": [
            -2.0498502254486084,
            0.07216382026672363,
            1.316878080368042
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.41422024394209844,
            0.0,
            0.9101766803805449
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5_340_bedside_lamp_485174",
        "episode_history": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What is the pattern on the lampshade of the bedside lamp that is on the wooden nightstand next to the bed with red pillows?",
        "answer": "The pattern on the lampshade is a geometric design with a combination of blue and white colors.",
        "object_id": 340,
        "class": "bedside lamp",
        "position": [
            -5.439718723297119,
            3.0721640586853027,
            3.5557632446289062
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.962792921438893,
            0.0,
            0.27024024575766326
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5_370_circular_sofa_9354",
        "episode_history": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where is the circular sofa with intricate patterns?",
        "answer": "The circular sofa with intricate patterns is in the bathroom, placed on a brown rug between the two sinks and in front of the bathtub.",
        "object_id": 370,
        "class": "circular sofa",
        "position": [
            -7.44792366027832,
            3.0721640586853027,
            3.3374123573303223
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.248335832501303,
            0.0,
            0.9686739979455858
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5_859_trashcan_76514",
        "episode_history": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to dispose of small bathroom waste?",
        "answer": "The trashcan next to the toilet.",
        "object_id": 859,
        "class": "trashcan",
        "position": [
            -9.715682983398438,
            -2.9278361797332764,
            3.263533115386963
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.29517591938309634,
            0.0,
            0.9554429216946159
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5_559_washing_machine_849360",
        "episode_history": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5",
        "category": "attribute recognition",
        "question": "What color is the washing machine that is next to the dryer and beneath the wooden cabinets in the laundry room?",
        "answer": "Red.",
        "object_id": 559,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -7.350297451019287,
            0.07216382026672363,
            2.176107883453369
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8118250693820624,
            0.0,
            0.583900725057616
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5_560_washing_machine_560962",
        "episode_history": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5",
        "category": "functional reasoning",
        "question": "What can I use to wash my clothes?",
        "answer": "The washing machine next to the dryer.",
        "object_id": 560,
        "class": "washing machine",
        "position": [
            -8.575244903564453,
            0.07216382026672363,
            2.1733057498931885
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.8264901706300115,
            0.0,
            0.5629511505023989
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5_696_tv_907340",
        "episode_history": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the TV mounted on the wall in the living room turned off?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 696,
        "class": "tv",
        "position": [
            -7.000385761260986,
            -2.9278361797332764,
            8.321883201599121
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9671481723627323,
            0.0,
            0.254213321239125
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5_700_guitar_614082",
        "episode_history": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5",
        "category": "object state recognition",
        "question": "Is the black acoustic guitar leaning against the wall in the corner of the room on a stand?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "object_id": 700,
        "class": "guitar",
        "position": [
            -6.125790596008301,
            -2.9278361797332764,
            8.437820434570312
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.9987189740350234,
            0.0,
            0.05060050298574712
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5_701_guitar_267733",
        "episode_history": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5",
        "category": "object localization",
        "question": "Where are the guitars located?",
        "answer": "The guitars are in the corner of the room, near the window with the brown walls and red carpet.",
        "object_id": 701,
        "class": "guitar",
        "position": [
            -6.7750678062438965,
            -2.9278361797332764,
            8.414785385131836
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            -0.9766790626923539,
            0.0,
            0.21470446781188393
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5_804_file_cabinet_764581",
        "episode_history": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object located in the corner of the room, beneath the wall decorations and next to the bookshelf?",
        "answer": "A file cabinet.",
        "object_id": 804,
        "class": "file cabinet",
        "position": [
            -2.4369421005249023,
            -2.9278361797332764,
            0.91386479139328
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.3281533575416457,
            0.0,
            0.9446244618546277
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5_807_desk_chair_358908",
        "episode_history": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5",
        "category": "object recognition",
        "question": "What is the object in front of the desk in the room with the stone wall and bookshelves?",
        "answer": "A desk chair.",
        "object_id": 807,
        "class": "desk chair",
        "position": [
            -1.5307989120483398,
            -2.9278361797332764,
            1.977579951286316
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.4899341836156979,
            0.0,
            0.8717594253719426
        ]
    },
    {
        "question_id": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5_860_urinal_702861",
        "episode_history": "00891-cvZr5TUy5C5",
        "category": "spatial understanding",
        "question": "What is directly to the right of the urinal in the bathroom?",
        "answer": "A toilet paper holder.",
        "object_id": 860,
        "class": "urinal",
        "position": [
            -9.092357635498047,
            -2.9278361797332764,
            3.9689955711364746
        ],
        "rotation": [
            0.0,
            0.16071753220962157,
            0.0,
            0.9870004431814857
        ]
    }
]